[
      {
        "question":"No, no don't! Stop cleansing my aura! No, just leave my aura alone, okay? I'll befine, alright? Really, everyone. I hope she'll be very happy.",
        "response":"No you don't.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, so I'm back in high school, I'm standing in the middle of thecafeteria, and I realize I am totally naked.",
        "response":"Oh, yeah. Had that dream.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And you never knew she was a lesbian...",
        "response":"No!! Okay?! Why does everyone keep fixating on that? She didn't know, how should Iknow?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No I don't, to hell with her, she left me!",
        "response":"And you never knew she was a lesbian...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah. Had that dream.",
        "response":"Then I look down, and I realize there's a phone... there.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Then I look down, and I realize there's a phone... there.",
        "response":"Instead of...?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No you don't.",
        "response":"No I don't, to hell with her, she left me!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's right.",
        "response":"Never had that dream.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Instead of...?",
        "response":"That's right.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So you wanna tell us now, or are we waiting for four wet bridesmaids?",
        "response":"Oh God... well, it started about a half hour before the wedding. I was in the roomwhere we were keeping all the presents, and I was looking at this gravy boat. This reallygorgeous Lamauge gravy boat. When all of a sudden- Sweet 'n' Lo?- I realized that I was more turned on by this gravy boat than byBarry! And then I got really freaked out, and that's when it hit me: how much Barry lookslike Mr. Potato Head. Y'know, I mean, he always looked familiar, but... Anyway, I just hadto get out of there, and I started wondering 'Why am I doing this, and who am I doing thisfor?'.  So anyway I just didn't know where to go, and I know that you and Ihave kinda drifted apart, but you're the only person I knew who lived here in the city.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God... well, it started about a half hour before the wedding. I was in the roomwhere we were keeping all the presents, and I was looking at this gravy boat. This reallygorgeous Lamauge gravy boat. When all of a sudden- Sweet 'n' Lo?- I realized that I was more turned on by this gravy boat than byBarry! And then I got really freaked out, and that's when it hit me: how much Barry lookslike Mr. Potato Head. Y'know, I mean, he always looked familiar, but... Anyway, I just hadto get out of there, and I started wondering 'Why am I doing this, and who am I doing thisfor?'.  So anyway I just didn't know where to go, and I know that you and Ihave kinda drifted apart, but you're the only person I knew who lived here in the city.",
        "response":"Who wasn't invited to the wedding.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon Daddy, listen to me! All of my life, everyone has always told me, 'You're ashoe! You're a shoe, you're a shoe, you're a shoe!'. And today I just stopped and I said,'What if I don't wanna be a shoe? What if I wanna be a- a purse, y'know? Or a- or a hat!No, I'm not saying I want you to buy me a hat, I'm saying I am a ha- It's a metaphor,Daddy!",
        "response":"You can see where he'd have trouble.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I guess we've established who's staying here with Monica...",
        "response":"Well, maybe that's my decision. Well, maybe I don't need your money. Wait!! Wait,I said maybe!!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look Daddy, it's my life. Well maybe I'll just stay here with Monica.",
        "response":"Well, I guess we've established who's staying here with Monica...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You can see where he'd have trouble.",
        "response":"Look Daddy, it's my life. Well maybe I'll just stay here with Monica.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Raindrops on roses and rabbits and kittens, ..bluebells and sleighbells and- something with mittens... La la la la...",
        "response":"I'm all better now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Who wasn't invited to the wedding.",
        "response":"Ooh, I was kinda hoping that wouldn't be an issue...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, look, this is probably for the best, y'know? Independence. Taking control ofyour life.",
        "response":"And hey, you need anything, you can always come to Joey. Me andChandler live across the hall. And he's away a lot.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And hey, you need anything, you can always come to Joey. Me andChandler live across the hall. And he's away a lot.",
        "response":"Joey, stop hitting on her! It's her wedding day!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey, stop hitting on her! It's her wedding day!",
        "response":"What, like there's a rule or something?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Please, no, go, that'd be fine!",
        "response":"Are, are you okay? I mean, do you want me to stay?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh, this is a Dear Diary moment.",
        "response":"Rach, wait, I can cancel...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rach, wait, I can cancel...",
        "response":"Please, no, go, that'd be fine!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes!",
        "response":"Ooh, this is a Dear Diary moment.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm all better now.",
        "response":"I helped!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I was kinda supposed to be headed for Aruba on my honeymoon, so nothing!",
        "response":"Right, you're not even getting your honeymoon, God.. No, no, although, Aruba, thistime of year... talk about your-  -big lizards... Anyway, if you don't feel likebeing alone tonight, Joey and Chandler are coming over to help me put together my newfurniture.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So Rachel, what're you, uh... what're you up to tonight?",
        "response":"Well, I was kinda supposed to be headed for Aruba on my honeymoon, so nothing!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, go on! It's Paul the Wine Guy!",
        "response":"Hi, come in! Paul, this is.. ...everybody, everybody, this is Paul.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are, are you okay? I mean, do you want me to stay?",
        "response":"That'd be good...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"No, go on! It's Paul the Wine Guy!",
        "is_tmp":false},
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's this?",
        "response":"I have no idea.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That'd be good...",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, I know, I'm such an idiot. I guess I should have caught on when she startedgoing to the dentist four and five times a week. I mean, how clean can teeth get?",
        "response":"My brother's going through that right now, he's such a mess. How did you getthrough it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This was Carol's favourite beer. She alwaysdrank it out of the can, I should have known.",
        "response":"Ross, let me ask you a question. She got the furniture, the stereo, the good TV-what did you get?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God!",
        "response":"I know, I know, I'm such an idiot. I guess I should have caught on when she startedgoing to the dentist four and five times a week. I mean, how clean can teeth get?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"My brother's going through that right now, he's such a mess. How did you getthrough it?",
        "response":"Well, you might try accidentally breaking something valuable of hers, say her-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ross, let me ask you a question. She got the furniture, the stereo, the good TV-what did you get?",
        "response":"You guys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I have no idea.",
        "response":"Done with the bookcase!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I have no idea.",
        "response":"Done with the bookcase!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Done with the bookcase!",
        "response":"All finished!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know what the scariest part is? What if there's only one woman for everybody,y'know? I mean what if you get one woman- and that's it? Unfortunately in my case, therewas only one woman- for her...",
        "response":"What are you talking about? 'One woman'? That's like saying there's only one flavourof ice cream for you. Lemme tell you something, Ross. There's lots of flavours out there.There's Rocky Road, and Cookie Dough, and Bing! Cherry Vanilla. You could get 'em withJimmies, or nuts, or whipped cream! This is the best thing that ever happened to you! Yougot married, you were, like, what, eight? Welcome back to the world! Grab a spoon!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What are you talking about? 'One woman'? That's like saying there's only one flavourof ice cream for you. Lemme tell you something, Ross. There's lots of flavours out there.There's Rocky Road, and Cookie Dough, and Bing! Cherry Vanilla. You could get 'em withJimmies, or nuts, or whipped cream! This is the best thing that ever happened to you! Yougot married, you were, like, what, eight? Welcome back to the world! Grab a spoon!",
        "response":"I honestly don't know if I'm hungry or horny.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"My brother's going through that right now, he's such a mess. How did you getthrough it?",
        "response":"Well, you might try accidentally breaking something valuable of hers, say her-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ever since she walked out on me, I, uh...",
        "response":"What?..... What, you wanna spell it out with noodles?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you might try accidentally breaking something valuable of hers, say her-",
        "response":"-leg?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you might try accidentally breaking something valuable of hers, say her-",
        "response":"-leg?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's one way! Me, I- I went for the watch.",
        "response":"You actually broke her watch?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"-leg?",
        "response":"That's one way! Me, I- I went for the watch.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"-leg?",
        "response":"That's one way! Me, I- I went for the watch.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah... yeah, I think there is. -What were you gonna say?",
        "response":"Well, ever-ev-... ever since she left me, um, I haven't been able to, uh, perform. ...Sexually.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?..... What, you wanna spell it out with noodles?",
        "response":"No, it's, it's more of a fifth date kinda revelation.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?..... What, you wanna spell it out with noodles?",
        "response":"No, it's, it's more of a fifth date kinda revelation.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, it's, it's more of a fifth date kinda revelation.",
        "response":"Oh, so there is gonna be a fifth date?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, it's, it's more of a fifth date kinda revelation.",
        "response":"Oh, so there is gonna be a fifth date?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Isn't there?",
        "response":"Yeah... yeah, I think there is. -What were you gonna say?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Isn't there?",
        "response":"Yeah... yeah, I think there is. -What were you gonna say?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, so there is gonna be a fifth date?",
        "response":"Isn't there?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, so there is gonna be a fifth date?",
        "response":"Isn't there?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah... yeah, I think there is. -What were you gonna say?",
        "response":"Well, ever-ev-... ever since she left me, um, I haven't been able to, uh, perform. ...Sexually.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, ever-ev-... ever since she left me, um, I haven't been able to, uh, perform. ...Sexually.",
        "response":"Oh God, oh God, I am sorry... I am so sorry...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, ever-ev-... ever since she left me, um, I haven't been able to, uh, perform. ...Sexually.",
        "response":"Oh God, oh God, I am sorry... I am so sorry...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Being spit on is probably not what you need right now. Um... how long?",
        "response":"Two years.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Being spit on is probably not what you need right now. Um... how long?",
        "response":"Two years.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's okay...",
        "response":"Being spit on is probably not what you need right now. Um... how long?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's okay...",
        "response":"Being spit on is probably not what you need right now. Um... how long?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God, oh God, I am sorry... I am so sorry...",
        "response":"It's okay...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God, oh God, I am sorry... I am so sorry...",
        "response":"It's okay...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow! I'm glad you smashed her watch!",
        "response":"So you still think you, um... might want that fifth date?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow! I'm glad you smashed her watch!",
        "response":"So you still think you, um... might want that fifth date?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So you still think you, um... might want that fifth date?",
        "response":"...Yeah. Yeah, I do.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I had a really great time last night.",
        "response":"Thank you. Thank you so much.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Two years.",
        "response":"Wow! I'm glad you smashed her watch!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Two years.",
        "response":"Wow! I'm glad you smashed her watch!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thank you. Thank you so much.",
        "response":"We'll talk later.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thank you. Thank you so much.",
        "response":"We'll talk later.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We'll talk later.",
        "response":"Yeah.  Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So how you doing today? Did you sleep okay? Talk to Barry? I can't stop smiling.",
        "response":"I can see that. You look like you slept with a hanger in your mouth.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can see that. You look like you slept with a hanger in your mouth.",
        "response":"I know, he's just so, so... Do you remember you and Tony DeMarco?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can see that. You look like you slept with a hanger in your mouth.",
        "response":"I know, he's just so, so... Do you remember you and Tony DeMarco?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I will not take this abuse.",
        "response":"You're right, I'm sorry.  'Once Iwas a wooden boy, a little wooden boy..'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow! Would I have seen you in anything?",
        "response":"I doubt it. Mostly regional work.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, he's just so, so... Do you remember you and Tony DeMarco?",
        "response":"Oh, yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, he's just so, so... Do you remember you and Tony DeMarco?",
        "response":"Oh, yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I'm an actor.",
        "response":"Wow! Would I have seen you in anything?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"'Look, Gippetto, I'm a real live boy.'",
        "response":"I will not take this abuse.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay. Okay. I am just going to get up, go to work and not think about him all day.Or else I'm just gonna get up and go to work.",
        "response":"Oh, look, wish me luck!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay. Okay. I am just going to get up, go to work and not think about him all day.Or else I'm just gonna get up and go to work.",
        "response":"Oh, look, wish me luck!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh wow. Are you in trouble.",
        "response":"Okay. Okay. I am just going to get up, go to work and not think about him all day.Or else I'm just gonna get up and go to work.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh wow. Are you in trouble.",
        "response":"Okay. Okay. I am just going to get up, go to work and not think about him all day.Or else I'm just gonna get up and go to work.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, it's like that. With feelings.",
        "response":"Oh wow. Are you in trouble.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, it's like that. With feelings.",
        "response":"Oh wow. Are you in trouble.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah.",
        "response":"Well, it's like that. With feelings.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah.",
        "response":"Well, it's like that. With feelings.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, look, wish me luck!",
        "response":"What for?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, welcome back! How was Florida?",
        "response":"You had sex, didn't you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, welcome back! How was Florida?",
        "response":"You had sex, didn't you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What for?",
        "response":"I'm gonna go get one of those job things.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, Monica!",
        "response":"Hey, welcome back! How was Florida?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You had sex, didn't you?",
        "response":"How do you do that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You had sex, didn't you?",
        "response":"How do you do that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, look, wish me luck!",
        "response":"What for?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How do you do that?",
        "response":"So? Who?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How do you do that?",
        "response":"So? Who?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I assume we're looking for an answer more sophisticated than 'to get you into bed'.",
        "response":"Is it me? Is it like I have some sort of beacon that only dogs and men with severeemotional problems can hear?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You mean you know Paul like I know Paul?",
        "response":"Are you kidding? I take credit for Paul. Y'know before me, there was no snap inhis turtle for two years.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why?! Why? Why, why would anybody do something like that?",
        "response":"I assume we're looking for an answer more sophisticated than 'to get you into bed'.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Paul the Wine Guy? Oh yeah, I know Paul.",
        "response":"You mean you know Paul like I know Paul?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Paul the Wine Guy? Oh yeah, I know Paul.",
        "response":"You mean you know Paul like I know Paul?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know Paul?",
        "response":"Paul the Wine Guy? Oh yeah, I know Paul.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know Paul?",
        "response":"Paul the Wine Guy? Oh yeah, I know Paul.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So? Who?",
        "response":"You know Paul?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So? Who?",
        "response":"You know Paul?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Is it me? Is it like I have some sort of beacon that only dogs and men with severeemotional problems can hear?",
        "response":"All right, c'mere, gimme your feet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And yet you're surprisingly upbeat.",
        "response":"You would be too if you found John and David boots on sale, fifty percent off!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And yet you're surprisingly upbeat.",
        "response":"You would be too if you found John and David boots on sale, fifty percent off!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you kidding? I'm trained for nothing! I was laughed out of twelve interviewstoday.",
        "response":"And yet you're surprisingly upbeat.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You would be too if you found John and David boots on sale, fifty percent off!",
        "response":"Oh, how well you know me...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You would be too if you found John and David boots on sale, fifty percent off!",
        "response":"Oh, how well you know me...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You got a job?",
        "response":"Are you kidding? I'm trained for nothing! I was laughed out of twelve interviewstoday.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right, c'mere, gimme your feet.",
        "response":"I just thought he was nice, y'know?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Guess what?",
        "response":"You got a job?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, how well you know me...",
        "response":"They're my new 'I don't need a job, I don't need my parents, I've got great boots'boots!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"They're my new 'I don't need a job, I don't need my parents, I've got great boots'boots!",
        "response":"How'd you pay for them?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um... my... father.",
        "response":"C'mon, you can't live off your parents your whole life.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How'd you pay for them?",
        "response":"Uh, credit card.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How'd you pay for them?",
        "response":"Uh, credit card.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And who pays for that?",
        "response":"Um... my... father.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And who pays for that?",
        "response":"Um... my... father.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, credit card.",
        "response":"And who pays for that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, credit card.",
        "response":"And who pays for that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thank you.",
        "response":"You're welcome. I remember when I first came to this city. I was fourteen. My momhad just killed herself and my step-dad was back in prison, and I got here, and I didn'tknow anybody. And I ended up living with this albino guy who was, like, cleaning windowsoutside port authority, and then he killed himself, and then I found aromatherapy. Sobelieve me, I know exactly how you feel.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know that. That's why I was getting married.",
        "response":"Give her a break, it's hard being on your own for the first time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon, you can't live off your parents your whole life.",
        "response":"I know that. That's why I was getting married.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um... my... father.",
        "response":"C'mon, you can't live off your parents your whole life.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Give her a break, it's hard being on your own for the first time.",
        "response":"Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Give her a break, it's hard being on your own for the first time.",
        "response":"Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. No, I gotta go home sometime.",
        "response":"You be okay?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You be okay?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mmm.  Oh, no-",
        "response":"Sorry-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.",
        "response":"Okay.  You know you probably didn't know this, but back in highschool, I had a, um, major crush on you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, you have it, really, I don't want it-",
        "response":"Split it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, you have it, really, I don't want it-",
        "response":"Split it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No no no, go-",
        "response":"No, you have it, really, I don't want it-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No no no, go-",
        "response":"No, you have it, really, I don't want it-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Split it?",
        "response":"Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Split it?",
        "response":"Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sorry-",
        "response":"No no no, go-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sorry-",
        "response":"No no no, go-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I did.",
        "response":"Oh. Listen, do you think- and try not to let my intense vulnerability become anykind of a factor here- but do you think it would be okay if I asked you out? Sometime?Maybe?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I did.",
        "response":"Oh. Listen, do you think- and try not to let my intense vulnerability become anykind of a factor here- but do you think it would be okay if I asked you out? Sometime?Maybe?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.  You know you probably didn't know this, but back in highschool, I had a, um, major crush on you.",
        "response":"I knew.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.  You know you probably didn't know this, but back in highschool, I had a, um, major crush on you.",
        "response":"I knew.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.",
        "response":"Okay.  You know you probably didn't know this, but back in highschool, I had a, um, major crush on you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I knew.",
        "response":"You did! Oh.... I always figured you just thought I was Monica's geeky olderbrother.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I knew.",
        "response":"You did! Oh.... I always figured you just thought I was Monica's geeky olderbrother.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You did! Oh.... I always figured you just thought I was Monica's geeky olderbrother.",
        "response":"I did.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You did! Oh.... I always figured you just thought I was Monica's geeky olderbrother.",
        "response":"I did.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh. Listen, do you think- and try not to let my intense vulnerability become anykind of a factor here- but do you think it would be okay if I asked you out? Sometime?Maybe?",
        "response":"Yeah, maybe...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh. Listen, do you think- and try not to let my intense vulnerability become anykind of a factor here- but do you think it would be okay if I asked you out? Sometime?Maybe?",
        "response":"Yeah, maybe...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"See ya.... Waitwait, what's with you?",
        "response":"I just grabbed a spoon.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Goodnight.",
        "response":"See ya.... Waitwait, what's with you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay... okay, maybe I will...",
        "response":"Goodnight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay... okay, maybe I will...",
        "response":"Goodnight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, maybe...",
        "response":"Okay... okay, maybe I will...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, maybe...",
        "response":"Okay... okay, maybe I will...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Goodnight.",
        "response":"Goodnight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I think for us, kissing is pretty much like an opening act, y'know? I meanit's like the stand-up comedian you have to sit through before Pink Floyd comes out.",
        "response":"Yeah, and-and it's not that we don't like the comedian, it's that-that... that's notwhy we bought the ticket.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't believe what I'm hearing here...",
        "response":"What? I-I said you had a-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Would anybody like more coffee?",
        "response":"Did you make it, or are you just serving it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did you make it, or are you just serving it?",
        "response":"I'm just serving it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? I-I said you had a-",
        "response":"What I said...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? I-I said you had a-",
        "response":"What I said...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Would you stop?",
        "response":"Oh, was I doing it again?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What I said...",
        "response":"Would you stop?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What I said...",
        "response":"Would you stop?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, and-and it's not that we don't like the comedian, it's that-that... that's notwhy we bought the ticket.",
        "response":"The problem is, though, after the concert's over, no matter how great the showwas, you girls are always looking for the comedian again, y'know? I mean, we're in thecar, we're fighting traffic... basically just trying to stay awake.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He's out banging other women over the head with a club, while she sits at hometrying to get the mastodon smell out of the carpet!",
        "response":"Marsha, these are cave people. Okay? They have issues like 'Gee, that glacier'sgetting kinda close.' See?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He's out banging other women over the head with a club, while she sits at hometrying to get the mastodon smell out of the carpet!",
        "response":"Marsha, these are cave people. Okay? They have issues like 'Gee, that glacier'sgetting kinda close.' See?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Marsha, these are cave people. Okay? They have issues like 'Gee, that glacier'sgetting kinda close.' See?",
        "response":"Speaking of issues, isn't that your ex-wife?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Does she.",
        "response":"He's out banging other women over the head with a club, while she sits at hometrying to get the mastodon smell out of the carpet!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Does she.",
        "response":"He's out banging other women over the head with a club, while she sits at hometrying to get the mastodon smell out of the carpet!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, it's good, it is good, it's just that- mm- doesn't she seem a little angry?",
        "response":"Well, she has issues.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, she has issues.",
        "response":"Does she.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, she has issues.",
        "response":"Does she.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Marsha, these are cave people. Okay? They have issues like 'Gee, that glacier'sgetting kinda close.' See?",
        "response":"Speaking of issues, isn't that your ex-wife?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, it is. Carol! Hi!",
        "response":"Okay, okay, yes, it is.  How about I'll, uh, catch up with you in the IceAge.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So.",
        "response":"You look great. I, uh... I hate that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So.",
        "response":"You look great. I, uh... I hate that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Speaking of issues, isn't that your ex-wife?",
        "response":"No. No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Speaking of issues, isn't that your ex-wife?",
        "response":"No. No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"So.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. No.",
        "response":"Yes, it is. Carol! Hi!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. No.",
        "response":"Yes, it is. Carol! Hi!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sorry. You look good too.",
        "response":"Ah, well, in here, anyone who... stands erect... So what's new? Still, uh...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sorry. You look good too.",
        "response":"Ah, well, in here, anyone who... stands erect... So what's new? Still, uh...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well... you never know. How's, um.. how's the family?",
        "response":"Marty's still totally paranoid. Oh, and, uh-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ah, well, in here, anyone who... stands erect... So what's new? Still, uh...",
        "response":"A lesbian?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ah, well, in here, anyone who... stands erect... So what's new? Still, uh...",
        "response":"A lesbian?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You look great. I, uh... I hate that.",
        "response":"Sorry. You look good too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You look great. I, uh... I hate that.",
        "response":"Sorry. You look good too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"A lesbian?",
        "response":"Well... you never know. How's, um.. how's the family?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"A lesbian?",
        "response":"Well... you never know. How's, um.. how's the family?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's because as far as my parents are concerned, Ross can do no wrong. Y'see,he's the Prince. Apparently they had some big ceremony before I was born.",
        "response":"Ew, ew, ew, ew ew ew ew ew!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well... you never know. How's, um.. how's the family?",
        "response":"Marty's still totally paranoid. Oh, and, uh-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, sorry, the swallowing slowed me down.",
        "response":"Whose little ball of paper is this?!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Marty's still totally paranoid. Oh, and, uh-",
        "response":"Why- why are you here, Carol?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Marty's still totally paranoid. Oh, and, uh-",
        "response":"Why- why are you here, Carol?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you through with that?",
        "response":"Yeah, sorry, the swallowing slowed me down.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why- why are you here, Carol?",
        "response":"I'm pregnant.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why- why are you here, Carol?",
        "response":"I'm pregnant.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm pregnant.",
        "response":"Pregnant?!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, look, don't touch that!",
        "response":"Oh, like I wasn't dreading tomorrow enough, having to give it back to him... 'HiBarry! Remember me? I'm the girl in the veil who stomped on your heart in front of yourentire family!' Oh God and now I'm gonna have to return the ring, without the ring, whichmakes it so much harder...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Has anybody seen my engagement ring?",
        "response":"Yeah, it's beautiful.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Ugly Naked Guy got a Thighmaster!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God, oh God, oh God oh God oh God oh God....",
        "response":"No, look, don't touch that!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God, oh God, oh God oh God oh God oh God....",
        "response":"No, look, don't touch that!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, it's beautiful.",
        "response":"Oh God, oh God, oh God oh God oh God oh God....",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, it's beautiful.",
        "response":"Oh God, oh God, oh God oh God oh God oh God....",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ew, ew, ew, ew ew ew ew ew!",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ew, ew, ew, ew ew ew ew ew!",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You don't get a lot of 'doy' these days...",
        "response":"I know I had it this morning, and I know I had it when I was in the kitchenwith...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know I had it this morning, and I know I had it when I was in the kitchenwith...",
        "response":"...Dinah?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know I had it this morning, and I know I had it when I was in the kitchenwith...",
        "response":"...Dinah?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I am sorry...",
        "response":"I gave you one job!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I am sorry...",
        "response":"I gave you one job!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohhhhh, don't be mad...",
        "response":"You didn't.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You didn't.",
        "response":"Oh, I am sorry...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You didn't.",
        "response":"Oh, I am sorry...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Dinah?",
        "response":"Ohhhhh, don't be mad...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry, why is this girl going to call me?",
        "response":"MRS. GELLER: Oh, she just graduated, and she wants to be something in cooking, or food,or.... I don't know. Anyway, I told her you had a restaurant-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GELLER: Oh, she just graduated, and she wants to be something in cooking, or food,or.... I don't know. Anyway, I told her you had a restaurant-",
        "response":"No Mom, I don't have a restaurant, I work in a restaurant.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So what are you gonna do?",
        "response":"I have no idea. No matter what I do, though, I'm still gonna be a father.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Now, Monica, you know that's not how you look for an engagement ring in alasagne...",
        "response":"I just... can't do it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Anyway, they want me to go down to this- sonogram thing with them tomorrow.",
        "response":"So what are you gonna do?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I gave you one job!",
        "response":"Oh, but look how straight those noodles are!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I just... can't do it.",
        "response":"Boys? We're going in.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow. That is not a happy hi.",
        "response":"Carol's pregnant.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":".....Hi.",
        "response":"Wow. That is not a happy hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, y'know, these people are pros. They know what they're doing, they take theirtime, they get the job done.",
        "response":"Boy, I know they say you can't change your parents,... boy, if you could-  -I'd want yours.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GELLER: Well, they don't have to know that...",
        "response":"Ross, could you come and help me with the spaghetti, please?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. We don't speak. She's like this high-powered, driven career type.",
        "response":"What does she do?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Boy, I know they say you can't change your parents,... boy, if you could-  -I'd want yours.",
        "response":"Must pee.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're twins?",
        "response":"Yeah. We don't speak. She's like this high-powered, driven career type.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No Mom, I don't have a restaurant, I work in a restaurant.",
        "response":"MRS. GELLER: Well, they don't have to know that...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's that supposed to mean?",
        "response":"MRS. GELLER: Nothing! It's an expression.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Y'know, it's even worse when you're twins.",
        "response":"You're twins?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GELLER: Nothing! It's an expression.",
        "response":"No it's not.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh.. okay, sure! Thanks!",
        "response":"Anyway.. um..  So, you- uh- you nervous about Barry tomorrow?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"D'ya.. uh.. d'ya need any help?",
        "response":"Uh.. okay, sure! Thanks!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"D'ya.. uh.. d'ya need any help?",
        "response":"Uh.. okay, sure! Thanks!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm just cleaning up.",
        "response":"D'ya.. uh.. d'ya need any help?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm just cleaning up.",
        "response":"D'ya.. uh.. d'ya need any help?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...How long was I in there?",
        "response":"I'm just cleaning up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...How long was I in there?",
        "response":"I'm just cleaning up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What does she do?",
        "response":"She's a waitress.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The lights, please..",
        "response":"...How long was I in there?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh.. okay, sure! Thanks!",
        "response":"Anyway.. um..  So, you- uh- you nervous about Barry tomorrow?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Anyway.. um..  So, you- uh- you nervous about Barry tomorrow?",
        "response":"Oh.. a little..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Anyway.. um..  So, you- uh- you nervous about Barry tomorrow?",
        "response":"Oh.. a little..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh.. a little..",
        "response":"Mm-hmm..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh.. a little..",
        "response":"Mm-hmm..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mm-hmm..",
        "response":"A lot.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mm-hmm..",
        "response":"A lot.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"A lot.",
        "response":"Mm.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"A lot.",
        "response":"Mm.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, got any advice? Y'know, as someone who's recently been- dumped?",
        "response":"Well, you may wanna steer clear of the word 'dumped'. Chances are he's gonna bethis, this broken shell of a man, y'know, so you should try not to look too terrific, Iknow it'll be hard. Or, y'know, uh, hey!, I'll go down there, and I'll give Barry back hisring, and you can go with Carol and Susan to the OB/GYN...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, got any advice? Y'know, as someone who's recently been- dumped?",
        "response":"Well, you may wanna steer clear of the word 'dumped'. Chances are he's gonna bethis, this broken shell of a man, y'know, so you should try not to look too terrific, Iknow it'll be hard. Or, y'know, uh, hey!, I'll go down there, and I'll give Barry back hisring, and you can go with Carol and Susan to the OB/GYN...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you may wanna steer clear of the word 'dumped'. Chances are he's gonna bethis, this broken shell of a man, y'know, so you should try not to look too terrific, Iknow it'll be hard. Or, y'know, uh, hey!, I'll go down there, and I'll give Barry back hisring, and you can go with Carol and Susan to the OB/GYN...",
        "response":"Oh, you've got Carol tomorrow.. When did it get so complicated?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you may wanna steer clear of the word 'dumped'. Chances are he's gonna bethis, this broken shell of a man, y'know, so you should try not to look too terrific, Iknow it'll be hard. Or, y'know, uh, hey!, I'll go down there, and I'll give Barry back hisring, and you can go with Carol and Susan to the OB/GYN...",
        "response":"Oh, you've got Carol tomorrow.. When did it get so complicated?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, you've got Carol tomorrow.. When did it get so complicated?",
        "response":"Got me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, you've got Carol tomorrow.. When did it get so complicated?",
        "response":"Got me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mm.",
        "response":"So, got any advice? Y'know, as someone who's recently been- dumped?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mm.",
        "response":"So, got any advice? Y'know, as someone who's recently been- dumped?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Got me.",
        "response":"Remember when we were in high school together?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"I mean, didn't you think you were just gonna meet somone, fall in love- and that'dbe it?  ..Ross?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"I mean, didn't you think you were just gonna meet somone, fall in love- and that'dbe it?  ..Ross?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I mean, didn't you think you were just gonna meet somone, fall in love- and that'dbe it?  ..Ross?",
        "response":"Yes, yes!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I mean, didn't you think you were just gonna meet somone, fall in love- and that'dbe it?  ..Ross?",
        "response":"Yes, yes!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Got me.",
        "response":"Remember when we were in high school together?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Remember when we were in high school together?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Remember when we were in high school together?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, yes!",
        "response":"Oh! Man, I never thought I'd be here..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, yes!",
        "response":"Oh! Man, I never thought I'd be here..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"-she, of course, she- uh- familiar with our.. special situation?",
        "response":"Yes, and she's very supportive.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello, Susan.  Good shake. Good shake. So, uh, we'rejust waiting for...?",
        "response":"Dr. Oberman.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ross.",
        "response":"Hello, Susan.  Good shake. Good shake. So, uh, we'rejust waiting for...?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"She.",
        "response":"-she, of course, she- uh- familiar with our.. special situation?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, and she's very supportive.",
        "response":"Okay, that's great.  No, I'm- Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh! Man, I never thought I'd be here..",
        "response":"Me either...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Dr. Oberman.",
        "response":"..Dr. Oberman. Okay. And is he-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"..Dr. Oberman. Okay. And is he-",
        "response":"She.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How could I forget?",
        "response":"Ross.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, and she's very supportive.",
        "response":"Okay, that's great.  No, I'm- Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, that's great.  No, I'm- Oh.",
        "response":"Thanks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, that's great.  No, I'm- Oh.",
        "response":"Thanks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Quack, quack..",
        "response":"Ross? That opens my cervix.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon in.",
        "response":"Are you sure?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon in.",
        "response":"Are you sure?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thanks.",
        "response":"Quack, quack..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thanks.",
        "response":"Quack, quack..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Barry?",
        "response":"C'mon in.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, um- so how's this, uh, how's this gonna work? Y'know, with us? Y'know, when,like, important decisions have to be made?",
        "response":"Give me a 'for instance'.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Give me a 'for instance'.",
        "response":"Well, uh, uh, I don't know, okay, okay, how about with the, uh, with the baby'sname?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Give me a 'for instance'.",
        "response":"Well, uh, uh, I don't know, okay, okay, how about with the, uh, with the baby'sname?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, uh, uh, I don't know, okay, okay, how about with the, uh, with the baby'sname?",
        "response":"Marlon-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you sure?",
        "response":"Yeah! It's fine, it's fine. Robbie's gonna be here for hours.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, how ya doin?",
        "response":"I'm- uh- I'm okay... You look great!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah! It's fine, it's fine. Robbie's gonna be here for hours.",
        "response":"Huh?!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm- uh- I'm okay... You look great!",
        "response":"Yeah, well..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh?!",
        "response":"So, how ya doin?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, uh, uh, I don't know, okay, okay, how about with the, uh, with the baby'sname?",
        "response":"Marlon-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Marlon?!",
        "response":"-if it's a boy, Minnie if it's a girl.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Marlon?!",
        "response":"-if it's a boy, Minnie if it's a girl.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"-if it's a boy, Minnie if it's a girl.",
        "response":"...As in Mouse?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"-if it's a boy, Minnie if it's a girl.",
        "response":"...As in Mouse?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...As in Mouse?",
        "response":"As in my grandmother.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...As in Mouse?",
        "response":"As in my grandmother.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Marlon-",
        "response":"Marlon?!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Marlon-",
        "response":"Marlon?!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"As in my grandmother.",
        "response":"Still, you- you say Minnie, you hear Mouse. Um, how about, um.. how about Julia?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"As in my grandmother.",
        "response":"Still, you- you say Minnie, you hear Mouse. Um, how about, um.. how about Julia?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sorry about that. So. What have you been up to?",
        "response":"Oh, not much. I-I got a job.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Still, you- you say Minnie, you hear Mouse. Um, how about, um.. how about Julia?",
        "response":"Julia..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why are- why are you so tanned?",
        "response":"Oh, I, uh- I went to Aruba.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, not much. I-I got a job.",
        "response":"Oh, that's great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, not much. I-I got a job.",
        "response":"Oh, that's great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that's great.",
        "response":"Why are- why are you so tanned?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that's great.",
        "response":"Why are- why are you so tanned?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh no. You went on our honeymoon alone?",
        "response":"No. I went with, uh.. Now, this may hurt.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mindy?! My maid of honour, Mindy?!",
        "response":"Yeah, well, uh, we're kind of a thing now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mindy?! My maid of honour, Mindy?!",
        "response":"Yeah, well, uh, we're kind of a thing now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I, uh- I went to Aruba.",
        "response":"Oh no. You went on our honeymoon alone?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I, uh- I went to Aruba.",
        "response":"Oh no. You went on our honeymoon alone?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why are- why are you so tanned?",
        "response":"Oh, I, uh- I went to Aruba.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No!  I went with Mindy.",
        "response":"Mindy?! My maid of honour, Mindy?!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. I went with, uh.. Now, this may hurt.",
        "response":"Me?!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Me?!",
        "response":"No!  I went with Mindy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And you've got lenses! But you hate sticking your finger in your eye!",
        "response":"Not for her. Listen, I really wanted to thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And you've got lenses! But you hate sticking your finger in your eye!",
        "response":"Not for her. Listen, I really wanted to thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Careful! They haven't quite taken yet.",
        "response":"And you've got lenses! But you hate sticking your finger in your eye!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Careful! They haven't quite taken yet.",
        "response":"And you've got lenses! But you hate sticking your finger in your eye!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, well, uh, we're kind of a thing now.",
        "response":"Oh! Well, um..  You've got plugs!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, well, uh, we're kind of a thing now.",
        "response":"Oh! Well, um..  You've got plugs!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh! Well, um..  You've got plugs!",
        "response":"Careful! They haven't quite taken yet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh! Well, um..  You've got plugs!",
        "response":"Careful! They haven't quite taken yet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Not for her. Listen, I really wanted to thank you.",
        "response":"Okay..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay..",
        "response":"See, about a month ago, I wanted to hurt you. More than I've ever wanted to hurtanyone in my life. And I'm an orthodontist.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay..",
        "response":"See, about a month ago, I wanted to hurt you. More than I've ever wanted to hurtanyone in my life. And I'm an orthodontist.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"See, about a month ago, I wanted to hurt you. More than I've ever wanted to hurtanyone in my life. And I'm an orthodontist.",
        "response":"Wow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"See, about a month ago, I wanted to hurt you. More than I've ever wanted to hurtanyone in my life. And I'm an orthodontist.",
        "response":"Wow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know, you were right? I mean, I thought we were happy. We weren't happy. Butwith Mindy, now I'm happy. Spit.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow.",
        "response":"You know, you were right? I mean, I thought we were happy. We weren't happy. Butwith Mindy, now I'm happy. Spit.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow.",
        "response":"You know, you were right? I mean, I thought we were happy. We weren't happy. Butwith Mindy, now I'm happy. Spit.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Not for her. Listen, I really wanted to thank you.",
        "response":"Okay..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What, it's gonna be Helen Willick?",
        "response":"No, actually, um, we talked about Helen Willick-Bunch.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Helen Geller? I don't think so.",
        "response":"Hello? It's not gonna be Helen Geller.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Me.",
        "response":"Anyway, um,  I guess this belongs to you. Andthank you for giving it to me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I mean it's not Geller.",
        "response":"What, it's gonna be Helen Willick?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I mean it's not Geller.",
        "response":"What, it's gonna be Helen Willick?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello? It's not gonna be Helen Geller.",
        "response":"Thank you!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello? It's not gonna be Helen Geller.",
        "response":"Thank you!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thank you!",
        "response":"No, I mean it's not Geller.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thank you!",
        "response":"No, I mean it's not Geller.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No no no, she gets a credit, hey, I'm in there too.",
        "response":"Ross. You're not actually suggesting Helen Willick-Bunch-Geller? 'Cause I thinkthat borders on child abuse.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No no no, she gets a credit, hey, I'm in there too.",
        "response":"Ross. You're not actually suggesting Helen Willick-Bunch-Geller? 'Cause I thinkthat borders on child abuse.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, 's'funny, really? Um, I don't remember you making any sperm.",
        "response":"Yeah, and we all know what a challenge that is!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, actually, um, we talked about Helen Willick-Bunch.",
        "response":"Well, wait a minute, wha- why is she in the title?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's my baby too.",
        "response":"Oh, 's'funny, really? Um, I don't remember you making any sperm.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's my baby too.",
        "response":"Oh, 's'funny, really? Um, I don't remember you making any sperm.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What, it's gonna be Helen Willick?",
        "response":"No, actually, um, we talked about Helen Willick-Bunch.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right, you two, stop it!",
        "response":"No no no, she gets a credit, hey, I'm in there too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, wait a minute, wha- why is she in the title?",
        "response":"It's my baby too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, no, nonononono, you see what he's doing? He knows no-one's gonna say all thosenames, so they'll wind up calling her Geller, then he gets his way!",
        "response":"My way?! You-you think this is my way? Believe me, of all the ways I ever imaginedthis moment in my life being, this is not my way- y'know what? Uh, um, this is too hard.I'm not, I can't do-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Of course not, I'm... suggesting Geller-Willick-Bunch.",
        "response":"Oh, no, nonononono, you see what he's doing? He knows no-one's gonna say all thosenames, so they'll wind up calling her Geller, then he gets his way!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ross. You're not actually suggesting Helen Willick-Bunch-Geller? 'Cause I thinkthat borders on child abuse.",
        "response":"Of course not, I'm... suggesting Geller-Willick-Bunch.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know, if you tilt your head to the left, and relax your eyes, it kinda lookslike an old potato.",
        "response":"Then don't do that, alright?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Monica. Whaddya think?",
        "response":"Mm-hmm.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay!",
        "response":"Monica. Whaddya think?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Then don't do that, alright?",
        "response":"Okay!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Then don't do that, alright?",
        "response":"Okay!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mm-hmm.",
        "response":"Wh- are you welling up?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mm-hmm.",
        "response":"Wh- are you welling up?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You are, you're welling up.",
        "response":"Am not!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You are, you're welling up.",
        "response":"Am not!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Am not!",
        "response":"You're gonna be an aunt.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Am not!",
        "response":"You're gonna be an aunt.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"You are, you're welling up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"You are, you're welling up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wh- are you welling up?",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wh- are you welling up?",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"&quot;So how does it feel knowing you're about to die?&quot;",
        "response":"&quot;Warden, in five minutes my pain will be over. But you'll have to live with theknowledge that you sent an honest man to die.&quot;",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, Ross.",
        "response":"What? Wh- hello? The Millners' farm in Connecticut? The Millners, they had thisunbelievable farm, they had horses, and, and rabbits that he could chase and it was- it w-.....Oh my God, Chi Chi!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"&quot;Warden, in five minutes my pain will be over. But you'll have to live with theknowledge that you sent an honest man to die.&quot;",
        "response":"Hey, that was really good!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"&quot;Warden, in five minutes my pain will be over. But you'll have to live with theknowledge that you sent an honest man to die.&quot;",
        "response":"Hey, that was really good!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? He said 'we should do it again', that's good, right?",
        "response":"Uh, no. Loosely translated 'We should do this again' means 'You will never see menaked'.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's funny, that, no, because, uh, our parents actually did, uh, send our dog offto live on a farm.",
        "response":"Uh, Ross.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, no. Loosely translated 'We should do this again' means 'You will never see menaked'.",
        "response":"Since when?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, that was really good!",
        "response":"Thanks! Let's keep going.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're gonna be an aunt.",
        "response":"Oh shut up!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay. &quot;So. Whaddya want from me, Damone, huh?&quot;",
        "response":"&quot;I just wanna go back to my cell. 'Cause in my cell, I can smoke.&quot;",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay. &quot;So. Whaddya want from me, Damone, huh?&quot;",
        "response":"&quot;I just wanna go back to my cell. 'Cause in my cell, I can smoke.&quot;",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"&quot;I just wanna go back to my cell. 'Cause in my cell, I can smoke.&quot;",
        "response":"&quot;Smoke away.&quot;",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thanks! Let's keep going.",
        "response":"Okay. &quot;So. Whaddya want from me, Damone, huh?&quot;",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thanks! Let's keep going.",
        "response":"Okay. &quot;So. Whaddya want from me, Damone, huh?&quot;",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I think this is probably why Damone smokes in his cell alone.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, that was really good!",
        "response":"Thanks! Let's keep going.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Relax your hand!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Not so much!",
        "response":"Whoah!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Don't think of it as a cigarette. Think of it as the thing that's been missingfrom your hand. When you're holding it, you feel right. You feel complete.",
        "response":"Y'miss it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No no no, I am not giving you a cigarette.",
        "response":"It's fine, it's fine. Look, do you wanna get this part, or not? Here.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Y'miss it?",
        "response":"Nah, not so much. Alright, now we smoke.  Oh.. my.. God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright.. okay. No. Give it to me.",
        "response":"No no no, I am not giving you a cigarette.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey!",
        "response":"Alright, now try taking a puff.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whoah!",
        "response":"Hey!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whoah!",
        "response":"Hey!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey!",
        "response":"Hey!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey!",
        "response":"Hey!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, don't tell me, don't tell me!  Decafcappucino for Joey.. Coffee black.. Late.. And an iced tea. I'm getting pretty good atthis!",
        "response":"Yeah. Yeah, excellent.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What did they do to you?",
        "response":"It's nothing, it's just- Okay. I'm going through my mail, and I open up theirmonthly, you know, STATEMENT-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's nothing, it's just- Okay. I'm going through my mail, and I open up theirmonthly, you know, STATEMENT-",
        "response":"Easy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, Satan's minions at work again...",
        "response":"Yes, 'cause now I have to go down there, and deal with them.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"- and there's five hundred extra dollars in my account.",
        "response":"Oh, Satan's minions at work again...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, 'cause now I have to go down there, and deal with them.",
        "response":"What are you talking about? Keep it!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah- no- I'm just- it's, I haven't worked- It's my bank.",
        "response":"What did they do to you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Easy.",
        "response":"- and there's five hundred extra dollars in my account.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. Yeah, excellent.",
        "response":"Good for me!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, but if you spent it, it would be like shopping!",
        "response":"Okay. Okay, let's say I bought a really great pair of shoes. Do you know what I'dhear, with every step I took? 'Not-mine. Not-mine. Not-mine.' And even if I was happy,okay, and, and skipping- 'Not-not-mine, not-not-mine, not-not-mine, not-not-mine'...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay. Okay, let's say I bought a really great pair of shoes. Do you know what I'dhear, with every step I took? 'Not-mine. Not-mine. Not-mine.' And even if I was happy,okay, and, and skipping- 'Not-not-mine, not-not-mine, not-not-mine, not-not-mine'...",
        "response":"We're with you. We got it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hold on a second, alright? Just think about what you went through the last time youquit.",
        "response":"Okay, so this time I won't quit!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And this- is my reward!",
        "response":"Hold on a second, alright? Just think about what you went through the last time youquit.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We're with you. We got it.",
        "response":"Okay. I'd- just- I'd never be able to enjoy it. It would be like this giant karmicdebt.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's not mine, I didn't earn it, if I kept it, it would be like stealing.",
        "response":"Yeah, but if you spent it, it would be like shopping!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What are you talking about? Keep it!",
        "response":"It's not mine, I didn't earn it, if I kept it, it would be like stealing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm smoking. I'm smoking, I'm smoking.",
        "response":"Oh, I can't believe you! You've been so good, for three years!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I can't believe you! You've been so good, for three years!",
        "response":"And this- is my reward!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. Not after what happened with Steve.",
        "response":"What are you talking about? We love Schhteve! Schhteve was schhexy!.. Sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"'S'going pretty good, y'know? It's nice, and, we're having fun.",
        "response":"So when do we get to meet the guy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This Alan again? How's it goin'?",
        "response":"'S'going pretty good, y'know? It's nice, and, we're having fun.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright. I'm gonna go change, I've got a date.",
        "response":"This Alan again? How's it goin'?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So when do we get to meet the guy?",
        "response":"Let's see, today's Monday... Never.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, so this time I won't quit!",
        "response":"Ohhh! Put it out!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohhh! Put it out!",
        "response":"All right! I'm putting it out, I'm putting it out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Let's see, today's Monday... Never.",
        "response":"Oh, come on! Come on!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, come on! Come on!",
        "response":"No. Not after what happened with Steve.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I mean, why should I let them meet him? I mean, I bring a guy home, and withinfive minutes they're all over him. I mean, they're like- coyotes, picking off the weakmembers of the herd.",
        "response":"Listen. As someone who's seen more than her fair share of bad beef, I'll tell you:that is not such a terrible thing. I mean, they're your friends, they're just looking outafter you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Listen. As someone who's seen more than her fair share of bad beef, I'll tell you:that is not such a terrible thing. I mean, they're your friends, they're just looking outafter you.",
        "response":"I know. I just wish that once, I'd bring a guy home that they actually liked.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Listen. As someone who's seen more than her fair share of bad beef, I'll tell you:that is not such a terrible thing. I mean, they're your friends, they're just looking outafter you.",
        "response":"I know. I just wish that once, I'd bring a guy home that they actually liked.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<b>SCENE 3: IRIDIUM</b>",
        "response":"I mean, why should I let them meet him? I mean, I bring a guy home, and withinfive minutes they're all over him. I mean, they're like- coyotes, picking off the weakmembers of the herd.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What are you talking about? We love Schhteve! Schhteve was schhexy!.. Sorry.",
        "response":"Look, I don't even know how I feel about him yet. Just give me a chance to figurethat out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know. I just wish that once, I'd bring a guy home that they actually liked.",
        "response":"Well, you do realise the odds of that happening are a little slimmer if they neverget to meet the guy..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, I don't even know how I feel about him yet. Just give me a chance to figurethat out.",
        "response":"Well, then can we meet him?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, then can we meet him?",
        "response":"Nope. Schhorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nope. Schhorry.",
        "response":"<b>SCENE 3: IRIDIUM</b>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...What shoe?",
        "response":"From the nursery rhyme. 'There was a crooked man, Who had a crooked smile, Wholived in a shoe, For a... while...'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...What shoe?",
        "response":"From the nursery rhyme. 'There was a crooked man, Who had a crooked smile, Wholived in a shoe, For a... while...'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Loved him! Yeah! He's great!",
        "response":"Wait a minute! We're talking about someone that <i>I'm</i> going out with?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wait a minute! We're talking about someone that <i>I'm</i> going out with?",
        "response":"Yeah!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah! We promise! We'll be good!",
        "response":"Chandler? Do you promise to be good?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi, Alan.",
        "response":"I've heard schho much about all you guyschh!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Do you all promise?",
        "response":"Yeah! We promise! We'll be good!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, yes! Like the man in the shoe!",
        "response":"...What shoe?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Hi, Alan.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"From the nursery rhyme. 'There was a crooked man, Who had a crooked smile, Wholived in a shoe, For a... while...'",
        "response":"...So I think Alan will become the yardstick against which all future boyfriendswill be measured.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Can I ask you guys a question? D'you ever think that Alan is maybe.. sometimes..",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know what I like most about him, though?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, Weird Girl.",
        "response":"I brought you alphabet soup.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The way he makes me feel about myself.",
        "response":"Yeah...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"The way he makes me feel about myself.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"The way he makes me feel about myself.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"..I dunno, a little too Alan?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, Lizzie.",
        "response":"Hey, Weird Girl.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did you pick out the vowels?",
        "response":"Yes. But I left in the Ys. 'Cause, y'know, &quot;sometimes y&quot;. Uh, I alsohave something else for you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did you pick out the vowels?",
        "response":"Yes. But I left in the Ys. 'Cause, y'know, &quot;sometimes y&quot;. Uh, I alsohave something else for you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes. But I left in the Ys. 'Cause, y'know, &quot;sometimes y&quot;. Uh, I alsohave something else for you.",
        "response":"Saltines?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes. But I left in the Ys. 'Cause, y'know, &quot;sometimes y&quot;. Uh, I alsohave something else for you.",
        "response":"Saltines?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Saltines?",
        "response":"No, but would you like a thousand dollars and a football phone?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Saltines?",
        "response":"No, but would you like a thousand dollars and a football phone?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I brought you alphabet soup.",
        "response":"Did you pick out the vowels?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I brought you alphabet soup.",
        "response":"Did you pick out the vowels?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, Weird Girl.",
        "response":"I brought you alphabet soup.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, but would you like a thousand dollars and a football phone?",
        "response":"What?  Oh my God, there's really money inhere.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, but would you like a thousand dollars and a football phone?",
        "response":"What?  Oh my God, there's really money inhere.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I want you to have it. I don't want it.",
        "response":"No, no, I ha-I have to give you something.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Weird Girl, what are you doing?",
        "response":"No, I want you to have it. I don't want it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Weird Girl, what are you doing?",
        "response":"No, I want you to have it. I don't want it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?  Oh my God, there's really money inhere.",
        "response":"I know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?  Oh my God, there's really money inhere.",
        "response":"I know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know.",
        "response":"Weird Girl, what are you doing?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know.",
        "response":"Weird Girl, what are you doing?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Would you like my tin-foil hat?",
        "response":"No. 'Cause you need that. No, it's okay, thanks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Would you like my tin-foil hat?",
        "response":"No. 'Cause you need that. No, it's okay, thanks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. 'Cause you need that. No, it's okay, thanks.",
        "response":"Please, let me do something.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. 'Cause you need that. No, it's okay, thanks.",
        "response":"Please, let me do something.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I want you to have it. I don't want it.",
        "response":"No, no, I ha-I have to give you something.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that's fine, no.",
        "response":"Would you like my tin-foil hat?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that's fine, no.",
        "response":"Would you like my tin-foil hat?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, I ha-I have to give you something.",
        "response":"Oh, that's fine, no.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, I ha-I have to give you something.",
        "response":"Oh, that's fine, no.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Please, let me do something.",
        "response":"Okay, alright, you buy me a soda, and then we're even. Okay?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Please, let me do something.",
        "response":"Okay, alright, you buy me a soda, and then we're even. Okay?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, alright, you buy me a soda, and then we're even. Okay?",
        "response":"Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, alright, you buy me a soda, and then we're even. Okay?",
        "response":"Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Keep the change.  Sure you don't wanna pretzel?",
        "response":"No, I'm fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.",
        "response":"Keep the change.  Sure you don't wanna pretzel?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.",
        "response":"Keep the change.  Sure you don't wanna pretzel?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.",
        "response":"Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.",
        "response":"Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, why is it unfair?",
        "response":"So I have a flaw! Big deal! Like Joey's constant knuckle-cracking isn'tannoying? And Ross, with his over-pronouncing every single word? And Monica, with thatsnort when she laughs? I mean, what the hell is that thing? ...I accept all those flaws,why can't you accept me for this?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know! I know, I opened it up and there it was, just floating in there, like thistiny little hitch-hiker!",
        "response":"Well, maybe it's a contest, y'know? Like, collect all five?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, maybe it's a contest, y'know? Like, collect all five?",
        "response":"Does, um, anyone wanna see?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Does the knuckle-cracking bother everybody?",
        "response":"Well, I-I could live without it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Keep the change.  Sure you don't wanna pretzel?",
        "response":"No, I'm fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, this is so unfair!",
        "response":"Oh, why is it unfair?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I'm fine.",
        "response":"See ya.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I'm fine.",
        "response":"See ya.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"See ya.",
        "response":"Huh!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, is it, like, a little annoying, or is it like when Phoebe chews her hair?",
        "response":"Oh, now, don't listen to him, Pheebs, I think it's endearing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"&quot;Indeed there isn't&quot;... I should really get back to work.",
        "response":"Yeah, 'cause otherwise someone might get what they actually ordered.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, 'cause otherwise someone might get what they actually ordered.",
        "response":"Ohh-ho-hooohhh. The hair comes out, and the gloves come on.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I-I could live without it.",
        "response":"Well, is it, like, a little annoying, or is it like when Phoebe chews her hair?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, now, don't listen to him, Pheebs, I think it's endearing.",
        "response":"Oh,  &quot;you do, do you&quot;?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, now, don't listen to him, Pheebs, I think it's endearing.",
        "response":"Oh,  &quot;you do, do you&quot;?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh,  &quot;you do, do you&quot;?",
        "response":"You know, there's nothing wrong with speaking correctly.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Okay.. Well, I'm going out with a guy my friends all really like.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did you ever go out with a guy your friends all really like?",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Can you believe it? ...Y'know what? I just don't feel <i>the thing</i>. I mean,they feel the thing, I don't feel the thing.",
        "response":"Honey.. you should always feel <i>the thing</i>. Listen, if that's how you feelabout the guy, Monica, dump him!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Can you believe it? ...Y'know what? I just don't feel <i>the thing</i>. I mean,they feel the thing, I don't feel the thing.",
        "response":"Honey.. you should always feel <i>the thing</i>. Listen, if that's how you feelabout the guy, Monica, dump him!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Waitwait.. we talking about the coyotes here? All right, a cow got through!",
        "response":"Can you believe it? ...Y'know what? I just don't feel <i>the thing</i>. I mean,they feel the thing, I don't feel the thing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Waitwait.. we talking about the coyotes here? All right, a cow got through!",
        "response":"Can you believe it? ...Y'know what? I just don't feel <i>the thing</i>. I mean,they feel the thing, I don't feel the thing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Honey.. you should always feel <i>the thing</i>. Listen, if that's how you feelabout the guy, Monica, dump him!",
        "response":"I know.. it's gonna be really hard.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Honey.. you should always feel <i>the thing</i>. Listen, if that's how you feelabout the guy, Monica, dump him!",
        "response":"I know.. it's gonna be really hard.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.. Well, I'm going out with a guy my friends all really like.",
        "response":"Waitwait.. we talking about the coyotes here? All right, a cow got through!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.. Well, I'm going out with a guy my friends all really like.",
        "response":"Waitwait.. we talking about the coyotes here? All right, a cow got through!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Okay.. Well, I'm going out with a guy my friends all really like.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chandler? It's Alan, he wants to speak to you.",
        "response":"Really? He does?  Hey, buddy, what's up! Oh, she told you aboutthat, huh. Well, yeah, I have one now and then. Well, yeah, now. Well, it's not that big-..well, that's true,.. Gee, y'know, no-one- no-one's ever put it like that before. Well,okay, thanks!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chandler? It's Alan, he wants to speak to you.",
        "response":"Really? He does?  Hey, buddy, what's up! Oh, she told you aboutthat, huh. Well, yeah, I have one now and then. Well, yeah, now. Well, it's not that big-..well, that's true,.. Gee, y'know, no-one- no-one's ever put it like that before. Well,okay, thanks!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really? He does?  Hey, buddy, what's up! Oh, she told you aboutthat, huh. Well, yeah, I have one now and then. Well, yeah, now. Well, it's not that big-..well, that's true,.. Gee, y'know, no-one- no-one's ever put it like that before. Well,okay, thanks!",
        "response":"God, he's good.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, y'know, I have had it with you guys and your cancer and your emphysema andyour heart disease. The bottom line is, smoking is cool, and you know it.",
        "response":"Chandler? It's Alan, he wants to speak to you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, he's a big boy, he'll get over it.",
        "response":"No, he'll be fine. It's the other five I'm worried about.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know.. it's gonna be really hard.",
        "response":"Well, he's a big boy, he'll get over it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know.. it's gonna be really hard.",
        "response":"Well, he's a big boy, he'll get over it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"God, he's good.",
        "response":"If only he were a woman.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"If only he were a woman.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sorry. ..Y'know, those stupid soda people gave me seven thousand dollars for thethumb.",
        "response":"You're kidding. Oh my God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, I might!",
        "response":"Sorry. ..Y'know, those stupid soda people gave me seven thousand dollars for thethumb.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're kidding. Oh my God.",
        "response":"And on my way over here, I stepped in gum. ...What is up with the universe?!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh, I'm alive with pleasure now.",
        "response":"Hey Pheebs, you gonna have the rest of that Pop-Tart?.. Pheebs?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Pheebs, you gonna have the rest of that Pop-Tart?.. Pheebs?",
        "response":"Does anyone want the rest of this Pop-Tart?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's going on?",
        "response":"Nothing. I just think it's nice when we're all here together.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Does anyone want the rest of this Pop-Tart?",
        "response":"Hey, I might!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Does anyone want the rest of this Pop-Tart?",
        "response":"Hey, I might!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"There y'go.",
        "response":"Ooh, I'm alive with pleasure now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nothing. I just think it's nice when we're all here together.",
        "response":"Even nicer when everyone gets to wear their underwear..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Please, guys, we have to talk.",
        "response":"Wait, wait, I'm getting a <i>deja vu</i>...no, I'm not.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wait, wait, I'm getting a <i>deja vu</i>...no, I'm not.",
        "response":"Alright, we have to talk.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wait, wait, I'm getting a <i>deja vu</i>...no, I'm not.",
        "response":"Alright, we have to talk.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Even nicer when everyone gets to wear their underwear..",
        "response":"Uh, Joey..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh! That was Lambchop!",
        "response":"Please, guys, we have to talk.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay..",
        "response":"Oh! That was Lambchop!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, Joey..",
        "response":"Oh, God!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, we have to talk.",
        "response":"There it is!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay. It's-it's about Alan. There's something that you should know. I mean,there's really no easy way to say this.. uh.. I've decided to break up with Alan.",
        "response":"Is there somebody else?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"-but that wouldn't be fair to me, it wouldn't be fair to Alan- It wouldn't be fairto you!",
        "response":"Who-who wants fair? Y'know, I just want things back. Y'know, the way they were.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"There it is!",
        "response":"Okay. It's-it's about Alan. There's something that you should know. I mean,there's really no easy way to say this.. uh.. I've decided to break up with Alan.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Who-who wants fair? Y'know, I just want things back. Y'know, the way they were.",
        "response":"I'm sorry..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'll meet somone else. There'll be other Alans.",
        "response":"Oh, yeah! Right!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Is there somebody else?",
        "response":"No, nononono.. it's just.. things change. People change.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay!",
        "response":"-but that wouldn't be fair to me, it wouldn't be fair to Alan- It wouldn't be fairto you!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, I- I could go on pretending-",
        "response":"Okay!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, we have to talk.",
        "response":"There it is!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm, I'm really sorry.",
        "response":"Yeah, I'm sorry too. But, I gotta tell you, I am a little relieved.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm, I'm really sorry.",
        "response":"Yeah, I'm sorry too. But, I gotta tell you, I am a little relieved.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you guys gonna be okay?",
        "response":"Hey hey, we'll be fine. We're just gonna need a little time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey hey, we'll be fine. We're just gonna need a little time.",
        "response":"I understand.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I'm sorry too. But, I gotta tell you, I am a little relieved.",
        "response":"Relieved?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah! Right!",
        "response":"Are you guys gonna be okay?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow.",
        "response":"I'm, I'm really sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow.",
        "response":"I'm, I'm really sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I understand.",
        "response":"Wow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't care, I don't care! Game's over! I'm weak! I've gotta smoke!I've gotta have the smoke!",
        "response":"If you never smoke again I'll give you seven thousanddollars!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Relieved?",
        "response":"Yeah, well, I had a great time with you.. I just can't stand your friends.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"If you never smoke again I'll give you seven thousanddollars!",
        "response":"Yeah, alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I'm sorry too. But, I gotta tell you, I am a little relieved.",
        "response":"Relieved?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did he mention us?",
        "response":"He said he's really gonna miss you guys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No no no!",
        "response":"I don't care, I don't care! Game's over! I'm weak! I've gotta smoke!I've gotta have the smoke!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, y'know..",
        "response":"Did he mention us?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...That's it. I'm getting cigarettes.",
        "response":"No no no!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, if Little Joey's dead, then I got no reason to live!",
        "response":"Joey, uh- <b>OM</b>nipotent.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I cannot sleep in a public place.",
        "response":"Would you look at her? She is so peaceful.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, Joey, what would you do if you were omnipotent?",
        "response":"Probably kill myself!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"..Excuse me?",
        "response":"Hey, if Little Joey's dead, then I got no reason to live!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey, uh- <b>OM</b>nipotent.",
        "response":"You <i>are</i>? Ross, I'm sorry..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How does she do that?",
        "response":"I cannot sleep in a public place.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Probably kill myself!",
        "response":"..Excuse me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Probably kill myself!",
        "response":"..Excuse me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I got no sleep last night!",
        "response":"Why?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"My grandmother has this new boyfriend, and they're both kind of insecure in bed.Oh, and deaf. So they're constantly, like, having to reassure each other that they'rehaving a good time. You have no idea how loud they are!",
        "response":"Well, if you want, you can stay with Rachel and me tonight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why?",
        "response":"My grandmother has this new boyfriend, and they're both kind of insecure in bed.Oh, and deaf. So they're constantly, like, having to reassure each other that they'rehaving a good time. You have no idea how loud they are!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You got waaaay too much free time.",
        "response":"Hey! Here's the birthday boy! Ross, check it out: hockey tickets,Rangers-Penguins, tonight at the Garden, and we're taking you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You got waaaay too much free time.",
        "response":"Hey! Here's the birthday boy! Ross, check it out: hockey tickets,Rangers-Penguins, tonight at the Garden, and we're taking you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Ninety-five, ninety-six, ninety-seven. See, I told you! Less than a hundred stepsfrom our place to here.",
        "response":"You got waaaay too much free time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey! Here's the birthday boy! Ross, check it out: hockey tickets,Rangers-Penguins, tonight at the Garden, and we're taking you.",
        "response":"Happy birthday, pal!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey! Here's the birthday boy! Ross, check it out: hockey tickets,Rangers-Penguins, tonight at the Garden, and we're taking you.",
        "response":"Happy birthday, pal!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, if you want, you can stay with Rachel and me tonight.",
        "response":"Thanks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Happy birthday, pal!",
        "response":"We love you, man.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, I'm guessing you had an extra ticket and couldn't decide which one of you got tobring a date?",
        "response":"Well, aren't we Mr. &quot;The glass is half empty&quot;.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon, Ross! You, me, Joey, ice, guys' night out,c'mon, whaddya say, big guy,  huh? huh? huh?",
        "response":"What are you doing?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, aren't we Mr. &quot;The glass is half empty&quot;.",
        "response":"Oh my God, oh- is today the twentieth, October twentieth?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So?",
        "response":"So, I'm guessing you had an extra ticket and couldn't decide which one of you got tobring a date?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God, oh- is today the twentieth, October twentieth?",
        "response":"Oh, I was hoping you wouldn't remember.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We love you, man.",
        "response":"Funny, my birthday was seven months ago.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Funny, my birthday was seven months ago.",
        "response":"So?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Funny, my birthday was seven months ago.",
        "response":"So?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I was hoping you wouldn't remember.",
        "response":"Ohhh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I remember the day I got my first pay check. There was a cave in in one of themines, and eight people were killed.",
        "response":"Wow, you worked in a mine?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"LESLIE) Look at you, you are so big I can't believe it!",
        "response":"I know. I know! I'm a duplex.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I swear I've seen birds do this on Wild Kingdom.",
        "response":"What are you guys doing here?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God!",
        "response":"I swear I've seen birds do this on Wild Kingdom.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow, you worked in a mine?",
        "response":"I worked in a Dairy Queen, why?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, yeah.",
        "response":"Oh, by the way, <i>great</i> service tonight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You can totally, totally live on this.",
        "response":"Yeah, yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What are you doing?",
        "response":"I have no idea.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Carol was wearing boots just like those the night that we- we first- y'know. Fact,she, uh- she never took'em off, 'cause we-we-  Sorry. Sorry.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Leech spots Messier in the crease- there's the pass!",
        "response":"We'll take a brief time out while Messier stops to look at some women's shoes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Poulet passes it up to Leech!",
        "response":"Leech spots Messier in the crease- there's the pass!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know. I know! I'm a duplex.",
        "response":"So what's going on with you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, Bunny?",
        "response":"Peach pit. That night we, uh- we had-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Peach pit. That night we, uh- we had-",
        "response":"-Peaches?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"-Peaches?",
        "response":"Actually, nectarines, but basically..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Peach pit.",
        "response":"Yes, Bunny?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Peach pit.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Could've been a peach.",
        "response":"Then, uh, then we got dressed, and I-I... I walked her to the-  -the bus stop... I'm fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Actually, nectarines, but basically..",
        "response":"Could've been a peach.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright. Let's talk reality for a second.",
        "response":"Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"When are you coming home?",
        "response":"What? Guys, I'm not.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"When are you coming home?",
        "response":"What? Guys, I'm not.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? Guys, I'm not.",
        "response":"C'mon, this is us.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? Guys, I'm not.",
        "response":"C'mon, this is us.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.",
        "response":"When are you coming home?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.",
        "response":"When are you coming home?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Waitressing?",
        "response":"Okay, I'm not just waitressing. I'm.. I, um... I write the specials on thespecials board, and, uh... and I, uh... I take the uh dead flowers out of the vase... Oh,and, um, sometimes Artelle lets me put the little chocolate blobbies on the cookies.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.",
        "response":"We thought since Phoebe was staying over tonight we'd have kinda like a slumberparty thing. We got some trashy magazines, we got cookie dough, we got Twister..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, Rach. How was it with your friends?  Okay! How wouldyou like some Tiki Death Punch?",
        "response":"What's that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm not! This is what I'm doing now. I've got this job-",
        "response":"Waitressing?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon, this is us.",
        "response":"I'm not! This is what I'm doing now. I've got this job-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's that?",
        "response":"Weeeell, it's rum, and-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's that?",
        "response":"Weeeell, it's rum, and-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Weeeell, it's rum, and-",
        "response":"Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Weeeell, it's rum, and-",
        "response":"Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We thought since Phoebe was staying over tonight we'd have kinda like a slumberparty thing. We got some trashy magazines, we got cookie dough, we got Twister..",
        "response":"Ooh! Ooh! And I brought Operation! But, um, I lost the tweezers, so we can'toperate. But we can prep the guy!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Could you please tell me what this is in reference to? ...Yes, hold on. Um, they say there's been some unusual activity on your account.",
        "response":"But I haven't used my card in weeks!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Could you please tell me what this is in reference to? ...Yes, hold on. Um, they say there's been some unusual activity on your account.",
        "response":"But I haven't used my card in weeks!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, God, ask them what they want.",
        "response":"Could you please tell me what this is in reference to? ...Yes, hold on. Um, they say there's been some unusual activity on your account.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, God, ask them what they want.",
        "response":"Could you please tell me what this is in reference to? ...Yes, hold on. Um, they say there's been some unusual activity on your account.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh! Ooh! And I brought Operation! But, um, I lost the tweezers, so we can'toperate. But we can prep the guy!",
        "response":"Uh, Rach, it's the Visa card people.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But I haven't used my card in weeks!",
        "response":"That <i>is</i> the unusual activity. Look, they just wanna see if you're okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But I haven't used my card in weeks!",
        "response":"That <i>is</i> the unusual activity. Look, they just wanna see if you're okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, Rach, it's the Visa card people.",
        "response":"Oh, God, ask them what they want.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That <i>is</i> the unusual activity. Look, they just wanna see if you're okay.",
        "response":"They wanna know if I'm okay. Okay.. they wanna know if I'm okay, okay, let's see.Well, let's see, the FICA guys took all my money, everyone I know is either gettingmarried, or getting promoted, or getting pregnant, and I'm getting coffee! And it's noteven for me! So if that sounds like I'm okay, okay, then you can tell them I'm okay, okay?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That <i>is</i> the unusual activity. Look, they just wanna see if you're okay.",
        "response":"They wanna know if I'm okay. Okay.. they wanna know if I'm okay, okay, let's see.Well, let's see, the FICA guys took all my money, everyone I know is either gettingmarried, or getting promoted, or getting pregnant, and I'm getting coffee! And it's noteven for me! So if that sounds like I'm okay, okay, then you can tell them I'm okay, okay?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"They wanna know if I'm okay. Okay.. they wanna know if I'm okay, okay, let's see.Well, let's see, the FICA guys took all my money, everyone I know is either gettingmarried, or getting promoted, or getting pregnant, and I'm getting coffee! And it's noteven for me! So if that sounds like I'm okay, okay, then you can tell them I'm okay, okay?",
        "response":"Uh- Rachel has left the building, can you call back?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"They wanna know if I'm okay. Okay.. they wanna know if I'm okay, okay, let's see.Well, let's see, the FICA guys took all my money, everyone I know is either gettingmarried, or getting promoted, or getting pregnant, and I'm getting coffee! And it's noteven for me! So if that sounds like I'm okay, okay, then you can tell them I'm okay, okay?",
        "response":"Uh- Rachel has left the building, can you call back?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? There was ice there that night with Carol? Plastic seats? Four thousandangry Pittsburgh fans?",
        "response":"No, actually I was just saying it looks like we're not sitting together. But now youmention it, there <b>was</b> ice there that night... It was the first frost...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sorry, sorry... Uh-oh.",
        "response":"What? There was ice there that night with Carol? Plastic seats? Four thousandangry Pittsburgh fans?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh- Rachel has left the building, can you call back?",
        "response":"Alright, c'mon!  Let's play Twister!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Monica, what is so amazing? I gave up, like, everything. And for what?",
        "response":"You are just like Jack.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You are just like Jack.",
        "response":"...Jack from downstairs?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, right! See, he gave up something, but then he got those magic beans. Andthen he woke up, and there was this, this big plant outside his window, full ofpossibilities and stuff.. And he lived in a village, and you live in <b>the</b> Village..",
        "response":"Okay, but Pheebs, Pheebs, Jack gave up a cow, I gave up an orthodontist. Okay,I-I-I know, I know I didn't love him-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ah, the other Jack.",
        "response":"Yeah, right! See, he gave up something, but then he got those magic beans. Andthen he woke up, and there was this, this big plant outside his window, full ofpossibilities and stuff.. And he lived in a village, and you live in <b>the</b> Village..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, but Pheebs, Pheebs, Jack gave up a cow, I gave up an orthodontist. Okay,I-I-I know, I know I didn't love him-",
        "response":"Oh, see, Jack did love the cow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, but Pheebs, Pheebs, Jack gave up a cow, I gave up an orthodontist. Okay,I-I-I know, I know I didn't love him-",
        "response":"Oh, see, Jack did love the cow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, see, Jack did love the cow.",
        "response":"But see, it was a plan. Y'know, it was clear. It was figured out, and noweverything's just kinda like-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, see, Jack did love the cow.",
        "response":"But see, it was a plan. Y'know, it was clear. It was figured out, and noweverything's just kinda like-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You are just like Jack.",
        "response":"...Jack from downstairs?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Jack from downstairs?",
        "response":"No, Jack and the Beanstalk.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, Jack and the Beanstalk.",
        "response":"Ah, the other Jack.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Get him! GET HIM! Get him! Get- YESSS! Not laughing now, are ya pal!",
        "response":"See buddy, that's all you need, a bunch of toothless guys hitting eachother with sticks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"See buddy, that's all you need, a bunch of toothless guys hitting eachother with sticks.",
        "response":"Pass it! Pass it!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"See buddy, that's all you need, a bunch of toothless guys hitting eachother with sticks.",
        "response":"Pass it! Pass it!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But see, it was a plan. Y'know, it was clear. It was figured out, and noweverything's just kinda like-",
        "response":"Floopy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But see, it was a plan. Y'know, it was clear. It was figured out, and noweverything's just kinda like-",
        "response":"Floopy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He's open!",
        "response":"Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Pass it! Pass it!",
        "response":"He's open!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Floopy?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It says to call this number ifyou're not completely satisfied with this candy bar. Well, I'm not completely satisfied.",
        "response":"Listen, it's kind of an emergency. Well, I guess you know that, or we'd be inthe predicament room.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It says to call this number ifyou're not completely satisfied with this candy bar. Well, I'm not completely satisfied.",
        "response":"Listen, it's kind of an emergency. Well, I guess you know that, or we'd be inthe predicament room.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, I don't wanna make any trouble, okay, but I'm in a lot ofpain here, alright? My face is <b>dented</b>.",
        "response":"Well, you'll have to wait your turn.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hold on.  Fill these out, sit over there.",
        "response":"Look, I don't wanna make any trouble, okay, but I'm in a lot ofpain here, alright? My face is <b>dented</b>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Listen, it's kind of an emergency. Well, I guess you know that, or we'd be inthe predicament room.",
        "response":"Hold on.  Fill these out, sit over there.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"'Scuse me.",
        "response":"It says to call this number ifyou're not completely satisfied with this candy bar. Well, I'm not completely satisfied.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you'll have to wait your turn.",
        "response":"Well, how long do you think it'll be?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, how long do you think it'll be?",
        "response":"Any minute now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!",
        "response":"Hey, look, we're on that TV thing!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"PIZZA GUY: Yeah. This one goes across the street, I must have given him yours. Oh,bonehead, bonehead!",
        "response":"Wait, was this a-a small mediterranean guy with curiously intelligent good looks?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wait! Did you say 'G.Stephanopoulos'?",
        "response":"PIZZA GUY: Yeah. This one goes across the street, I must have given him yours. Oh,bonehead, bonehead!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wait, was this a-a small mediterranean guy with curiously intelligent good looks?",
        "response":"PIZZA GUY: Yeah, that sounds about right.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"PIZZA GUY: Yeah, that sounds about right.",
        "response":"Was he wearing a stunning blue suit?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God.",
        "response":"PIZZA GUY: So you guys want me to take this back?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Do you have a plan?",
        "response":"I don't even have a 'pl'.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Do you have a plan?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Do you have a plan?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebe?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"White House adviser? Clinton's campaign guy? The one with the great hair, sexysmile, really cute butt?",
        "response":"Oh, him, the little guy? Oh, I love him!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello? Who are we spying on?",
        "response":"White House adviser? Clinton's campaign guy? The one with the great hair, sexysmile, really cute butt?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"PIZZA GUY: So you guys want me to take this back?",
        "response":"Are you nuts?! We've got George Stephanopoulos' pizza!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh, wait.. wait, I see a woman.",
        "response":"Please tell me it's his mother.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Please tell me it's his mother.",
        "response":"Definitely not his mother.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Please tell me it's his mother.",
        "response":"Definitely not his mother.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I see pizza!",
        "response":"Oh, I wanna see! Lemme see! Lemme see!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Big Bird's friend.",
        "response":"I see pizza!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Definitely not his mother.",
        "response":"Oh, no...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, no...",
        "response":"Oh, wait, she's walking across the floor.. she's walking.. she's walking.. she'sgoing for the pizza-  Hey, that's not for you, bitch!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MONICA+PHOEBE: Shut up!",
        "response":"So, whaddya think George is like?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh please, they're having sex.",
        "response":"MONICA+PHOEBE: Shut up!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh. Maybe they're- napping.",
        "response":"Oh please, they're having sex.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Oh. Maybe they're- napping.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Oh. Maybe they're- napping.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Definitely not his mother.",
        "response":"Oh, no...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I think he's shy.",
        "response":"Yeah?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Light still out?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, what? What? What is it? That she left you? That she likes women? That sheleft you for another woman that likes women?",
        "response":"Little louder, okay, I think there's a man on the twelfth floor in a coma thatdidn't quite hear you...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, what? What? What is it? That she left you? That she likes women? That sheleft you for another woman that likes women?",
        "response":"Little louder, okay, I think there's a man on the twelfth floor in a coma thatdidn't quite hear you...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, it's just a little more complicated...",
        "response":"Well, what? What? What is it? That she left you? That she likes women? That sheleft you for another woman that likes women?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Little louder, okay, I think there's a man on the twelfth floor in a coma thatdidn't quite hear you...",
        "response":"Then what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Little louder, okay, I think there's a man on the twelfth floor in a coma thatdidn't quite hear you...",
        "response":"Then what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah?",
        "response":"Yeah. I think you have to draw him out. And then- when you do- he's a preppyanimal.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Then what?",
        "response":"My first time with Carol was..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"My first time with Carol was..",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So in your whole life, you've only been with one-  -oh.",
        "response":"Whoah, boy, hockey was a big mistake! There was a whole bunch of stuff we could'vedone tonight!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, unless goose is a vegetable...ha haaaah!",
        "response":"Oh! Oh! Oh! Okay, fine, fine. Now I don't feel so bad about sleeping with JasonHurley.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay. Okay, I got one. Do you remember that vegetarian pate that I made that youloved so much?",
        "response":"Uh-huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh.",
        "response":"So in your whole life, you've only been with one-  -oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh.",
        "response":"Well, unless goose is a vegetable...ha haaaah!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh.",
        "response":"Well, unless goose is a vegetable...ha haaaah!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It was my <i>first time</i>.",
        "response":"With Carol?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"It was my <i>first time</i>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"It was my <i>first time</i>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, unless goose is a vegetable...ha haaaah!",
        "response":"Oh! Oh! Oh! Okay, fine, fine. Now I don't feel so bad about sleeping with JasonHurley.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that's nice!",
        "response":"Okay, okay, okay, I got one!  Anyway- The valentine Tommy Rollerson left in your locker wasreally from me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, okay, okay, I got one!  Anyway- The valentine Tommy Rollerson left in your locker wasreally from me.",
        "response":"Excuse me?!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, okay, okay, I got one!  Anyway- The valentine Tommy Rollerson left in your locker wasreally from me.",
        "response":"Excuse me?!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh! Oh! Oh! Okay, fine, fine. Now I don't feel so bad about sleeping with JasonHurley.",
        "response":"What?! You slept with Jason?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh! Oh! Oh! Okay, fine, fine. Now I don't feel so bad about sleeping with JasonHurley.",
        "response":"What?! You slept with Jason?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?! You slept with Jason?",
        "response":"You'd already broken up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You'd already broken up.",
        "response":"How long?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How long?",
        "response":"A couple hours.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello? Like he was really gonna send you one?  She was a <i>big girl</i>.",
        "response":"Really. Well, at least 'big girls' don't pee in their pants in seventh grade!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello? Like he was really gonna send you one?  She was a <i>big girl</i>.",
        "response":"Really. Well, at least 'big girls' don't pee in their pants in seventh grade!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Man. Can you believe he's only had sex with one woman?",
        "response":"I think it's great. Y'know, it's sweet, it's romantic..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really. Well, at least 'big girls' don't pee in their pants in seventh grade!",
        "response":"I was laughing! You made me laugh!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Excuse me?!",
        "response":"Hello? Like he was really gonna send you one?  She was a <i>big girl</i>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Excuse me?!",
        "response":"Hello? Like he was really gonna send you one?  She was a <i>big girl</i>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I think it's great. Y'know, it's sweet, it's romantic..",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Where?",
        "response":"Right- where we've been looking all night!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"There he is! There he is!",
        "response":"Where?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Fun? Where was the fun? Tell me specifically, which part was the fun part? Where'smy puck?",
        "response":"Oh, ah- the kid has it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah? Well, I'm rubber, you're glue, whatever-  -can't doit.  Listen, uh- gimme back my puck.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, ah- the kid has it.",
        "response":"The kid..?  Excuse me, uh, that's, that's my puck.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Now <b>that</b> was fun.",
        "response":"<b>CREDITS SCENE: RACHEL+MONICA'S PLACE</b>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I think it's great. Y'know, it's sweet, it's romantic..",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"No, you kidding? The guy's a freak..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"'Yes', how about. C'mere. Gimme!",
        "response":"No! No!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"'Yes', how about. C'mere. Gimme!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"'Yes', how about. C'mere. Gimme!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright.  Yes, this is Rachel.",
        "response":"Nooo!  Hello? Oh, yeah, no, I know, I-Ihaven't been using it much. Oh, well, thanks, but, I'm okay, really.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nooo!  Hello? Oh, yeah, no, I know, I-Ihaven't been using it much. Oh, well, thanks, but, I'm okay, really.",
        "response":"Green. To the green.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, Pheebs: Right hand blue. Good.",
        "response":"Hello? Oh, uh, Rachel, it's the Visa card people.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello? Oh, uh, Rachel, it's the Visa card people.",
        "response":"Oh, okay. Will you take my place?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<b>CREDITS SCENE: RACHEL+MONICA'S PLACE</b>",
        "response":"Okay, Monica: Right foot red.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, okay. Will you take my place?",
        "response":"Alright.  Yes, this is Rachel.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, okay. Will you take my place?",
        "response":"Alright.  Yes, this is Rachel.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Green. To the green.",
        "response":"I've got magic beans. Never-never mind.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thanks.",
        "response":"Okay, Pheebs: Right hand blue. Good.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"To the left, to the left- aww!",
        "response":"Ohhh... I'm fine.</font></p><p align=\"center\"><strong><font size=\"3\">END</font></strong></p><hr><p align=\"center\"><!--webbot bot=\"ImageMap\" startspanrectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season1/105egld.htm\"rectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season1.htm\"rectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season1/103thumb.htm\"src=\"contrl08.gif\" width=\"194\" height=\"60\"alt=\"Contrl08.gif \" --><MAP NAME=\"FrontPageMap0\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"139, 1, 197, 84\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season1/105egld.htm\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"70, 2, 129, 84\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season1.htm\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"0, 1, 55, 79\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season1/103thumb.htm\"></MAP><img src=\"contrl08.gif\" width=\"194\" height=\"60\" alt=\"Contrl08.gif \" usemap=\"#FrontPageMap0\"><!--webbot bot=\"ImageMap\" i-checksum=\"16661\" endspan--></p><hr><center><img src=\"/cgi-bin/counter/24\"></center><hr></body></html>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"There's a beautiful woman at eight, nine, teno'clock!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"There's a beautiful woman at eight, nine, teno'clock!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I've got magic beans. Never-never mind.",
        "response":"To the left, to the left- aww!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ross, ten o'clock.",
        "response":"Is it? Feels like two.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Is it? Feels like two.",
        "response":"No, <b>ten o'clock</b>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Is it? Feels like two.",
        "response":"No, <b>ten o'clock</b>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, <b>ten o'clock</b>.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, <b>ten o'clock</b>.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh please, could she <i>be</i> more out of my league? Ross, back me up here.",
        "response":"He could never get a woman like that in a million years.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, c'mon. She's a person, you can do it!",
        "response":"Oh please, could she <i>be</i> more out of my league? Ross, back me up here.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"She's amazing! She makes the women that I dream about look like short, fat, baldmen!",
        "response":"Well, go over to her! She's not with anyone.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah, and what would my opening line be? 'Excuse me. Blarrglarrghh.'",
        "response":"Oh, c'mon. She's a person, you can do it!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, go over to her! She's not with anyone.",
        "response":"Oh yeah, and what would my opening line be? 'Excuse me. Blarrglarrghh.'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh. Hel-lo!",
        "response":"She's amazing! She makes the women that I dream about look like short, fat, baldmen!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He could never get a woman like that in a million years.",
        "response":"Thank you, buddy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"There's a beautiful woman at eight, nine, teno'clock!",
        "response":"Oh. Hel-lo!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"There's a beautiful woman at eight, nine, teno'clock!",
        "response":"Oh. Hel-lo!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.... um... okay, next word... would be... Chandler! Chandler is my name, and,uh... ...hi.",
        "response":"Yes, you said that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.... um... okay, next word... would be... Chandler! Chandler is my name, and,uh... ...hi.",
        "response":"Yes, you said that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God, I can't believe I'm even considering this... I'm very very aware of mytongue...",
        "response":"C'mon! C'mon!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah!",
        "response":"Oh God, I can't believe I'm even considering this... I'm very very aware of mytongue...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Yes?",
        "response":"Hi.... um... okay, next word... would be... Chandler! Chandler is my name, and,uh... ...hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Yes?",
        "response":"Hi.... um... okay, next word... would be... Chandler! Chandler is my name, and,uh... ...hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon! C'mon!",
        "response":"Here goes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Y'think?",
        "response":"Yeah!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Here goes.",
        "response":"...Yes?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Hey! You're in a play! I didn't know you could dance! You had a beard!",
        "response":"C'mon, you guys, it wasn't that bad. It was better than that thing I did with thetrolls, at least you got to see my head.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Hey! You're in a play! I didn't know you could dance! You had a beard!",
        "response":"C'mon, you guys, it wasn't that bad. It was better than that thing I did with thetrolls, at least you got to see my head.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, you said that.",
        "response":"Yes, yes I did, but what I didn't say was what I was about to say, what I wantedto say was, uh... would you like to go out with me sometime, thankyou, goodnight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, you said that.",
        "response":"Yes, yes I did, but what I didn't say was what I was about to say, what I wantedto say was, uh... would you like to go out with me sometime, thankyou, goodnight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, yes I did, but what I didn't say was what I was about to say, what I wantedto say was, uh... would you like to go out with me sometime, thankyou, goodnight.",
        "response":"Chandler?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon, you guys, it wasn't that bad. It was better than that thing I did with thetrolls, at least you got to see my head.",
        "response":"Saw your head. Saw your head.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whadja think?",
        "response":"...Hey! You're in a play! I didn't know you could dance! You had a beard!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whadja think?",
        "response":"...Hey! You're in a play! I didn't know you could dance! You had a beard!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey! You're in a play! I didn't know you could dance! You had a beard!",
        "response":"Whadja think?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It was unbelievable. I-I've never met anyone like her. She's had the mostamazing life! She was in the Israeli army...",
        "response":"<i>AURORA: ...Luckily none of the bullets hit the engine block. So, we made it to theborder, but just barely, and I- ...I've been talking about myself all night long, I'msorry. What about you? Tell me one of your stories.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<i>AURORA: ...Luckily none of the bullets hit the engine block. So, we made it to theborder, but just barely, and I- ...I've been talking about myself all night long, I'msorry. What about you? Tell me one of your stories.",
        "response":"Alright. Once I got on the subway, right, and it was at night, and I rode it allthe way to Brooklyn... just for the hell of it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I'm still married.",
        "response":"So tell me, how do- how do you think your husband would feel about you sittinghere with me?...Sliding your foot so far up my pant leg you can count the change in mypocket?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I'm still married.",
        "response":"So tell me, how do- how do you think your husband would feel about you sittinghere with me?...Sliding your foot so far up my pant leg you can count the change in mypocket?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I can't believe I've been here almost seven seconds and you haven't askedme how my date went.",
        "response":"Oh, right, right. How was your date, 'Chand-lrr'?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, right, right. How was your date, 'Chand-lrr'?",
        "response":"It was unbelievable. I-I've never met anyone like her. She's had the mostamazing life! She was in the Israeli army...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I'm sorry, then you're widowed?...Hopefully?",
        "response":"No, I'm still married.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I'm sorry, then you're widowed?...Hopefully?",
        "response":"No, I'm still married.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Oh, I'm sorry, then you're widowed?...Hopefully?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Didn't you listen to the story? I mean, this is twisted! How could you getinvolved with a woman like this?",
        "response":"Well, y'know, I had some trouble with it at first too, but the way I look at itis, I get all the good stuff: all the fun, all the talking, all the sex; and <b>none</b>of the responsibility. I mean, this is every guy's fantasy!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So tell me, how do- how do you think your husband would feel about you sittinghere with me?...Sliding your foot so far up my pant leg you can count the change in mypocket?",
        "response":"Don't worry. I imagine he'd be okay with you because really, he's okay with Ethan.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So tell me, how do- how do you think your husband would feel about you sittinghere with me?...Sliding your foot so far up my pant leg you can count the change in mypocket?",
        "response":"Don't worry. I imagine he'd be okay with you because really, he's okay with Ethan.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What 'not work out'? I'm seeing her again on Thursday. Didn't you listen to thestory?",
        "response":"Didn't you listen to the story? I mean, this is twisted! How could you getinvolved with a woman like this?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"</i>MONICA: Oh. I'm sorry it didn't work out.",
        "response":"What 'not work out'? I'm seeing her again on Thursday. Didn't you listen to thestory?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Don't worry. I imagine he'd be okay with you because really, he's okay with Ethan.",
        "response":"Ethan? There's, there's an Ethan?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Don't worry. I imagine he'd be okay with you because really, he's okay with Ethan.",
        "response":"Ethan? There's, there's an Ethan?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Hm.",
        "response":"</i>MONICA: Oh. I'm sorry it didn't work out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ethan? There's, there's an Ethan?",
        "response":"Mmmm... Ethan is my... boyfriend.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are we greeting each other this way now? 'Cause I like that.",
        "response":"Look! I cleaned! I did the windows, I did the floors... I even used all theattachments on the vacuum, except that little round one with the bristles, I don't knowwhat that's for.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look! I cleaned! I did the windows, I did the floors... I even used all theattachments on the vacuum, except that little round one with the bristles, I don't knowwhat that's for.",
        "response":"Oh yeah, nobody knows. And we're not supposed to ask.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Good for you, Joey.",
        "response":"When I'm with a woman, I need to <em>know</em> that I'm going out with more peoplethan she is.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? So you guys don't mind going out with someone else who's going out withsomeone else?",
        "response":"I couldn't do it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Very clean! It looks great! Terrific!",
        "response":"...Oh! I-I see you moved the green ottoman.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah, nobody knows. And we're not supposed to ask.",
        "response":"Well, whaddya think?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Tah-daaah!",
        "response":"Are we greeting each other this way now? 'Cause I like that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I couldn't do it.",
        "response":"Good for you, Joey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I couldn't do it.",
        "response":"Good for you, Joey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I dunno.. I-I thought it looked better there. And I- and also, it's an extra seataround the coffee table.",
        "response":"Yeah, yeah, it's interesting.. but y'know what? Just for fun, let's see what itlooked like in the old spot.  Alright, just to compare. Let's see. Well, itlooks good there too. Let's just leave it there for a while.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How-how did that happen?",
        "response":"I dunno.. I-I thought it looked better there. And I- and also, it's an extra seataround the coffee table.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You guys, I am not that bad!",
        "response":"Yeah, you are, Monica. Remember when I lived with you? You were like, a little,y'know,  Ree! Ree! Ree! Ree!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, you are, Monica. Remember when I lived with you? You were like, a little,y'know,  Ree! Ree! Ree! Ree!",
        "response":"That is so unfair!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That is so unfair!",
        "response":"Oh c'mon! When we were kids, yours was the only Raggedy Ann doll that wasn'traggedy!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Oh! I-I see you moved the green ottoman.",
        "response":"Uh-oh...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Oh! I-I see you moved the green ottoman.",
        "response":"Uh-oh...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-oh...",
        "response":"How-how did that happen?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, so I'm responsible, I'm organised. But hey, I can be a kook.",
        "response":"Alright, you madcap gal. Try to imagine this. The phone bill arrives, but you don'tpay it right away.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, so I'm responsible, I'm organised. But hey, I can be a kook.",
        "response":"Alright, you madcap gal. Try to imagine this. The phone bill arrives, but you don'tpay it right away.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh c'mon! When we were kids, yours was the only Raggedy Ann doll that wasn'traggedy!",
        "response":"Okay, so I'm responsible, I'm organised. But hey, I can be a kook.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh c'mon! When we were kids, yours was the only Raggedy Ann doll that wasn'traggedy!",
        "response":"Okay, so I'm responsible, I'm organised. But hey, I can be a kook.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, you madcap gal. Try to imagine this. The phone bill arrives, but you don'tpay it right away.",
        "response":"Why not?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, you madcap gal. Try to imagine this. The phone bill arrives, but you don'tpay it right away.",
        "response":"Why not?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Because you're a kook! Instead you wait until they send you a notice.",
        "response":"I could do that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why not?",
        "response":"Because you're a kook! Instead you wait until they send you a notice.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why not?",
        "response":"Because you're a kook! Instead you wait until they send you a notice.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why would someone do that?! ...One might wonder.",
        "response":"Someone's left a glass on the coffee table. There's no coaster. It's a colddrink, it's a hot day. Little beads of condensation are inching their way closer andcloser to the surface of the wood...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Someone's left a glass on the coffee table. There's no coaster. It's a colddrink, it's a hot day. Little beads of condensation are inching their way closer andcloser to the surface of the wood...",
        "response":"STOP IT!! ...Oh my God. It's true! Who am I?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, uh, you let me go grocery shopping, and I buy laundry detergent, but it'snot the one with the easy-pour spout.",
        "response":"Why would someone do that?! ...One might wonder.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Can you believe this? Al Pacino! This guy's the reason I became an actor! 'I'm outof order? Pfeeeh. You're out of order! This whole courtroom's out of order!'",
        "response":"Seriously, what-what's the part?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I could do that.",
        "response":"Okay, uh, you let me go grocery shopping, and I buy laundry detergent, but it'snot the one with the easy-pour spout.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"'Just when I thought I was out, they pull me back in!'",
        "response":"C'mon, seriously, Joey, what's the part?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Seriously, what-what's the part?",
        "response":"'Just when I thought I was out, they pull me back in!'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon, seriously, Joey, what's the part?",
        "response":"...I'm his",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...I'm his",
        "response":"..You're, you're 'mah mah mah' what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh no, it's terrific, it's- it's- y'know, you deserve this, after all your yearsof struggling, you've finally been able to crack your way into showbusiness.",
        "response":"Okay, okay, fine! Make jokes, I don't care! This is a big break for me!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon, you guys. This is a real movie, and Al Pacino's in it, and that's big!",
        "response":"Oh no, it's terrific, it's- it's- y'know, you deserve this, after all your yearsof struggling, you've finally been able to crack your way into showbusiness.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"..You're, you're 'mah mah mah' what?",
        "response":"...I'm his butt double. 'Kay? I play Al Pacino's butt. Alright? He goes into theshower, and then- I'm his butt.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...I'm his butt double. 'Kay? I play Al Pacino's butt. Alright? He goes into theshower, and then- I'm his butt.",
        "response":"Oh my God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God.",
        "response":"C'mon, you guys. This is a real movie, and Al Pacino's in it, and that's big!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, alright, alright...",
        "response":"Here. I need to borrow some moisturizer.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Here. I need to borrow some moisturizer.",
        "response":"For what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Here. I need to borrow some moisturizer.",
        "response":"For what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"For what?",
        "response":"Whaddya think? Today's the big day!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that would be Monica. Hey, listen, I wanna borrow a coupla things, Auroraspent the night, I really wanna make her breakfast.",
        "response":"Oh, you got the whole night, huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whaddya think? Today's the big day!",
        "response":"Oh my God. Okay, go into the bathroom, use whatever you want, just don't ever tellme what you did in there.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whaddya think? Today's the big day!",
        "response":"Oh my God. Okay, go into the bathroom, use whatever you want, just don't ever tellme what you did in there.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God. Okay, go into the bathroom, use whatever you want, just don't ever tellme what you did in there.",
        "response":"Thank you!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He's in the bathroom. I don't think you wanna go in there!",
        "response":"C'mon, we're roommates!  Myeyes!! My eyes!!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He's in the bathroom. I don't think you wanna go in there!",
        "response":"C'mon, we're roommates!  Myeyes!! My eyes!!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Where's Joey? His mom's on the phone.",
        "response":"He's in the bathroom. I don't think you wanna go in there!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon, we're roommates!  Myeyes!! My eyes!!",
        "response":"I warned you...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"For what?",
        "response":"Whaddya think? Today's the big day!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh, do I sense a little bit of resentment?",
        "response":"No, no resentment, believe me, it's worth it. 'Kay? Y'know in a relationship youhave these key moments that you know you'll remember for the rest of your life? Well,every- single- second is like that with Aurora.. and I've just wasted about thirty-five ofthem talking to you people, so, uh.. Monica, can you help me with the door?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, well, I only have twenty minutes until Ethan, so, y'know..",
        "response":"Ooh, do I sense a little bit of resentment?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Dammit, hire the girl!  Okay, everybody ready?",
        "response":"Uh, listen, I just wanna thank you for this great opportunity.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, you got the whole night, huh?",
        "response":"Yeah, well, I only have twenty minutes until Ethan, so, y'know..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, listen, I just wanna thank you for this great opportunity.",
        "response":"Lose the robe.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, listen, I just wanna thank you for this great opportunity.",
        "response":"Lose the robe.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Me?",
        "response":"That would work.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Lose the robe.",
        "response":"Me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Lose the robe.",
        "response":"Me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, that was clenching.",
        "response":"Oh. Well, the way I see it, the guy's upset here, y'know? I mean, his wife's dead,his brother's missing... I think his butt would be angry here.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, that was clenching.",
        "response":"Oh. Well, the way I see it, the guy's upset here, y'know? I mean, his wife's dead,his brother's missing... I think his butt would be angry here.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right. Okay. Losing the robe.  And the robe is lost.",
        "response":"Okay, everybody, we'd like to get this in one take, please. Let's roll it..water's working .. and... action.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And cut. Hey, Butt Guy, what the hell are you doing?",
        "response":"Well, I'm- I'm showering.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That would work.",
        "response":"Right. Okay. Losing the robe.  And the robe is lost.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That would work.",
        "response":"Right. Okay. Losing the robe.  And the robe is lost.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I'm- I'm showering.",
        "response":"No, that was clenching.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I'm- I'm showering.",
        "response":"No, that was clenching.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Me?",
        "response":"That would work.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh. Well, the way I see it, the guy's upset here, y'know? I mean, his wife's dead,his brother's missing... I think his butt would be angry here.",
        "response":"I think his butt would like to get this shot before lunch. Once again,rolling... water working... and action....and cut. What was that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh. Well, the way I see it, the guy's upset here, y'know? I mean, his wife's dead,his brother's missing... I think his butt would be angry here.",
        "response":"I think his butt would like to get this shot before lunch. Once again,rolling... water working... and action....and cut. What was that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I think his butt would like to get this shot before lunch. Once again,rolling... water working... and action....and cut. What was that?",
        "response":"I was going for quiet desperation. But if you have to ask...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, actually I meant my fingers. Look at 'em, look at how happy they are.",
        "response":"Oh my God, I'm late.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, actually I meant my fingers. Look at 'em, look at how happy they are.",
        "response":"Oh my God, I'm late.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thank you.",
        "response":"No, actually I meant my fingers. Look at 'em, look at how happy they are.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thank you.",
        "response":"No, actually I meant my fingers. Look at 'em, look at how happy they are.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God, I'm late.",
        "response":"Oh no nonononononnononono, don't go..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"God, I love these fingers...",
        "response":"Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God, I'm late.",
        "response":"Oh no nonononononnononono, don't go..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay. Oh no, I have to.",
        "response":"Too bad, she's leaving.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay. Oh no, I have to.",
        "response":"Too bad, she's leaving.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh no nonononononnononono, don't go..",
        "response":"Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh no nonononononnononono, don't go..",
        "response":"Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Don't go.",
        "response":"Okay. Oh no, I have to.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Don't go.",
        "response":"Okay. Oh no, I have to.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.",
        "response":"Don't go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.",
        "response":"Don't go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry. He'll be waiting for me.",
        "response":"Well, I thought- I thought you talked to Rick.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry. He'll be waiting for me.",
        "response":"Well, I thought- I thought you talked to Rick.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What, Ethan? He got to spend the whole day with you!",
        "response":"No, it's-it's Andrew.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's not Rick.",
        "response":"What, Ethan? He got to spend the whole day with you!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's not Rick.",
        "response":"What, Ethan? He got to spend the whole day with you!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Too bad, she's leaving.",
        "response":"I'm sorry. He'll be waiting for me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Too bad, she's leaving.",
        "response":"I'm sorry. He'll be waiting for me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I thought- I thought you talked to Rick.",
        "response":"It's not Rick.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I thought- I thought you talked to Rick.",
        "response":"It's not Rick.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, it's-it's Andrew.",
        "response":"I know there'll be many moments in the years to come when I'll regret asking thefollowing question, but- And Andrew is?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, it's-it's Andrew.",
        "response":"I know there'll be many moments in the years to come when I'll regret asking thefollowing question, but- And Andrew is?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know there'll be many moments in the years to come when I'll regret asking thefollowing question, but- And Andrew is?",
        "response":"He's... new.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know there'll be many moments in the years to come when I'll regret asking thefollowing question, but- And Andrew is?",
        "response":"He's... new.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, so what you're saying is you're not completely fulfilled by Rick, Ethan andmyself?",
        "response":"No, that's not exactly what I was..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, so what you're saying is you're not completely fulfilled by Rick, Ethan andmyself?",
        "response":"No, that's not exactly what I was..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He's... new.",
        "response":"Oh, so what you're saying is you're not completely fulfilled by Rick, Ethan andmyself?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He's... new.",
        "response":"Oh, so what you're saying is you're not completely fulfilled by Rick, Ethan andmyself?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What, Ethan? He got to spend the whole day with you!",
        "response":"No, it's-it's Andrew.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, that's not exactly what I was..",
        "response":"Well, y'know, most women would kill for three guys like us.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, that's not exactly what I was..",
        "response":"Well, y'know, most women would kill for three guys like us.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, y'know, most women would kill for three guys like us.",
        "response":"So what do you want?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, y'know, most women would kill for three guys like us.",
        "response":"So what do you want?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You have me!",
        "response":"Nono, just you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So what do you want?",
        "response":"You.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So what do you want?",
        "response":"You.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You.",
        "response":"You have me!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You.",
        "response":"You have me!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Like, ...all of them?",
        "response":"C'mon, we're great together, why not?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Like, ...all of them?",
        "response":"C'mon, we're great together, why not?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Lose the other guys.",
        "response":"...Like, ...all of them?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Lose the other guys.",
        "response":"...Like, ...all of them?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whaddyou mean?",
        "response":"Lose the other guys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whaddyou mean?",
        "response":"Lose the other guys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nono, just you.",
        "response":"Whaddyou mean?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nono, just you.",
        "response":"Whaddyou mean?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You have me!",
        "response":"Nono, just you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why can't we just have what we have now? Why can't we just talk, and laugh, andmake love, without feeling obligated to one another... and up until tonight I thoughtthat's what you wanted too.",
        "response":"...Well, y'know, part of me wants that, but it's like I'm two guys, y'know? Imean, one guy's going 'Shut up! This is great!' But there's this other guy. Actually it'sthe same guy that wells up every time that Grinch's heart grows three sizes and breaksthat measuring device... And he's saying, y'know, 'This is too hard! Get out! Get out!'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why can't we just have what we have now? Why can't we just talk, and laugh, andmake love, without feeling obligated to one another... and up until tonight I thoughtthat's what you wanted too.",
        "response":"...Well, y'know, part of me wants that, but it's like I'm two guys, y'know? Imean, one guy's going 'Shut up! This is great!' But there's this other guy. Actually it'sthe same guy that wells up every time that Grinch's heart grows three sizes and breaksthat measuring device... And he's saying, y'know, 'This is too hard! Get out! Get out!'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Well, y'know, part of me wants that, but it's like I'm two guys, y'know? Imean, one guy's going 'Shut up! This is great!' But there's this other guy. Actually it'sthe same guy that wells up every time that Grinch's heart grows three sizes and breaksthat measuring device... And he's saying, y'know, 'This is too hard! Get out! Get out!'",
        "response":"So... which one of the two guys will you listen to?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...Well, y'know, part of me wants that, but it's like I'm two guys, y'know? Imean, one guy's going 'Shut up! This is great!' But there's this other guy. Actually it'sthe same guy that wells up every time that Grinch's heart grows three sizes and breaksthat measuring device... And he's saying, y'know, 'This is too hard! Get out! Get out!'",
        "response":"So... which one of the two guys will you listen to?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon, we're great together, why not?",
        "response":"Why can't we just have what we have now? Why can't we just talk, and laugh, andmake love, without feeling obligated to one another... and up until tonight I thoughtthat's what you wanted too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon, we're great together, why not?",
        "response":"Why can't we just have what we have now? Why can't we just talk, and laugh, andmake love, without feeling obligated to one another... and up until tonight I thoughtthat's what you wanted too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So... which one of the two guys will you listen to?",
        "response":"I don't know, I-I have to listen to both of them, they don't exactly let eachother finish...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So... which one of the two guys will you listen to?",
        "response":"I don't know, I-I have to listen to both of them, they don't exactly let eachother finish...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know, I-I have to listen to both of them, they don't exactly let eachother finish...",
        "response":"Which one?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know, I-I have to listen to both of them, they don't exactly let eachother finish...",
        "response":"Which one?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, call me if you change your mind.",
        "response":"Sorry, the first guy runs the lips.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...The second guy.",
        "response":"Well, call me if you change your mind.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...The second guy.",
        "response":"Well, call me if you change your mind.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"'Big guy'?",
        "response":"It felt like a 'big guy' moment.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No? What happened, big guy?",
        "response":"'Big guy'?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Which one?",
        "response":"...The second guy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Which one?",
        "response":"...The second guy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I got fired.",
        "response":"Oh!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hard to tell, I was naked.",
        "response":"No, I don't think this was your shot. I mean, I don't even think you just get oneshot. I really believe big things are gonna happen for you, I do! You've gotta just keepthinking about the day that some kid is gonna run up to his friends and go 'I got thepart! I got the part! I'm gonna be Joey Tribbiani's ass!'.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I don't think this was your shot. I mean, I don't even think you just get oneshot. I really believe big things are gonna happen for you, I do! You've gotta just keepthinking about the day that some kid is gonna run up to his friends and go 'I got thepart! I got the part! I'm gonna be Joey Tribbiani's ass!'.",
        "response":"Yeah? That's so nice!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, they said I acted too much with it. I told everybody about this! Noweverybody's gonna go to the theatre, expecting to see me, and-",
        "response":"Oh, Joey, you know what, no-one is gonna be able to tell.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Something so sweet and... disturbing about that.",
        "response":"Y'know, I've done nothing but crappy plays for six years. And I finally get my shot,and I blow it!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh!",
        "response":"Yeah, they said I acted too much with it. I told everybody about this! Noweverybody's gonna go to the theatre, expecting to see me, and-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh!",
        "response":"Really? Just casually strewn about in that reckless haphazard manner?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, Joey, you know what, no-one is gonna be able to tell.",
        "response":"My mom will.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, Mon, you-you gonna leave your shoes out here?",
        "response":"Uh-huh!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"My mom will.",
        "response":"Something so sweet and... disturbing about that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh, this is cool...it says in some parts of the world, people actually eat theplacenta. [Joey grimaces]",
        "response":"And, we're done with the yogurt. [sets yogurt down on table]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really? Just casually strewn about in that reckless haphazard manner?",
        "response":"Doesn't matter, I'll get 'em tomorrow. Or not. Whenever.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, that's our friend Tanya.",
        "response":"ROSS [surprised, chuckling nervously]: Of course it's your friend Tanya. [looks upfrightenedly]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, I got the results of the amnio today.",
        "response":"ROSS [making flinging gestures with hands]: Oh, tell me, tell me, is everything, uhh....?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And, we're done with the yogurt. [sets yogurt down on table]",
        "response":"[softly] Sorry. [Camera pans back to Monica, still on phone]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"ROSS [making flinging gestures with hands]: Oh, tell me, tell me, is everything, uhh....?",
        "response":"Totally and completely healthy!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh great! Is it vegetarian, 'cause Susan doesn't eat meat.",
        "response":"ROSS [pauses]: I'm pretty sure that it is...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh!",
        "response":"Really? Just casually strewn about in that reckless haphazard manner?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"ROSS [pauses]: I'm pretty sure that it is...",
        "response":"So, I got the results of the amnio today.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Don't you want to know about the sex?",
        "response":"ROSS [chuckles nervously]: The sex? [chuckles] Um, I'm having enough trouble with theimage of you and Susan together, when you throw in Tanya [miming washing hair, that's thebest I could think of], yaw...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"ROSS [chuckles nervously]: The sex? [chuckles] Um, I'm having enough trouble with theimage of you and Susan together, when you throw in Tanya [miming washing hair, that's thebest I could think of], yaw...",
        "response":"The sex of the baby, Ross.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Do you want to know?",
        "response":"No, no, no, no, no, I don't want to know, absolutely not. I think, you know, I thinkyou should know until you look down there, and say, oop, there it is! [pauses] Or isn't...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"ROSS [surprised, chuckling nervously]: Of course it's your friend Tanya. [looks upfrightenedly]",
        "response":"Don't you want to know about the sex?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, you know the sex of the baby? Oh, oh oh oh!",
        "response":"Do you want to know?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, you know the sex of the baby? Oh, oh oh oh!",
        "response":"Do you want to know?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The sex of the baby, Ross.",
        "response":"Oh, you know the sex of the baby? Oh, oh oh oh!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, hello Ross!",
        "response":"Susan...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, we did, everything's A-OK!",
        "response":"Oh, that's so... [Susan hugs Carol, they giggle, Ross steps away] It really is...dowe know...?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, so it's just because it was my table, I have to buy a new one?",
        "response":"That's the rule.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What rule? There's no rule, if anything, you owe me a table!",
        "response":"How'd you get to that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's the rule.",
        "response":"What rule? There's no rule, if anything, you owe me a table!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's the rule.",
        "response":"What rule? There's no rule, if anything, you owe me a table!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, so, did you hear?",
        "response":"Yes, we did, everything's A-OK!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, so, did you hear?",
        "response":"Yes, we did, everything's A-OK!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Susan...",
        "response":"So, so, did you hear?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Susan...",
        "response":"So, so, did you hear?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I believe the piece of furniture was fine until your little breakfastadventure with Angela Delvecchio",
        "response":"You knew about that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I believe the piece of furniture was fine until your little breakfastadventure with Angela Delvecchio",
        "response":"You knew about that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How'd you get to that?",
        "response":"Well, I believe the piece of furniture was fine until your little breakfastadventure with Angela Delvecchio",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How'd you get to that?",
        "response":"Well, I believe the piece of furniture was fine until your little breakfastadventure with Angela Delvecchio",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, let's just say the impressions you made in the butter left little to theimagination.",
        "response":"Ok, ok, How about if we split it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, let's just say the impressions you made in the butter left little to theimagination.",
        "response":"Ok, ok, How about if we split it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You knew about that?",
        "response":"Well, let's just say the impressions you made in the butter left little to theimagination.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You knew about that?",
        "response":"Well, let's just say the impressions you made in the butter left little to theimagination.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What rule? There's no rule, if anything, you owe me a table!",
        "response":"How'd you get to that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why not?",
        "response":"Well, it's a big--it's a pretty big commitment, I mean, what if one of us wantsto move out?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, ok, How about if we split it?",
        "response":"What do you mean, like, buy it together?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, ok, How about if we split it?",
        "response":"What do you mean, like, buy it together?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah",
        "response":"You think we're ready for something like that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah",
        "response":"You think we're ready for something like that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You think we're ready for something like that?",
        "response":"Why not?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You think we're ready for something like that?",
        "response":"Why not?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What do you mean, like, buy it together?",
        "response":"Yeah",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What do you mean, like, buy it together?",
        "response":"Yeah",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, it's a big--it's a pretty big commitment, I mean, what if one of us wantsto move out?",
        "response":"Why, are you moving out?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, it's a big--it's a pretty big commitment, I mean, what if one of us wantsto move out?",
        "response":"Why, are you moving out?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You'd tell me if you were moving out right",
        "response":"Yeah, yeah, it's just that with my last roommate Kip",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You'd tell me if you were moving out right",
        "response":"Yeah, yeah, it's just that with my last roommate Kip",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why not?",
        "response":"Well, it's a big--it's a pretty big commitment, I mean, what if one of us wantsto move out?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm not moving out.",
        "response":"You'd tell me if you were moving out right",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm not moving out.",
        "response":"You'd tell me if you were moving out right",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why, are you moving out?",
        "response":"I'm not moving out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why, are you moving out?",
        "response":"I'm not moving out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's just that we bought a hibachi together, and then he ran off and gotmarried, and things got pretty ugly",
        "response":"Well, let me ask you something, was Kip a better roommate than me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's just that we bought a hibachi together, and then he ran off and gotmarried, and things got pretty ugly",
        "response":"Well, let me ask you something, was Kip a better roommate than me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Aw, I know all about Kip!",
        "response":"It's just that we bought a hibachi together, and then he ran off and gotmarried, and things got pretty ugly",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Aw, I know all about Kip!",
        "response":"It's just that we bought a hibachi together, and then he ran off and gotmarried, and things got pretty ugly",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, let me ask you something, was Kip a better roommate than me?",
        "response":"Aw, don't do that",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, Paolo, hi, what are you doing here?",
        "response":"Uh, Racquela tell me you massage, eh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, yeah, it's just that with my last roommate Kip",
        "response":"Aw, I know all about Kip!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, yeah, it's just that with my last roommate Kip",
        "response":"Aw, I know all about Kip!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Buon Giorno, Bella Phoebe!",
        "response":"Oh, Paolo, hi, what are you doing here?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, I am, uh, being naked?",
        "response":"Um, that's really your decision, I mean, some people prefer, you know, to takeoff...oh whoops! You're being naked!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wha, heh, how could you know, I don't even know!",
        "response":"Carol called me to thank me for the lasagna, I asked, she told me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, okay, I don't know what you just said, so let's get started.",
        "response":"Uh, I am, uh, being naked?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Paolo speaks Italian]",
        "response":"Oh, okay, I don't know what you just said, so let's get started.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, Paolo, hi, what are you doing here?",
        "response":"Uh, Racquela tell me you massage, eh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, Racquela tell me you massage, eh?",
        "response":"Well, Racquela's right, yeah!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And Monica knows...",
        "response":"Wha, heh, how could you know, I don't even know!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, Racquela's right, yeah!",
        "response":"[Paolo speaks Italian]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Fine!",
        "response":"Phoebe, what's the matter?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah, I'm sure. [Flashback resumes while Phoebe does voice-over] And all of asudden his hands weren't the problem anymore. [Flashback continues: Paolo rolls over,Phoebe looks down, then quickly looks up, bites lip, shakes her head]",
        "response":"Was it...?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You have to tell her! You have to tell her! It's your moral obligation, as a friend,as a woman, I think it's a feminist issue! Guys? Guys? [waiting for guys to chime in]",
        "response":"Oh, yeah, you have to tell her.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So what are you gonna do?",
        "response":"You have to tell her! You have to tell her! It's your moral obligation, as a friend,as a woman, I think it's a feminist issue! Guys? Guys? [waiting for guys to chime in]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebe, what's the matter?",
        "response":"Nothing, I'm sorry, I'm just, I'm out of sorts.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right, you know Paolo?",
        "response":"I'm familiar with his work, yes...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm familiar with his work, yes...",
        "response":"Well, he made a move on me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[all talking indistinctly, high-fiving]",
        "response":"Thanks Rach.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The actress!",
        "response":"[all talking indistinctly, high-fiving]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Was it...?",
        "response":"Oh, boy scouts could have camped under there.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So what, like people are gonna come in and think, &quot;Uh-oh, I'm outsideagain?&quot; Of course!",
        "response":"CHANDLER [gesturing towards another table]: What about the birds?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"CHANDLER [gesturing towards another table]: What about the birds?",
        "response":"I don't know, birds just don't say, &quot;Hello, sit here, eat something&quot;",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's patio furniture!",
        "response":"So what, like people are gonna come in and think, &quot;Uh-oh, I'm outsideagain?&quot; Of course!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right, how about the ladybugs?",
        "response":"Oh, so, forget about the birds, but big red insects suggest fine dining!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right, how about the ladybugs?",
        "response":"Oh, so, forget about the birds, but big red insects suggest fine dining!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know, birds just don't say, &quot;Hello, sit here, eat something&quot;",
        "response":"You pick one.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Will you pick one, just pick one! Here, how about that one? [points to a table]",
        "response":"That's patio furniture!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You pick one.",
        "response":"All right, how about the ladybugs?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You pick one.",
        "response":"All right, how about the ladybugs?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Fine, you want to get the birds, get the birds!",
        "response":"Not like that, I won't! [pauses] Kip would have liked the birds! [Joey turns andgives Chandler a dirty look]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, these aren't all my suitcases. [picks up small blue suitcase and shows toPhoebe] This one's Paolo's.",
        "response":"Um, um, Rachel can we talk for a sec?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, so, forget about the birds, but big red insects suggest fine dining!",
        "response":"Fine, you want to get the birds, get the birds!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, so, forget about the birds, but big red insects suggest fine dining!",
        "response":"Fine, you want to get the birds, get the birds!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you moving out?",
        "response":"No, these aren't all my suitcases. [picks up small blue suitcase and shows toPhoebe] This one's Paolo's.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you moving out?",
        "response":"No, these aren't all my suitcases. [picks up small blue suitcase and shows toPhoebe] This one's Paolo's.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi Pheebs!",
        "response":"Are you moving out?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi Pheebs!",
        "response":"Are you moving out?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey!",
        "response":"Hi Pheebs!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, um, [clears throat] we haven't known each other for that long a time, and, um,there are three things that you should know about me. One, my friends are the mostimportant thing in my life, two, I never lie, and three, I make the best oatmeal raisincookies in the world. [Phoebe opens a tin and offers Rachel a cookie]",
        "response":"RACHEL [taking cookie]: Ok, thanks Pheebs [takes bite of cookie, overwhelmed] Oh my God,",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, Pheebs, Pheebs...",
        "response":"Ok, um, [clears throat] we haven't known each other for that long a time, and, um,there are three things that you should know about me. One, my friends are the mostimportant thing in my life, two, I never lie, and three, I make the best oatmeal raisincookies in the world. [Phoebe opens a tin and offers Rachel a cookie]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, these aren't all my suitcases. [picks up small blue suitcase and shows toPhoebe] This one's Paolo's.",
        "response":"Um, um, Rachel can we talk for a sec?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, um, Rachel can we talk for a sec?",
        "response":"Well, sure...just a sec, though, 'cause Paolo's on his way over.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, um, Rachel can we talk for a sec?",
        "response":"Well, sure...just a sec, though, 'cause Paolo's on his way over.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, sure...just a sec, though, 'cause Paolo's on his way over.",
        "response":"Oh! [sits down] Ok, um, ok, um,",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, sure...just a sec, though, 'cause Paolo's on his way over.",
        "response":"Oh! [sits down] Ok, um, ok, um,",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh! [sits down] Ok, um, ok, um,",
        "response":"Oh, Pheebs, Pheebs...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh! [sits down] Ok, um, ok, um,",
        "response":"Oh, Pheebs, Pheebs...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I don't make them a lot because I don't think it's fair to the other cookies",
        "response":"All right, well, you're right, these are the best oatmeal cookies I've ever had.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I don't make them a lot because I don't think it's fair to the other cookies",
        "response":"All right, well, you're right, these are the best oatmeal cookies I've ever had.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why have I never tasted these before?",
        "response":"Oh, I don't make them a lot because I don't think it's fair to the other cookies",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why have I never tasted these before?",
        "response":"Oh, I don't make them a lot because I don't think it's fair to the other cookies",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right, well, you're right, these are the best oatmeal cookies I've ever had.",
        "response":"Which proves that I never lie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right, well, you're right, these are the best oatmeal cookies I've ever had.",
        "response":"Which proves that I never lie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"RACHEL [taking cookie]: Ok, thanks Pheebs [takes bite of cookie, overwhelmed] Oh my God,",
        "response":"I know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Which proves that I never lie.",
        "response":"I guess you don't.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know.",
        "response":"Why have I never tasted these before?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I need some milk.",
        "response":"Ok, I've got milk [takes thermos from her bag and starts to pour a cup] Here yougo... [Rachel drinks straight from thermos] Oh![Rachel finishes thermos] Better?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I need some milk.",
        "response":"Ok, I've got milk [takes thermos from her bag and starts to pour a cup] Here yougo... [Rachel drinks straight from thermos] Oh![Rachel finishes thermos] Better?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Who cares, we'll eat at the sink! Come on, let's play!",
        "response":"Heads up Ross! [Monica scores on Chandler and Joey] Score! [points at Chandler]You suck!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So how does this work, you going to balance the plates on these little guys'heads?",
        "response":"Who cares, we'll eat at the sink! Come on, let's play!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, what do you think?",
        "response":"I think It's the most beautiful table I've ever seen.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I think It's the most beautiful table I've ever seen.",
        "response":"I know!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Which proves that I never lie.",
        "response":"I guess you don't.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I guess you don't.",
        "response":"Paolo made a pass at me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you okay?",
        "response":"I need some milk.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, I've got milk [takes thermos from her bag and starts to pour a cup] Here yougo... [Rachel drinks straight from thermos] Oh![Rachel finishes thermos] Better?",
        "response":"No...oh!, I feel so stupid! Oh, I think about the other day with you guys and Iwas all &quot;Oh, Paolo, he's so great, he makes me feel so...&quot; Oh, God, I'm soembarrassed!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, I've got milk [takes thermos from her bag and starts to pour a cup] Here yougo... [Rachel drinks straight from thermos] Oh![Rachel finishes thermos] Better?",
        "response":"No...oh!, I feel so stupid! Oh, I think about the other day with you guys and Iwas all &quot;Oh, Paolo, he's so great, he makes me feel so...&quot; Oh, God, I'm soembarrassed!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No...oh!, I feel so stupid! Oh, I think about the other day with you guys and Iwas all &quot;Oh, Paolo, he's so great, he makes me feel so...&quot; Oh, God, I'm soembarrassed!",
        "response":"I'm so embarrassed, I'm the one he hit on!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, wait, oh, what are we sorry about?",
        "response":"I don't know...right, he's the pig!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know...right, he's the pig!",
        "response":"Such a pig!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know...right, he's the pig!",
        "response":"Such a pig!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, God, he's such a pig,",
        "response":"Oh he's like a...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Such a pig!",
        "response":"Oh, God, he's such a pig,",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Such a pig!",
        "response":"Oh, God, he's such a pig,",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh he's like a...",
        "response":"He's like a big disgusting...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh he's like a...",
        "response":"He's like a big disgusting...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, God, he's such a pig,",
        "response":"Oh he's like a...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He's like a big disgusting...",
        "response":"...like a...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He's like a big disgusting...",
        "response":"...like a...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...pig...pig man!",
        "response":"Yes, good! Ok...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...pig...pig man!",
        "response":"Yes, good! Ok...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...like a...",
        "response":"...pig...pig man!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...like a...",
        "response":"...pig...pig man!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[voice wavers] Oh, but he was my pig man...how did I not see this?",
        "response":"[raises hand] Oh! I know! [Rachel startled] It's because... he's gorgeous, andhe's charming, and when he looks at you...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[voice wavers] Oh, but he was my pig man...how did I not see this?",
        "response":"[raises hand] Oh! I know! [Rachel startled] It's because... he's gorgeous, andhe's charming, and when he looks at you...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[raises hand] Oh! I know! [Rachel startled] It's because... he's gorgeous, andhe's charming, and when he looks at you...",
        "response":"Ok, Ok, Pheebs...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[raises hand] Oh! I know! [Rachel startled] It's because... he's gorgeous, andhe's charming, and when he looks at you...",
        "response":"Ok, Ok, Pheebs...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, good! Ok...",
        "response":"[voice wavers] Oh, but he was my pig man...how did I not see this?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, good! Ok...",
        "response":"[voice wavers] Oh, but he was my pig man...how did I not see this?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, Ok, Pheebs...",
        "response":"The end.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, Ok, Pheebs...",
        "response":"The end.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The end.",
        "response":"Oh, God...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Paolo, I-I just want to tell you and I think I speak for everyone when I say...[shuts door in his face and walks away]",
        "response":"Oh, just look at her... [girls move toward Rachel on the balcony]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, just look at her... [girls move toward Rachel on the balcony]",
        "response":"Oh you guys, I-I really think just one of us should go out there so she's notoverwhelmed...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Should I not have told you?",
        "response":"No, no, trust, me, it's, it's, it's much better that I know. Uh, I just liked itbetter before it was better...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh you guys, I-I really think just one of us should go out there so she's notoverwhelmed...",
        "response":"Oh, you're right.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Come on, two on one.",
        "response":"What are you still doing here? She just broke up with the guy, it's time for youto swoop in!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What are you still doing here? She just broke up with the guy, it's time for youto swoop in!",
        "response":"What, now?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, God...",
        "response":"Should I not have told you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, God...",
        "response":"Should I not have told you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The end.",
        "response":"Oh, God...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh, I've been better...",
        "response":"Come here. [he hugs Rachel] Listen, you deserve so much better than him...you know,I mean, you, you, you should be with a guy who knows what he has when he has you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[pulls Monica back] ...and I really think it should be me.",
        "response":"<b>[Scene: balcony where Ross has climbed through the window]</b>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, you're right.",
        "response":"[pulls Monica back] ...and I really think it should be me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<b>[Scene: balcony where Ross has climbed through the window]</b>",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You all right?",
        "response":"Ooh, I've been better...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You all right?",
        "response":"Ooh, I've been better...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"You all right?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"You all right?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh, I've been better...",
        "response":"Come here. [he hugs Rachel] Listen, you deserve so much better than him...you know,I mean, you, you, you should be with a guy who knows what he has when he has you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Come here. [he hugs Rachel] Listen, you deserve so much better than him...you know,I mean, you, you, you should be with a guy who knows what he has when he has you.",
        "response":"Oh, Ross...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Come here. [he hugs Rachel] Listen, you deserve so much better than him...you know,I mean, you, you, you should be with a guy who knows what he has when he has you.",
        "response":"Oh, Ross...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I am so sick of guys. I don't want to look at another guy, I don't' want to thinkabout another guy, I don't even want to be near another guy. [Ross crosses arms]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I am so sick of guys. I don't want to look at another guy, I don't' want to thinkabout another guy, I don't even want to be near another guy. [Ross crosses arms]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I am so sick of guys. I don't want to look at another guy, I don't' want to thinkabout another guy, I don't even want to be near another guy. [Ross crosses arms]",
        "response":"Huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I am so sick of guys. I don't want to look at another guy, I don't' want to thinkabout another guy, I don't even want to be near another guy. [Ross crosses arms]",
        "response":"Huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, Ross...",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, Ross...",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"See, Rach, uh, see, I don't think that swearing off guys altogether is the answer. Ireally don't. I think that what you need is to develop a more sophisticated screeningprocess.",
        "response":"No. I just need to be by myself for a while, you know? I just got to figure outwhat I want",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. I just need to be by myself for a while, you know? I just got to figure outwhat I want",
        "response":"Uh, no, no, see, because not...not all guys are going to be a Paolo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh Ross, you're so great!",
        "response":"Ohhhh [hugs her &amp; sighs]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You ok?",
        "response":"...medium...hmm...any cookies left?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You ok?",
        "response":"...medium...hmm...any cookies left?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...medium...hmm...any cookies left?",
        "response":"Yep!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh.",
        "response":"Oh Ross, you're so great!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh.",
        "response":"Oh Ross, you're so great!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh...",
        "response":"You ok?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. I just need to be by myself for a while, you know? I just got to figure outwhat I want",
        "response":"Uh, no, no, see, because not...not all guys are going to be a Paolo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, no, no, see, because not...not all guys are going to be a Paolo.",
        "response":"No, I know, I know, and I'm sure your little boy is not going to grow up to beone.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wha-I'm having, I'm having a boy! [babbling] Huh, am I having a boy?",
        "response":"Yes, you're having a boy! [Monica runs over and hugs Ross]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I know, I know, and I'm sure your little boy is not going to grow up to beone.",
        "response":"ROSS [astonished]: What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh...no. No, no, in fact, you're not having a boy.",
        "response":"Wha-I'm having, I'm having a boy! [babbling] Huh, am I having a boy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I-I'm, I'm having a boy?",
        "response":"Uh...no. No, no, in fact, you're not having a boy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I-I'm, I'm having a boy?",
        "response":"Uh...no. No, no, in fact, you're not having a boy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"ROSS [astonished]: What?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I-I'm, I'm having a boy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I am telling you, years from now, schoolchildren will study it as one of thegreatest first dates of all time. It was unbelievable! We could totally be ourselves, wedidn't have to play any games...",
        "response":"So have you called her yet?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah--get out!",
        "response":"You guys are always hanging out in my apartment! Come on, I'll only use my lefthand, huh? Come on, wussies! [Joey and Chandler pick her up] All right, ok, I gotta go.I'm going, [they throw her out] and I'm gone.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You guys are always hanging out in my apartment! Come on, I'll only use my lefthand, huh? Come on, wussies! [Joey and Chandler pick her up] All right, ok, I gotta go.I'm going, [they throw her out] and I'm gone.",
        "response":"One more game?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know, you don't wanna mess with corn nuts. They're craaazy.",
        "response":"Oh my God. You guys! You gotta come see this! There's somecreep out there with a telescope!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So have you called her yet?",
        "response":"Let her know I like her? What are you, insane? It's the next day! How needy do I want to seem?  I'm right, right?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God. You guys! You gotta come see this! There's somecreep out there with a telescope!",
        "response":"I can't believe it! He's looking right at us!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"JOEY &amp; CHANDLER: Shut-out!",
        "response":"Where are you guys going? Come on, one more game!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, you're having a boy! [Monica runs over and hugs Ross]",
        "response":"I'm having a boy! Oh, I'm having a boy!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes! And that would be a shut-down!",
        "response":"JOEY &amp; CHANDLER: Shut-out!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, uh, why didn't you say anything?",
        "response":"Oh, no no no no. Last time I left a spontaneous message I ended up using thephrase 'Yes indeedy-o'.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, well, does he look upset? Does he look like he was just told to shoveanything?",
        "response":"No, no actually, he's smiling.. and... Oh my God, don't do that!!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, well, does he look upset? Does he look like he was just told to shoveanything?",
        "response":"No, no actually, he's smiling.. and... Oh my God, don't do that!!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, they're just talking...",
        "response":"Yeah, well, does he look upset? Does he look like he was just told to shoveanything?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, they're just talking...",
        "response":"Yeah, well, does he look upset? Does he look like he was just told to shoveanything?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, interestingly enough her leaf blower picked up.",
        "response":"So, uh, why didn't you say anything?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Which, by the way, is the real San Francisco treat.  I got her machine.",
        "response":"Her answer machine?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Her answer machine?",
        "response":"No, interestingly enough her leaf blower picked up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, okay, what's going on?",
        "response":"Okay, they're just talking...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's nice... now, was that before or after you told him to stop calling, stopsending you flowers and to generally leave you alone, hmm?",
        "response":"Right,.. well,.. we never actually got to that... Oh, it was just so nice to seehim again, y'know? It was comfortable, it was familiar... it was just nice!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Then we took a walk down to Bendall's, and I told him not to, but he got me alittle bottle of Chanel...",
        "response":"That's nice... now, was that before or after you told him to stop calling, stopsending you flowers and to generally leave you alone, hmm?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Y'know, it was, uh.. it was actually really great. He took me to lunch at theRussian Tea Room, and I had that chicken, where y'know you poke it and all the buttersquirts out...",
        "response":"Not a good day for birds...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Not a good day for birds...",
        "response":"Then we took a walk down to Bendall's, and I told him not to, but he got me alittle bottle of Chanel...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no actually, he's smiling.. and... Oh my God, don't do that!!",
        "response":"What? What? What?!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no actually, he's smiling.. and... Oh my God, don't do that!!",
        "response":"What? What? What?!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? What? What?!",
        "response":"That man across the street just kicked that pigeon!  Oh!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And basically, that's how a bill becomes a law.",
        "response":"Oh!... Right!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh!... Right!",
        "response":"Hey Rach!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's nice... now, was that before or after you told him to stop calling, stopsending you flowers and to generally leave you alone, hmm?",
        "response":"Right,.. well,.. we never actually got to that... Oh, it was just so nice to seehim again, y'know? It was comfortable, it was familiar... it was just nice!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right,.. well,.. we never actually got to that... Oh, it was just so nice to seehim again, y'know? It was comfortable, it was familiar... it was just nice!",
        "response":"That's, that's nice twice!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, but it was different with him today! And he wasn't, like, Orthodontist Guy,y'know? I mean, we had fun! Is there anything wrong with that?",
        "response":"Yes!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right. All right all right all right all right, I know it's stupid! I will gosee him this afternoon, and I will just put an end to it!",
        "response":"<b></b>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why?",
        "response":"I have my reasons.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow... Wow!",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<b></b>",
        "response":"Wow... Wow!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes!",
        "response":"Why?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes!",
        "response":"Why?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What was with the dishes?",
        "response":"Oh, uh.. I want her to think I might be in a restaurant.. y'know? I might havesome kind of life, like I haven't been sitting around here honing for the past few hours.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, Danielle! I wasn't expecting themachine... Give me a call when you get a chance.  Bye bye. Oh God!",
        "response":"THAT's what you've been working on for the past two hours?!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"THAT's what you've been working on for the past two hours?!",
        "response":"Hey, I've been honing!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nooo, it wasn't.",
        "response":"Ooh, and it's so nice having this little sink here...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm not crazy, right? I mean, it was never like that.",
        "response":"Nooo, it wasn't.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm not crazy, right? I mean, it was never like that.",
        "response":"Nooo, it wasn't.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"I'm not crazy, right? I mean, it was never like that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"I'm not crazy, right? I mean, it was never like that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, I've been honing!",
        "response":"What was with the dishes?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Great, now he's waving back.",
        "response":"Man, we gotta do something about that guy. This morning, I caught him looking intoour apartment. It creeps me out! I feel like I can't do stuff!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Man, we gotta do something about that guy. This morning, I caught him looking intoour apartment. It creeps me out! I feel like I can't do stuff!",
        "response":"What kinda stuff..?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Man, we gotta do something about that guy. This morning, I caught him looking intoour apartment. It creeps me out! I feel like I can't do stuff!",
        "response":"What kinda stuff..?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What kinda stuff..?",
        "response":"Will you grow up? I'm not talking about sexy stuff, but, like, when I'm cookingnaked.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Will you grow up? I'm not talking about sexy stuff, but, like, when I'm cookingnaked.",
        "response":"You cook naked?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look look! He's doing it again, the guy with the telescope!",
        "response":"Oh my God!  Go away!  Stop looking in here!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God!  Go away!  Stop looking in here!",
        "response":"Great, now he's waving back.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You cook naked?",
        "response":"Yeah, toast, oatmeal... nothing that spatters.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, way, way better than Mindy.",
        "response":"No, not that, I mean, what about you and Mindy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, way, way better than Mindy.",
        "response":"No, not that, I mean, what about you and Mindy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, what about Mindy?",
        "response":"Oh, way, way better than Mindy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, what about Mindy?",
        "response":"Oh, way, way better than Mindy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, it's just... Oh, Barry, this was not good.",
        "response":"No, it was. It was very very good.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, it's just... Oh, Barry, this was not good.",
        "response":"No, it was. It was very very good.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's the matter?",
        "response":"Oh, it's just... Oh, Barry, this was not good.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, it was. It was very very good.",
        "response":"Well, what about Mindy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, it was. It was very very good.",
        "response":"Well, what about Mindy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, Barry..! Come on, this is all way too..",
        "response":"We can, we can go to Aruba! When I went there on what would have been ourhoneymoon, it was, uh... it was really nice. You would've liked it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, Barry..! Come on, this is all way too..",
        "response":"We can, we can go to Aruba! When I went there on what would have been ourhoneymoon, it was, uh... it was really nice. You would've liked it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We can, we can go to Aruba! When I went there on what would have been ourhoneymoon, it was, uh... it was really nice. You would've liked it.",
        "response":"I had a bra.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.. uh, but for future reference, that thing in your hand can also be used as aphone.",
        "response":"Yes, it's working! Why isn't she calling me back?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Can I use your phone?",
        "response":"Yeah.. uh, but for future reference, that thing in your hand can also be used as aphone.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, not that, I mean, what about you and Mindy?",
        "response":"Well, if you want, I'll just- I'll just break it off with her.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, not that, I mean, what about you and Mindy?",
        "response":"Well, if you want, I'll just- I'll just break it off with her.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, if you want, I'll just- I'll just break it off with her.",
        "response":"No. No no no no, no. I mean, don't do that. Not, I mean not for me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thanks, Bernice.  Let's go away this weekend.",
        "response":"Oh, Barry..! Come on, this is all way too..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Y'see, this is where you'd use that 'hello' word we talked about.",
        "response":"I'm not gonna talk to her, she obviously got my message and is choosing not tocall me. Now I'm needy and snubbed. God, I miss just being needy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Pretty well, actually...",
        "response":"Uh, Rach... how come you have dental floss in your hair?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"She answered.",
        "response":"Y'see, this is where you'd use that 'hello' word we talked about.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, Rach... how come you have dental floss in your hair?",
        "response":"Oh, do I?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, Rach... how come you have dental floss in your hair?",
        "response":"Oh, do I?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Y'don't think that makes me seem a little...",
        "response":"...desperate, needy, pathetic?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...desperate, needy, pathetic?",
        "response":"Ah, you obviously saw my personal ad.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ah, you obviously saw my personal ad.",
        "response":"How many beeps?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How many beeps?",
        "response":"She answered.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What, uh... what were you thinking?",
        "response":"I don't know! I mean, we still care about each other. There's a history there.'S'like you and Carol.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know! I mean, we still care about each other. There's a history there.'S'like you and Carol.",
        "response":"No! No no, it is nothing like me and Carol!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"....We ended up having sex in his chair.",
        "response":"You had SEX in his CHAIR?!... I said that a little too loudly, didn't I?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sex in his chair.",
        "response":"What, uh... what were you thinking?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh huh.",
        "response":"....We ended up having sex in his chair.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh huh.",
        "response":"....We ended up having sex in his chair.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You- you had what?",
        "response":"Sex in his chair.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, do I?",
        "response":"Uh huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, do I?",
        "response":"Uh huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello? Mindy! Hi! Hey, how are you? Yes, yes, I've heard, congratulations, that isso great. Really? Oh. Okay. Okay, well I'm working tomorrow, but if you want you can, youcan, you can come by and... okay... great... great... all right, so I'll, so I'll see youtomorrow! Okay.. okay... bye.  Oh God. Oh God. Oh God.",
        "response":"So how's Mindy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello? Mindy! Hi! Hey, how are you? Yes, yes, I've heard, congratulations, that isso great. Really? Oh. Okay. Okay, well I'm working tomorrow, but if you want you can, youcan, you can come by and... okay... great... great... all right, so I'll, so I'll see youtomorrow! Okay.. okay... bye.  Oh God. Oh God. Oh God.",
        "response":"So how's Mindy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello? Hello?",
        "response":"Hello? Mindy! Hi! Hey, how are you? Yes, yes, I've heard, congratulations, that isso great. Really? Oh. Okay. Okay, well I'm working tomorrow, but if you want you can, youcan, you can come by and... okay... great... great... all right, so I'll, so I'll see youtomorrow! Okay.. okay... bye.  Oh God. Oh God. Oh God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Where are you going?",
        "response":"I just have to go, all right? Do I need a reason? Huh? I mean I have thingsto do with my life, I have a jam packed schedule, and I am late- for keeping up with it.Okay?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So how's Mindy?",
        "response":"Oh, she wants to see me tomorrow...Oh, she sounded really weird, I gotta callBarry...  Hi, it's me, I just.. Mindy!! Mindy! Hi! No, I figured that's whereyou'd be!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No! No no, it is nothing like me and Carol!",
        "response":"Please. If she said to you, &quot;Ross, I want you on this couch, right here,right now&quot;, what would you say?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know! I mean, we still care about each other. There's a history there.'S'like you and Carol.",
        "response":"No! No no, it is nothing like me and Carol!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's, it's, it's, uh, a totally diferent situation! It's, it's apples and oranges,it's, it's orthodontists and lesbi- I gotta go.",
        "response":"Where are you going?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Get down?",
        "response":"...And boogie!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Relax. Y'know, she may not even know.",
        "response":"Please. I haven't heard from her in seven months, and now she calls me? I mean,what else is it about? Oh! She was my best friend, you guys! We went to camp together...she taught me how to kiss..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Please. I haven't heard from her in seven months, and now she calls me? I mean,what else is it about? Oh! She was my best friend, you guys! We went to camp together...she taught me how to kiss..",
        "response":"Yeah?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thanks, but I gotta go to work and get my eyes scratched out by Mindy.",
        "response":"Relax. Y'know, she may not even know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...And boogie!",
        "response":"Thanks, but I gotta go to work and get my eyes scratched out by Mindy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And now, y'know, I'm like... I'm like the other woman! I feel so..",
        "response":"..Naughty!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And now, y'know, I'm like... I'm like the other woman! I feel so..",
        "response":"..Naughty!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah?",
        "response":"And now, y'know, I'm like... I'm like the other woman! I feel so..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah?",
        "response":"And now, y'know, I'm like... I'm like the other woman! I feel so..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"..Naughty!",
        "response":"Right, I'll see you guys later...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right, I'll see you guys later...",
        "response":"Oh, hold up, I'll walk out with you. Now, Rach, when she taught you to kiss, youwere at camp, and.. were you wearing any kinda little uniform, or-  That's fine, yeah...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why don't you just take it with you?",
        "response":"Hey, we haven't been on a second date, she needs to hear me pee?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why don't you just take it with you?",
        "response":"Hey, we haven't been on a second date, she needs to hear me pee?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, we haven't been on a second date, she needs to hear me pee?",
        "response":"Why don't you just call her?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, we haven't been on a second date, she needs to hear me pee?",
        "response":"Why don't you just call her?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, I'm gonna go to the bathroom. Will you watch my phone?",
        "response":"Why don't you just take it with you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why don't you just call her?",
        "response":"I can't call her, I left a message! I have some pride.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why don't you just call her?",
        "response":"I can't call her, I left a message! I have some pride.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"..Naughty!",
        "response":"Right, I'll see you guys later...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No!  Danielle, hi! It's, uh, it's Chandler! I'm fine. Uh, listen, I don'tknow if you tried to call me, because, uh, idiot that I am, I accidentally shut off myphone. Oh, uh, okay, that's fine, that's great. Okay.  She's on the otherline, she's gonna call me back.  She's on the other line, she's gonnacall me back, she's on the other line, gonna call me back...",
        "response":"Don't you have to pee?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No!  Danielle, hi! It's, uh, it's Chandler! I'm fine. Uh, listen, I don'tknow if you tried to call me, because, uh, idiot that I am, I accidentally shut off myphone. Oh, uh, okay, that's fine, that's great. Okay.  She's on the otherline, she's gonna call me back.  She's on the other line, she's gonnacall me back, she's on the other line, gonna call me back...",
        "response":"Don't you have to pee?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Do you?",
        "response":"No!  Danielle, hi! It's, uh, it's Chandler! I'm fine. Uh, listen, I don'tknow if you tried to call me, because, uh, idiot that I am, I accidentally shut off myphone. Oh, uh, okay, that's fine, that's great. Okay.  She's on the otherline, she's gonna call me back.  She's on the other line, she's gonnacall me back, she's on the other line, gonna call me back...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Do you?",
        "response":"No!  Danielle, hi! It's, uh, it's Chandler! I'm fine. Uh, listen, I don'tknow if you tried to call me, because, uh, idiot that I am, I accidentally shut off myphone. Oh, uh, okay, that's fine, that's great. Okay.  She's on the otherline, she's gonna call me back.  She's on the other line, she's gonnacall me back, she's on the other line, gonna call me back...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't call her, I left a message! I have some pride.",
        "response":"Do you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't call her, I left a message! I have some pride.",
        "response":"Do you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Don't you have to pee?",
        "response":"'S'why I'm dancing...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, you.",
        "response":"Hey, you.... So, what's up?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mindy.",
        "response":"Hey, you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sure we should... So.",
        "response":"Now- I know things've been weird lately, but you're like my oldest friend in theworld.. except for maybe Laurie Schaffer, who I don't talk to anywhere, 'cause she's allbitter now that she lost the weight and it turns out she doesn't have a pretty face.....Okay, I'm just gonna ask you this once, and I want a straight answer.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sure we should... So.",
        "response":"Now- I know things've been weird lately, but you're like my oldest friend in theworld.. except for maybe Laurie Schaffer, who I don't talk to anywhere, 'cause she's allbitter now that she lost the weight and it turns out she doesn't have a pretty face.....Okay, I'm just gonna ask you this once, and I want a straight answer.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Now- I know things've been weird lately, but you're like my oldest friend in theworld.. except for maybe Laurie Schaffer, who I don't talk to anywhere, 'cause she's allbitter now that she lost the weight and it turns out she doesn't have a pretty face.....Okay, I'm just gonna ask you this once, and I want a straight answer.",
        "response":"Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Now- I know things've been weird lately, but you're like my oldest friend in theworld.. except for maybe Laurie Schaffer, who I don't talk to anywhere, 'cause she's allbitter now that she lost the weight and it turns out she doesn't have a pretty face.....Okay, I'm just gonna ask you this once, and I want a straight answer.",
        "response":"Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, you.... So, what's up?",
        "response":"Um.. we should really be sitting for this.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, you.... So, what's up?",
        "response":"Um.. we should really be sitting for this.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um.. we should really be sitting for this.",
        "response":"Sure we should... So.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um.. we should really be sitting for this.",
        "response":"Sure we should... So.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, you.",
        "response":"Hey, you.... So, what's up?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh that's so great!",
        "response":"Was that all you wanted to ask me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh that's so great!",
        "response":"Was that all you wanted to ask me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Was that all you wanted to ask me?",
        "response":"That's all!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Will you be my maid of honour?",
        "response":"Of course!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Will you be my maid of honour?",
        "response":"Of course!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.",
        "response":"Will you be my maid of honour?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.",
        "response":"Will you be my maid of honour?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Of course!",
        "response":"Oh that's so great!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Of course!",
        "response":"Oh that's so great!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh sure it is!",
        "response":"Oh no, it isn't! No! I think Barry is seeing someone in the city.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh sure it is!",
        "response":"Oh no, it isn't! No! I think Barry is seeing someone in the city.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Was that all you wanted to ask me?",
        "response":"That's all!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohhhh!!  ...What? What?",
        "response":"That's not all.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohhhh!!  ...What? What?",
        "response":"That's not all.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's all!",
        "response":"Ohhhh!!  ...What? What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's all!",
        "response":"Ohhhh!!  ...What? What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's not all.",
        "response":"Oh sure it is!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's not all.",
        "response":"Oh sure it is!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, ever since we announced the engagement, he's been acting really weird, andthen last night, he came home smelling like Chanel.",
        "response":"Really. Mindy, if it'll make you feel any better, when I was engagedto him he went through a whole weird thing too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, ever since we announced the engagement, he's been acting really weird, andthen last night, he came home smelling like Chanel.",
        "response":"Really. Mindy, if it'll make you feel any better, when I was engagedto him he went through a whole weird thing too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really. Mindy, if it'll make you feel any better, when I was engagedto him he went through a whole weird thing too.",
        "response":"Oh God! You see, that's what I was afraid of!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really. Mindy, if it'll make you feel any better, when I was engagedto him he went through a whole weird thing too.",
        "response":"Oh God! You see, that's what I was afraid of!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, what- what would make you think that?",
        "response":"Well, ever since we announced the engagement, he's been acting really weird, andthen last night, he came home smelling like Chanel.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, what- what would make you think that?",
        "response":"Well, ever since we announced the engagement, he's been acting really weird, andthen last night, he came home smelling like Chanel.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh no, it isn't! No! I think Barry is seeing someone in the city.",
        "response":"Um, what- what would make you think that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh no, it isn't! No! I think Barry is seeing someone in the city.",
        "response":"Um, what- what would make you think that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God! You see, that's what I was afraid of!",
        "response":"What? What's what you were afraid of?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know. I know, and when he proposed to me, everyone said &quot;Don't do it, he'sjust gonna do to you what he did to Rachel&quot;, and- now I feel so stupid.",
        "response":"Uh.. Oh, Mindy, you are so stupid. Oh, we are both so stupid.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know. I know, and when he proposed to me, everyone said &quot;Don't do it, he'sjust gonna do to you what he did to Rachel&quot;, and- now I feel so stupid.",
        "response":"Uh.. Oh, Mindy, you are so stupid. Oh, we are both so stupid.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I know. I know, and when he proposed to me, everyone said &quot;Don't do it, he'sjust gonna do to you what he did to Rachel&quot;, and- now I feel so stupid.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I know. I know, and when he proposed to me, everyone said &quot;Don't do it, he'sjust gonna do to you what he did to Rachel&quot;, and- now I feel so stupid.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? What's what you were afraid of?",
        "response":"Okay, okay... when Barry was engaged to you, he and I- kind of- had a little thingon the side.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? What's what you were afraid of?",
        "response":"Okay, okay... when Barry was engaged to you, he and I- kind of- had a little thingon the side.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, okay... when Barry was engaged to you, he and I- kind of- had a little thingon the side.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, okay... when Barry was engaged to you, he and I- kind of- had a little thingon the side.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God! You see, that's what I was afraid of!",
        "response":"What? What's what you were afraid of?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh.. Oh, Mindy, you are so stupid. Oh, we are both so stupid.",
        "response":"What do you mean?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh.. Oh, Mindy, you are so stupid. Oh, we are both so stupid.",
        "response":"What do you mean?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I am so sorry.",
        "response":"No me, I am so sorry...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What do you mean?",
        "response":"Smell familiar?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What do you mean?",
        "response":"Smell familiar?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh no.",
        "response":"Oh, I am so sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh no.",
        "response":"Oh, I am so sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Smell familiar?",
        "response":"Oh no.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Smell familiar?",
        "response":"Oh no.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, so listen, I went across the street and talked to the doorman- I got thepeeper's name! Can I use the phone?",
        "response":"Nngghhh!!!!!!!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I tried to call you from the coffee shop, and there was no answer.",
        "response":"I turned it off. Mother of God, I turned it off!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nngghhh!!!!!!!",
        "response":"Can I use your phone?  Yeah, the number for a Sidney Marks,please.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?!",
        "response":"I tried to call you from the coffee shop, and there was no answer.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?!",
        "response":"I tried to call you from the coffee shop, and there was no answer.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Four letters: &quot;Circle or hoop&quot;.",
        "response":"Ring dammit, ring!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, you know our phone's not working?",
        "response":"What?!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"&quot;Heating device&quot;.",
        "response":"Radiator.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ring dammit, ring!",
        "response":"Thanks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So she's a woman! So what?",
        "response":"Yeah. Yeah, so what?  Look, I live across the street, and I know all about you and your little telescope, and I don't appreciate it, okay? Yeah,I can see you right now! Hello! If I wanna walk around my apartment in my underwear, Ishouldn't have to feel like- Thank you, but... that's not really the point... The point isthat... mostly free weights, but occasionally..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So she's a woman! So what?",
        "response":"Yeah. Yeah, so what?  Look, I live across the street, and I know all about you and your little telescope, and I don't appreciate it, okay? Yeah,I can see you right now! Hello! If I wanna walk around my apartment in my underwear, Ishouldn't have to feel like- Thank you, but... that's not really the point... The point isthat... mostly free weights, but occasionally..",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. Yeah, so what?  Look, I live across the street, and I know all about you and your little telescope, and I don't appreciate it, okay? Yeah,I can see you right now! Hello! If I wanna walk around my apartment in my underwear, Ishouldn't have to feel like- Thank you, but... that's not really the point... The point isthat... mostly free weights, but occasionally..",
        "response":"Joey!!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. Yeah, so what?  Look, I live across the street, and I know all about you and your little telescope, and I don't appreciate it, okay? Yeah,I can see you right now! Hello! If I wanna walk around my apartment in my underwear, Ishouldn't have to feel like- Thank you, but... that's not really the point... The point isthat... mostly free weights, but occasionally..",
        "response":"Joey!!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey!!",
        "response":"Yeah, my neighbour... Yeah, the brunette...  She saysyou looked very pretty the other day in the green dress.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, is Sidney there? Oh, this is?  Sidney's a woman.",
        "response":"So she's a woman! So what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Radiator.",
        "response":"Five letters.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Radiator.",
        "response":"Five letters.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Five letters.",
        "response":"Rdtor.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, my neighbour... Yeah, the brunette...  She saysyou looked very pretty the other day in the green dress.",
        "response":"The green dress? Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, my neighbour... Yeah, the brunette...  She saysyou looked very pretty the other day in the green dress.",
        "response":"The green dress? Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey!!",
        "response":"Yeah, my neighbour... Yeah, the brunette...  She saysyou looked very pretty the other day in the green dress.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The green dress? Really?",
        "response":"Yeah, she said you looked like Ingrid Bergman that day.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The green dress? Really?",
        "response":"Yeah, she said you looked like Ingrid Bergman that day.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh... uh... what're'you... what're'you guys doing here?",
        "response":"Uh, we are here to break up with you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, she said you looked like Ingrid Bergman that day.",
        "response":"Nooo!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello, sweetheart.",
        "response":"Uh... uh... what're'you... what're'you guys doing here?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sure, sure. Come on...  ...in...",
        "response":"Hello, sweetheart.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Basically, we think you're a horrible human being, and bad things should happen toyou.",
        "response":"I'm sorry... I'm sorry, God, I am so sorry, I'm an idiot, I was weak, I couldn'thelp myself! Whatever I did, I only did because I love you so much!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry... I'm sorry, God, I am so sorry, I'm an idiot, I was weak, I couldn'thelp myself! Whatever I did, I only did because I love you so much!",
        "response":"Uh- which one of us are you talking to there, Barr?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Both of you?",
        "response":"Basically, we think you're a horrible human being, and bad things should happen toyou.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Even when we were having sex in that chair?",
        "response":"I swear, whatever I was doing, I was always thinking of you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh- which one of us are you talking to there, Barr?",
        "response":"....Mindy. Mindy, of course Mindy, it was always Mindy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh- which one of us are you talking to there, Barr?",
        "response":"....Mindy. Mindy, of course Mindy, it was always Mindy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"....Mindy. Mindy, of course Mindy, it was always Mindy.",
        "response":"Even when we were having sex in that chair?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"....Mindy. Mindy, of course Mindy, it was always Mindy.",
        "response":"Even when we were having sex in that chair?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, we are here to break up with you.",
        "response":"Both of you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay. Okay, we'll be here! Hating you! Did you see how he was sweating when hewalked out of there? Listen honey, if I'm hogging the ball too much you just jump right inthere and take a couple punches because I'm telling you, this feels GREAT.",
        "response":"Yeah... I'm pretty sure I'm still gonna marry him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sweetheart, just gimme- gimme another chance, okay, we'll start all overagain. We'll go back to Aruba.",
        "response":"Dr. Farber, we've got a bit of an emergency here...JasonCostalano is choking on his retainer.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Dr. Farber, we've got a bit of an emergency here...JasonCostalano is choking on his retainer.",
        "response":"Oh God...  I'll be right there, Bernice.  Look, please,please don't go anywhere, okay? I'll be- I'll be right back.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I swear, whatever I was doing, I was always thinking of you.",
        "response":"Please! During that second time you couldn't have picked her out of a lineup!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Please! During that second time you couldn't have picked her out of a lineup!",
        "response":"You did it twice?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Even when we were having sex in that chair?",
        "response":"I swear, whatever I was doing, I was always thinking of you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You did it twice?",
        "response":"Well, the first time didn't really count... I mean, y'know, 's'Barry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You did it twice?",
        "response":"Well, the first time didn't really count... I mean, y'know, 's'Barry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, the first time didn't really count... I mean, y'know, 's'Barry.",
        "response":"Okay...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What are you talking about?! Mindy, the guy is the devil! He's Satan in a smock!",
        "response":"Look, I know he's not perfect, but the truth is, at the end of the day, I stillreally wanna be Mrs. Dr. Barry Farber, DDS.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What are you talking about?! Mindy, the guy is the devil! He's Satan in a smock!",
        "response":"Look, I know he's not perfect, but the truth is, at the end of the day, I stillreally wanna be Mrs. Dr. Barry Farber, DDS.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I hope you can find some way to be happy for me. And I hope you'll still be my maidof honour...?",
        "response":"And I hope Barry doesn't kill you and eat you in Aruba.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah... I'm pretty sure I'm still gonna marry him.",
        "response":"What are you talking about?! Mindy, the guy is the devil! He's Satan in a smock!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah... I'm pretty sure I'm still gonna marry him.",
        "response":"What are you talking about?! Mindy, the guy is the devil! He's Satan in a smock!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, I know he's not perfect, but the truth is, at the end of the day, I stillreally wanna be Mrs. Dr. Barry Farber, DDS.",
        "response":"Oh God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, I know he's not perfect, but the truth is, at the end of the day, I stillreally wanna be Mrs. Dr. Barry Farber, DDS.",
        "response":"Oh God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God.",
        "response":"I hope you can find some way to be happy for me. And I hope you'll still be my maidof honour...?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God.",
        "response":"I hope you can find some way to be happy for me. And I hope you'll still be my maidof honour...?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What are you doing here?",
        "response":"Well, I've been calling you, but it turns out I had your number wrong. And whenI finally got the right one from Information, there was no answer. So I thought I'd justcome down here, and make sure you were okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Yeah! Y'know, ever since I ran out on Barry at the wedding, I have wonderedwhether I made the right choice. And now I know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Yeah! Y'know, ever since I ran out on Barry at the wedding, I have wonderedwhether I made the right choice. And now I know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah! Y'know, ever since I ran out on Barry at the wedding, I have wonderedwhether I made the right choice. And now I know.",
        "response":"Aww...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Danielle! Hi! Uh- everybody, this is Danielle, Danielle, everybody.",
        "response":"Hi. Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi. Hi.",
        "response":"What are you doing here?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You okay?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I've been calling you, but it turns out I had your number wrong. And whenI finally got the right one from Information, there was no answer. So I thought I'd justcome down here, and make sure you were okay.",
        "response":"...I'm, I'm okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I've been calling you, but it turns out I had your number wrong. And whenI finally got the right one from Information, there was no answer. So I thought I'd justcome down here, and make sure you were okay.",
        "response":"...I'm, I'm okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Listen uh, maybe we could get together later?",
        "response":"That sounds good. I'll call you- or you call me, whatever...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Listen uh, maybe we could get together later?",
        "response":"That sounds good. I'll call you- or you call me, whatever...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...I'm, I'm okay.",
        "response":"Listen uh, maybe we could get together later?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...I'm, I'm okay.",
        "response":"Listen uh, maybe we could get together later?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That sounds good. I'll call you- or you call me, whatever...",
        "response":"You got it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That sounds good. I'll call you- or you call me, whatever...",
        "response":"You got it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You got it.",
        "response":"Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You DON'T KNOW?",
        "response":"Well, she seems very nice and everything, but that whole thing about her comingall the way down here, just to see if I was okay? I mean,... how needy is that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Oh, yeah. Had that dream.",
        "question":"Alright, so I'm back in high school, I'm standing in the middle of thecafeteria, and I realize I am totally naked.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Then I look down, and I realize there's a phone... there.",
        "question":"Oh, yeah. Had that dream.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Instead of...?",
        "question":"Then I look down, and I realize there's a phone... there.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...I dunno.",
        "response":"You DON'T KNOW?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"That's right.",
        "question":"Instead of...?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"That's right.",
        "question":"Instead of...?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.",
        "response":"G'bye, everybody.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You got it.",
        "response":"Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Oh God... well, it started about a half hour before the wedding. I was in the roomwhere we were keeping all the presents, and I was looking at this gravy boat. This reallygorgeous Lamauge gravy boat. When all of a sudden- Sweet 'n' Lo?- I realized that I was more turned on by this gravy boat than byBarry! And then I got really freaked out, and that's when it hit me: how much Barry lookslike Mr. Potato Head. Y'know, I mean, he always looked familiar, but... Anyway, I just hadto get out of there, and I started wondering 'Why am I doing this, and who am I doing thisfor?'.  So anyway I just didn't know where to go, and I know that you and Ihave kinda drifted apart, but you're the only person I knew who lived here in the city.",
        "question":"So you wanna tell us now, or are we waiting for four wet bridesmaids?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Who wasn't invited to the wedding.",
        "question":"Oh God... well, it started about a half hour before the wedding. I was in the roomwhere we were keeping all the presents, and I was looking at this gravy boat. This reallygorgeous Lamauge gravy boat. When all of a sudden- Sweet 'n' Lo?- I realized that I was more turned on by this gravy boat than byBarry! And then I got really freaked out, and that's when it hit me: how much Barry lookslike Mr. Potato Head. Y'know, I mean, he always looked familiar, but... Anyway, I just hadto get out of there, and I started wondering 'Why am I doing this, and who am I doing thisfor?'.  So anyway I just didn't know where to go, and I know that you and Ihave kinda drifted apart, but you're the only person I knew who lived here in the city.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Who wasn't invited to the wedding.",
        "question":"Oh God... well, it started about a half hour before the wedding. I was in the roomwhere we were keeping all the presents, and I was looking at this gravy boat. This reallygorgeous Lamauge gravy boat. When all of a sudden- Sweet 'n' Lo?- I realized that I was more turned on by this gravy boat than byBarry! And then I got really freaked out, and that's when it hit me: how much Barry lookslike Mr. Potato Head. Y'know, I mean, he always looked familiar, but... Anyway, I just hadto get out of there, and I started wondering 'Why am I doing this, and who am I doing thisfor?'.  So anyway I just didn't know where to go, and I know that you and Ihave kinda drifted apart, but you're the only person I knew who lived here in the city.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"No you don't.",
        "question":"No, no don't! Stop cleansing my aura! No, just leave my aura alone, okay? I'll befine, alright? Really, everyone. I hope she'll be very happy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"No!! Okay?! Why does everyone keep fixating on that? She didn't know, how should Iknow?",
        "question":"And you never knew she was a lesbian...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"And you never knew she was a lesbian...",
        "question":"No I don't, to hell with her, she left me!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Ooh, I was kinda hoping that wouldn't be an issue...",
        "question":"Who wasn't invited to the wedding.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"No I don't, to hell with her, she left me!",
        "question":"No you don't.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Never had that dream.",
        "question":"That's right.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"You can see where he'd have trouble.",
        "question":"C'mon Daddy, listen to me! All of my life, everyone has always told me, 'You're ashoe! You're a shoe, you're a shoe, you're a shoe!'. And today I just stopped and I said,'What if I don't wanna be a shoe? What if I wanna be a- a purse, y'know? Or a- or a hat!No, I'm not saying I want you to buy me a hat, I'm saying I am a ha- It's a metaphor,Daddy!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"And hey, you need anything, you can always come to Joey. Me andChandler live across the hall. And he's away a lot.",
        "question":"Okay, look, this is probably for the best, y'know? Independence. Taking control ofyour life.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Joey, stop hitting on her! It's her wedding day!",
        "question":"And hey, you need anything, you can always come to Joey. Me andChandler live across the hall. And he's away a lot.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Joey, stop hitting on her! It's her wedding day!",
        "question":"And hey, you need anything, you can always come to Joey. Me andChandler live across the hall. And he's away a lot.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Well, maybe that's my decision. Well, maybe I don't need your money. Wait!! Wait,I said maybe!!",
        "question":"Well, I guess we've established who's staying here with Monica...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Well, I guess we've established who's staying here with Monica...",
        "question":"Look Daddy, it's my life. Well maybe I'll just stay here with Monica.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Look Daddy, it's my life. Well maybe I'll just stay here with Monica.",
        "question":"You can see where he'd have trouble.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"I'm all better now.",
        "question":"Raindrops on roses and rabbits and kittens, ..bluebells and sleighbells and- something with mittens... La la la la...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"I helped!",
        "question":"I'm all better now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"What, like there's a rule or something?",
        "question":"Joey, stop hitting on her! It's her wedding day!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Are, are you okay? I mean, do you want me to stay?",
        "question":"Please, no, go, that'd be fine!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"That'd be good...",
        "question":"Are, are you okay? I mean, do you want me to stay?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Rach, wait, I can cancel...",
        "question":"Ooh, this is a Dear Diary moment.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Please, no, go, that'd be fine!",
        "question":"Rach, wait, I can cancel...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"No, go on! It's Paul the Wine Guy!",
        "question":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Ooh, this is a Dear Diary moment.",
        "question":"Yes!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Really?",
        "question":"That'd be good...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Really?",
        "question":"That'd be good...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Right, you're not even getting your honeymoon, God.. No, no, although, Aruba, thistime of year... talk about your-  -big lizards... Anyway, if you don't feel likebeing alone tonight, Joey and Chandler are coming over to help me put together my newfurniture.",
        "question":"Well, I was kinda supposed to be headed for Aruba on my honeymoon, so nothing!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Ross, let me ask you a question. She got the furniture, the stereo, the good TV-what did you get?",
        "question":"This was Carol's favourite beer. She alwaysdrank it out of the can, I should have known.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Well, I was kinda supposed to be headed for Aruba on my honeymoon, so nothing!",
        "question":"So Rachel, what're you, uh... what're you up to tonight?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Hi, come in! Paul, this is.. ...everybody, everybody, this is Paul.",
        "question":"No, go on! It's Paul the Wine Guy!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"No, go on! It's Paul the Wine Guy!",
        "question":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Done with the bookcase!",
        "question":"I have no idea.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Done with the bookcase!",
        "question":"I have no idea.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"All finished!",
        "question":"Done with the bookcase!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"I have no idea.",
        "question":"What's this?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"My brother's going through that right now, he's such a mess. How did you getthrough it?",
        "question":"I know, I know, I'm such an idiot. I guess I should have caught on when she startedgoing to the dentist four and five times a week. I mean, how clean can teeth get?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"My brother's going through that right now, he's such a mess. How did you getthrough it?",
        "question":"I know, I know, I'm such an idiot. I guess I should have caught on when she startedgoing to the dentist four and five times a week. I mean, how clean can teeth get?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"I know, I know, I'm such an idiot. I guess I should have caught on when she startedgoing to the dentist four and five times a week. I mean, how clean can teeth get?",
        "question":"Oh my God!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Well, you might try accidentally breaking something valuable of hers, say her-",
        "question":"My brother's going through that right now, he's such a mess. How did you getthrough it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Well, you might try accidentally breaking something valuable of hers, say her-",
        "question":"My brother's going through that right now, he's such a mess. How did you getthrough it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"You guys.",
        "question":"Ross, let me ask you a question. She got the furniture, the stereo, the good TV-what did you get?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"-leg?",
        "question":"Well, you might try accidentally breaking something valuable of hers, say her-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"-leg?",
        "question":"Well, you might try accidentally breaking something valuable of hers, say her-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"That's one way! Me, I- I went for the watch.",
        "question":"-leg?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"What are you talking about? 'One woman'? That's like saying there's only one flavourof ice cream for you. Lemme tell you something, Ross. There's lots of flavours out there.There's Rocky Road, and Cookie Dough, and Bing! Cherry Vanilla. You could get 'em withJimmies, or nuts, or whipped cream! This is the best thing that ever happened to you! Yougot married, you were, like, what, eight? Welcome back to the world! Grab a spoon!",
        "question":"You know what the scariest part is? What if there's only one woman for everybody,y'know? I mean what if you get one woman- and that's it? Unfortunately in my case, therewas only one woman- for her...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"I honestly don't know if I'm hungry or horny.",
        "question":"What are you talking about? 'One woman'? That's like saying there's only one flavourof ice cream for you. Lemme tell you something, Ross. There's lots of flavours out there.There's Rocky Road, and Cookie Dough, and Bing! Cherry Vanilla. You could get 'em withJimmies, or nuts, or whipped cream! This is the best thing that ever happened to you! Yougot married, you were, like, what, eight? Welcome back to the world! Grab a spoon!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"No, it's, it's more of a fifth date kinda revelation.",
        "question":"What?..... What, you wanna spell it out with noodles?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"No, it's, it's more of a fifth date kinda revelation.",
        "question":"What?..... What, you wanna spell it out with noodles?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"What?..... What, you wanna spell it out with noodles?",
        "question":"Ever since she walked out on me, I, uh...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"You actually broke her watch?",
        "question":"That's one way! Me, I- I went for the watch.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Oh, so there is gonna be a fifth date?",
        "question":"No, it's, it's more of a fifth date kinda revelation.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Oh, so there is gonna be a fifth date?",
        "question":"No, it's, it's more of a fifth date kinda revelation.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"That's one way! Me, I- I went for the watch.",
        "question":"-leg?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, no she doesn't but I can, I can get a message to her.",
        "response":"Great. Uhh, just tell her her husband stopped by. [leaves flowers on bar]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I'm looking for Phoebe, does she still live here?",
        "response":"Uh, no she doesn't but I can, I can get a message to her.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I'm looking for Phoebe, does she still live here?",
        "response":"Uh, no she doesn't but I can, I can get a message to her.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi, hi can I help you?",
        "response":"Yeah, I'm looking for Phoebe, does she still live here?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi, hi can I help you?",
        "response":"Yeah, I'm looking for Phoebe, does she still live here?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Yeah... yeah, I think there is. -What were you gonna say?",
        "question":"Isn't there?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Isn't there?",
        "question":"Oh, so there is gonna be a fifth date?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "response":"Isn't there?",
        "question":"Oh, so there is gonna be a fifth date?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Hi, hi can I help you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I mean, I'm not <i>married</i> married, ya know, he's just a friend and he'sgay and he's just from Canada and he just needed a green card.",
        "response":"I can't believe you married Duncan. I mean how could you not tell me? We livedtogether, we told each other everything.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't believe you married Duncan. I mean how could you not tell me? We livedtogether, we told each other everything.",
        "response":"I'm sorry Monica but I knew if I told you, you'd get really, like, judgemental andyou would not approve.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't believe you married Duncan. I mean how could you not tell me? We livedtogether, we told each other everything.",
        "response":"I'm sorry Monica but I knew if I told you, you'd get really, like, judgemental andyou would not approve.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry Monica but I knew if I told you, you'd get really, like, judgemental andyou would not approve.",
        "response":"Of course I wouldn't approve, I mean, you were totally in love with this guy who,hello, was gay. I mean, what the hell were you thinking?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Great. Uhh, just tell her her husband stopped by. [leaves flowers on bar]",
        "response":"What? [in surprise she forgets she has the pigeon in the pot and lets it get away]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Great. Uhh, just tell her her husband stopped by. [leaves flowers on bar]",
        "response":"What? [in surprise she forgets she has the pigeon in the pot and lets it get away]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, no she doesn't but I can, I can get a message to her.",
        "response":"Great. Uhh, just tell her her husband stopped by. [leaves flowers on bar]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Please, when he left town you stayed in your pajamas for a month and I saw you eata cheeseburger.",
        "response":"Huuh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? [in surprise she forgets she has the pigeon in the pot and lets it get away]",
        "response":"Hey, how, how did you do that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What have I not told you?",
        "response":"Oh, I don't know. Umm, how about the fact that the underwear out there on thetelephone pole is yours from when you were having sex with Fun Bobby out on the terrace.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't believe you didn't tell me.",
        "response":"Oh, c'mon, like you tell me everything.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't believe you didn't tell me.",
        "response":"Oh, c'mon, like you tell me everything.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, c'mon, like you tell me everything.",
        "response":"What have I not told you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, c'mon, like you tell me everything.",
        "response":"What have I not told you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I might have.",
        "response":"I can't believe you didn't tell me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I might have.",
        "response":"I can't believe you didn't tell me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, didn't you?",
        "response":"I might have.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huuh.",
        "response":"Well, didn't you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I didn't know it was a big secret.",
        "response":"Oh it's not big, not at all, you know, kinda the same lines as, say, oh I don'tknow, having a third nipple.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey, what did you think a nubbin was?",
        "response":"I don't know, you see somethin', you hear a word, I thought that's what it was. Letme see it again.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wait a minute, who told you? [turns to Chandler who's looking sheepish] You aredead meat.",
        "response":"I didn't know it was a big secret.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whip it out, whip it out.",
        "response":"C'mon, there's nothin' to see, it's just a tiny bump, it's totally useless.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't believe you. You told me it was a nubbin.",
        "response":"Joey, what did you think a nubbin was?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, show it. Show it. The nubbin, the nubbin, the nubbin.",
        "response":"Joey was in a porno movie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey was in a porno movie.",
        "response":"Huuh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You bitch.",
        "response":"Whip it out, whip it out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why yes Ross, pressing my third nipple opens the delivery entrance to themagical land of Narnia.",
        "response":"You know, in some cultures having a third nipple is actually a sign of virility.You get the best huts and women dance naked around you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look honey, I wanted you to hook up with Ross as much as you did. But he's withher now and you're just gonna have to get over it.",
        "response":"Ohh, I'm gonna have to get over it. God, see I didn't know that's I had to do, Ijust have to get over it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know, in some cultures having a third nipple is actually a sign of virility.You get the best huts and women dance naked around you.",
        "response":"Huh? Are, uh, any of these cultures, per chance, in the tri-state area?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[to Monica at the counter] Ooh, Julie's so smart, Julie's so special.",
        "response":"Look honey, I wanted you to hook up with Ross as much as you did. But he's withher now and you're just gonna have to get over it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Bye-bye Julie. [Julie leaves]",
        "response":"[Rachel is still cleaning, Ross is laying on the couch. Ross kicks Rachel in the butt.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Rachel is still cleaning, Ross is laying on the couch. Ross kicks Rachel in the butt.]",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huuh.",
        "response":"If I'm goin' down, I'm takin' everybody with me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, c'mon, cut it out.",
        "response":"Hey?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey was in a porno movie.",
        "response":"Huuh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Can I ask you somethin'?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Can I ask you somethin'?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Can I ask you somethin'?",
        "response":"Sure.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Can I ask you somethin'?",
        "response":"Sure.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Naa.",
        "response":"What? C'mon, talk to me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sure.",
        "response":"Naa.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sure.",
        "response":"Naa.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, what's the longest you've been in the relationship before ha, have, having thesex?",
        "response":"Why? Who's not having. . . Are you and Julie not, are, are you and, are you andJulie not having sex?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, what's the longest you've been in the relationship before ha, have, having thesex?",
        "response":"Why? Who's not having. . . Are you and Julie not, are, are you and, are you andJulie not having sex?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? C'mon, talk to me.",
        "response":"OK, what's the longest you've been in the relationship before ha, have, having thesex?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? C'mon, talk to me.",
        "response":"OK, what's the longest you've been in the relationship before ha, have, having thesex?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Technically, huh, no.",
        "response":"Wow. Is it, is it 'cause she's so cold in bed. Or, or is it 'cause she's like,kinda bossy, makes it feel like school?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Technically, huh, no.",
        "response":"Wow. Is it, is it 'cause she's so cold in bed. Or, or is it 'cause she's like,kinda bossy, makes it feel like school?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why? Who's not having. . . Are you and Julie not, are, are you and, are you andJulie not having sex?",
        "response":"Technically, huh, no.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why? Who's not having. . . Are you and Julie not, are, are you and, are you andJulie not having sex?",
        "response":"Technically, huh, no.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Naa.",
        "response":"What? C'mon, talk to me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's just, it's, it's me. You, you know I've only been with one woman my whole lifeand she turned out to be a lesbian. So now I've got myself all psyched out, you know, andit's become, like this, this thing and I. . . Well, you just must think I'm weird.",
        "response":"No, no, no, no I don't think it's weird, I think, I think umm, in fact, in factyou know what I think?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's just, it's, it's me. You, you know I've only been with one woman my whole lifeand she turned out to be a lesbian. So now I've got myself all psyched out, you know, andit's become, like this, this thing and I. . . Well, you just must think I'm weird.",
        "response":"No, no, no, no I don't think it's weird, I think, I think umm, in fact, in factyou know what I think?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no no no, don't need to know the details.",
        "response":"It's just, it's, it's me. You, you know I've only been with one woman my whole lifeand she turned out to be a lesbian. So now I've got myself all psyched out, you know, andit's become, like this, this thing and I. . . Well, you just must think I'm weird.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no no no, don't need to know the details.",
        "response":"It's just, it's, it's me. You, you know I've only been with one woman my whole lifeand she turned out to be a lesbian. So now I've got myself all psyched out, you know, andit's become, like this, this thing and I. . . Well, you just must think I'm weird.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow. Is it, is it 'cause she's so cold in bed. Or, or is it 'cause she's like,kinda bossy, makes it feel like school?",
        "response":"No, no, she's great and it's not like we haven't done anything. I mean, uh, uh, we,we do plenty of other stuff, lot's of other stuff, like uhh. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow. Is it, is it 'cause she's so cold in bed. Or, or is it 'cause she's like,kinda bossy, makes it feel like school?",
        "response":"No, no, she's great and it's not like we haven't done anything. I mean, uh, uh, we,we do plenty of other stuff, lot's of other stuff, like uhh. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, she's great and it's not like we haven't done anything. I mean, uh, uh, we,we do plenty of other stuff, lot's of other stuff, like uhh. . .",
        "response":"No, no no no, don't need to know the details.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, she's great and it's not like we haven't done anything. I mean, uh, uh, we,we do plenty of other stuff, lot's of other stuff, like uhh. . .",
        "response":"No, no no no, don't need to know the details.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, no, no I don't think it's weird, I think, I think umm, in fact, in factyou know what I think?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Let me tell you something. As a woman there is nothing sexier than a man who doesnot want to have sex.",
        "response":"No kidding?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Let me tell you something. As a woman there is nothing sexier than a man who doesnot want to have sex.",
        "response":"No kidding?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sexy?",
        "response":"Let me tell you something. As a woman there is nothing sexier than a man who doesnot want to have sex.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sexy?",
        "response":"Let me tell you something. As a woman there is nothing sexier than a man who doesnot want to have sex.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, no, no I don't think it's weird, I think, I think umm, in fact, in factyou know what I think?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I think it's sexy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I think it's sexy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I think it's sexy.",
        "response":"Sexy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I think it's sexy.",
        "response":"Sexy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You'd wait?",
        "response":"Yes, absolutely. I would wait and wait. . . then I'd wait some more.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No kidding?",
        "response":"Oh yeah. In fact you know what I'd do?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No kidding?",
        "response":"Oh yeah. In fact you know what I'd do?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah. In fact you know what I'd do?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah. In fact you know what I'd do?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'd wait.",
        "response":"You'd wait?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'd wait.",
        "response":"You'd wait?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I'd wait.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I'd wait.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah, I don't care how much she tells you she wants it, I don't care if begs,she pleads, she tells you she, she's gonna have sex with, with another man. That justmeans it's working.",
        "response":"Women really want this?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah, I don't care how much she tells you she wants it, I don't care if begs,she pleads, she tells you she, she's gonna have sex with, with another man. That justmeans it's working.",
        "response":"Women really want this?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Oh yeah, I don't care how much she tells you she wants it, I don't care if begs,she pleads, she tells you she, she's gonna have sex with, with another man. That justmeans it's working.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Oh yeah, I don't care how much she tells you she wants it, I don't care if begs,she pleads, she tells you she, she's gonna have sex with, with another man. That justmeans it's working.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Women really want this?",
        "response":"More than jewelry. [Rachel struts off, extremely pleased with herself]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You'd wait?",
        "response":"Yes, absolutely. I would wait and wait. . . then I'd wait some more.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, absolutely. I would wait and wait. . . then I'd wait some more.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, absolutely. I would wait and wait. . . then I'd wait some more.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Phoebe!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahh, look at you, you look great.",
        "response":"Do I? Thank you, so do you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Ahh, look at you, you look great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Ahh, look at you, you look great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebe!",
        "response":"Ta-da.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebe!",
        "response":"Ta-da.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ta-da.",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ta-da.",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sparkly. So, wow, this is pretty wonerful, huh. Mr. major capades guy. I, Iremember when you were just, like, King Friday in Mr. Roger's Ice is Nice.",
        "response":"You always said I'd make it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sparkly. So, wow, this is pretty wonerful, huh. Mr. major capades guy. I, Iremember when you were just, like, King Friday in Mr. Roger's Ice is Nice.",
        "response":"You always said I'd make it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thanks.",
        "response":"Sparkly. So, wow, this is pretty wonerful, huh. Mr. major capades guy. I, Iremember when you were just, like, King Friday in Mr. Roger's Ice is Nice.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thanks.",
        "response":"Sparkly. So, wow, this is pretty wonerful, huh. Mr. major capades guy. I, Iremember when you were just, like, King Friday in Mr. Roger's Ice is Nice.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You always said I'd make it.",
        "response":"Yeah, well, ya know, I'm kind of spooky that way. Wooo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You always said I'd make it.",
        "response":"Yeah, well, ya know, I'm kind of spooky that way. Wooo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahh, look at you, you look great.",
        "response":"Do I? Thank you, so do you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Do I? Thank you, so do you.",
        "response":"Thanks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Do I? Thank you, so do you.",
        "response":"Thanks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, well, ya know, I'm kind of spooky that way. Wooo.",
        "response":"I missed you. [they hug] I'm gonna get changed.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, well, ya know, I'm kind of spooky that way. Wooo.",
        "response":"I missed you. [they hug] I'm gonna get changed.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I missed you. [they hug] I'm gonna get changed.",
        "response":"OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I missed you. [they hug] I'm gonna get changed.",
        "response":"OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, now. Phoebs.",
        "response":"Oh, right, OK. Ole.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, now. Phoebs.",
        "response":"Oh, right, OK. Ole.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, right, OK. Ole.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK.",
        "response":"Um, now. Phoebs.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK.",
        "response":"Um, now. Phoebs.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[pulls Rachel aside] I just, I wanted to thank you for our uh, our little talkbefore.",
        "response":"Oh, God, no problem. So you're gonna go with the uh, waiting thing?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, God, no problem. So you're gonna go with the uh, waiting thing?",
        "response":"Well, I was going to, but after I talked to you, I talked to Joey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, God, no problem. So you're gonna go with the uh, waiting thing?",
        "response":"Well, I was going to, but after I talked to you, I talked to Joey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah?",
        "response":"Sorry, you had a paleontologist on your face. But, uh, it's gone now, you'realright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"[pulls Rachel aside] I just, I wanted to thank you for our uh, our little talkbefore.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Um, the matador. [Duncan leaves] Ole, ha ha ha.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, right, OK. Ole.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi everyone.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, Julie.",
        "response":"Yeah?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Shh, OK, here I come, here I come. See I'm comin' to fix the copier, I can't get tothe copier, I'm thinkin' what do I do, what do I do. . . so I just watch 'em have sex. Andthen I say, wait, here's my line, [Joey from TV] <i>you know that's bad fo r the papertray</i>.",
        "response":"Nice work my friend.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What did, what did he say?",
        "response":"Basically he told me to get over myself and just do it, ya know. So I though aboutwhat you said and I though about what he said and, well, his way I get to have sex tonightso. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's wrong with people having sex?",
        "response":"Well, well um, you know, these movies are offensive and uh, degrading to women andfemales. And uh, and the lighting's always unflattering. And, Monica help me out here.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nice work my friend.",
        "response":"Thank you. Wait wait wait wait, you see me again. Hang on, the guy's butt's blockin'me. There I am, there I am, there I am, there I am, there I am. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So um, so what's up, you came to see me yesterday.",
        "response":"Oh, yeah, um, alright, I kinda need a divorce.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Great, people having sex, that's just what I need to see.",
        "response":"What's wrong with people having sex?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I was going to, but after I talked to you, I talked to Joey.",
        "response":"What did, what did he say?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I was going to, but after I talked to you, I talked to Joey.",
        "response":"What did, what did he say?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah, um, alright, I kinda need a divorce.",
        "response":"Ohh. . .K. How come?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah, um, alright, I kinda need a divorce.",
        "response":"Ohh. . .K. How come?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Oh God, I don't know how to tell you this. I'm straight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Oh God, I don't know how to tell you this. I'm straight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God, I don't know how to tell you this. I'm straight.",
        "response":"Huuh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God, I don't know how to tell you this. I'm straight.",
        "response":"Huuh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohh. . .K. How come?",
        "response":"Umm, actually, I'm getting married again.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohh. . .K. How come?",
        "response":"Umm, actually, I'm getting married again.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Umm, actually, I'm getting married again.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Umm, actually, I'm getting married again.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I, I don't, I don't understand, how can you be straight? I mean, you're, you're sosmart and funny and you throw such great Academy Award parties.",
        "response":"I know, that's what I kept telling myself but you just reach a point where youcan't live a lie anymore.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I, I don't, I don't understand, how can you be straight? I mean, you're, you're sosmart and funny and you throw such great Academy Award parties.",
        "response":"I know, that's what I kept telling myself but you just reach a point where youcan't live a lie anymore.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So how long have you known?",
        "response":"Well I guess on some level I always knew I was straight. I though I was supposedto be something else, you know, I'm an ice dancer, all my friends are gay, I was justtryin' to fit in.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I know, I.",
        "response":"I, I don't, I don't understand, how can you be straight? I mean, you're, you're sosmart and funny and you throw such great Academy Award parties.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I know, I.",
        "response":"I, I don't, I don't understand, how can you be straight? I mean, you're, you're sosmart and funny and you throw such great Academy Award parties.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, that's what I kept telling myself but you just reach a point where youcan't live a lie anymore.",
        "response":"So how long have you known?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, that's what I kept telling myself but you just reach a point where youcan't live a lie anymore.",
        "response":"So how long have you known?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huuh.",
        "response":"Yeah, I know, I.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huuh.",
        "response":"Yeah, I know, I.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh. Well is she, is she the first that you've been with?",
        "response":"Well, I've never told you this but, there were one or two times, back in college,when I'd get really drunk, go to a straight bar and wake up with a woman next to me. ButI, I, I told myself it was the liquor and e-everyone experiments in college.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh. Well is she, is she the first that you've been with?",
        "response":"Well, I've never told you this but, there were one or two times, back in college,when I'd get really drunk, go to a straight bar and wake up with a woman next to me. ButI, I, I told myself it was the liquor and e-everyone experiments in college.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well I guess on some level I always knew I was straight. I though I was supposedto be something else, you know, I'm an ice dancer, all my friends are gay, I was justtryin' to fit in.",
        "response":"And um, and there's actually a, a woman?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So how long have you known?",
        "response":"Well I guess on some level I always knew I was straight. I though I was supposedto be something else, you know, I'm an ice dancer, all my friends are gay, I was justtryin' to fit in.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well I guess on some level I always knew I was straight. I though I was supposedto be something else, you know, I'm an ice dancer, all my friends are gay, I was justtryin' to fit in.",
        "response":"And um, and there's actually a, a woman?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Her name's Debra.",
        "response":"Oh. Well is she, is she the first that you've been with?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Her name's Debra.",
        "response":"Oh. Well is she, is she the first that you've been with?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And um, and there's actually a, a woman?",
        "response":"Her name's Debra.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And um, and there's actually a, a woman?",
        "response":"Her name's Debra.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I've never told you this but, there were one or two times, back in college,when I'd get really drunk, go to a straight bar and wake up with a woman next to me. ButI, I, I told myself it was the liquor and e-everyone experiments in college.",
        "response":"Sure.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I've never told you this but, there were one or two times, back in college,when I'd get really drunk, go to a straight bar and wake up with a woman next to me. ButI, I, I told myself it was the liquor and e-everyone experiments in college.",
        "response":"Sure.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But now I know I don't have a choice about this, I was born this way.",
        "response":"I, I don't know what to say. I mean, you know, you're married to someone for sixyears and you think you know him and then one day says, 'Oh, I'm not gay.'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But now I know I don't have a choice about this, I was born this way.",
        "response":"I, I don't know what to say. I mean, you know, you're married to someone for sixyears and you think you know him and then one day says, 'Oh, I'm not gay.'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I, I don't know what to say. I mean, you know, you're married to someone for sixyears and you think you know him and then one day says, 'Oh, I'm not gay.'",
        "response":"I'm, I'm still me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I, I don't know what to say. I mean, you know, you're married to someone for sixyears and you think you know him and then one day says, 'Oh, I'm not gay.'",
        "response":"I'm, I'm still me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm, I'm still me.",
        "response":"Why couldn't you have just figured this out six years ago?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sure.",
        "response":"But now I know I don't have a choice about this, I was born this way.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sure.",
        "response":"But now I know I don't have a choice about this, I was born this way.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you have been in our lives for nearly two months now and we don't reallyknow you. I mean, who is Julie? I mean, what do you like, what don't you like? We wannahear everything.",
        "response":"Well, that could take a while.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you have been in our lives for nearly two months now and we don't reallyknow you. I mean, who is Julie? I mean, what do you like, what don't you like? We wannahear everything.",
        "response":"Well, that could take a while.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What about Julie?",
        "response":"Well, you have been in our lives for nearly two months now and we don't reallyknow you. I mean, who is Julie? I mean, what do you like, what don't you like? We wannahear everything.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What about Julie?",
        "response":"Well, you have been in our lives for nearly two months now and we don't reallyknow you. I mean, who is Julie? I mean, what do you like, what don't you like? We wannahear everything.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, I mean, no, c'mon you guys, I mean, c'mon look it's only eleven thirty.Let's just talk, we never just hang out and talk anymore.",
        "response":"Rachel, that's all we do.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, that could take a while.",
        "response":"So. I mean, who here does not have the time to get to know Julie?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK Julie, so now let's start with your childhood, what was that like?",
        "response":"Well, in a nutshell. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rachel, that's all we do.",
        "response":"Maybe that's all we do, what about Julie?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe that's all we do, what about Julie?",
        "response":"What about Julie?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, but it'll be OK, they're pretty cool, my brother's straight so. . .",
        "response":"[handing him the papers] Here you go. You know what, I just have one morequestion, um, if you had figured this out sooner and um, I had been around, do you thinkthat I would have been the one who. . . no, um, I'm sorry, don't tell me, I don't th inkeither answer would make me feel better.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, but it'll be OK, they're pretty cool, my brother's straight so. . .",
        "response":"[handing him the papers] Here you go. You know what, I just have one morequestion, um, if you had figured this out sooner and um, I had been around, do you thinkthat I would have been the one who. . . no, um, I'm sorry, don't tell me, I don't th inkeither answer would make me feel better.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[handing him the papers] Here you go. You know what, I just have one morequestion, um, if you had figured this out sooner and um, I had been around, do you thinkthat I would have been the one who. . . no, um, I'm sorry, don't tell me, I don't th inkeither answer would make me feel better.",
        "response":"I love you Phoebe. [they hug and kiss]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[handing him the papers] Here you go. You know what, I just have one morequestion, um, if you had figured this out sooner and um, I had been around, do you thinkthat I would have been the one who. . . no, um, I'm sorry, don't tell me, I don't th inkeither answer would make me feel better.",
        "response":"I love you Phoebe. [they hug and kiss]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, um, have you told your parents?",
        "response":"No, but it'll be OK, they're pretty cool, my brother's straight so. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I love you Phoebe. [they hug and kiss]",
        "response":"So your brother's straigh huh? Seriously.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And my second grade teacher was Ms. Thomas, and my first grade teacher was Mrs.Cobb.",
        "response":"Mrs., Mrs. Gobb?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mrs., Mrs. Gobb?",
        "response":"No Cobb, as in cobb salad.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, in a nutshell. . .",
        "response":"Nah, uh, uh, uh, uh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Goodnight.",
        "response":"So, it's pretty late, you're probably uh, not still planning on. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, it's pretty late, you're probably uh, not still planning on. . .",
        "response":"Oh, no no, I am.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, it's pretty late, you're probably uh, not still planning on. . .",
        "response":"Oh, no no, I am.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, well, are hey, are you nervous?",
        "response":"Um, no, I uh, I have done it before.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, well, are hey, are you nervous?",
        "response":"Um, no, I uh, I have done it before.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Now, what exactly is in a cobb salad?",
        "response":"I'm goin' home.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, no no, I am.",
        "response":"Oh, well, are hey, are you nervous?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, no no, I am.",
        "response":"Oh, well, are hey, are you nervous?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm goin' home.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, OK, I mean uh, what, how are you gonna handle it. I mean, are, are ya gonna,are ya gonna talk about it before hand, are you just gonna pounce?",
        "response":"I uh, I don't know, I guess I'm just gonna see, see what happens.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nothing, I mean, um, it is your first time with her and, you know if the firsttime doesn't go well, well then that's, that's pretty darn hard to recover from.",
        "response":"OK, now I'm nervous.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nothing, I mean, um, it is your first time with her and, you know if the firsttime doesn't go well, well then that's, that's pretty darn hard to recover from.",
        "response":"OK, now I'm nervous.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wha, uhh, what?",
        "response":"Nothing, I mean, um, it is your first time with her and, you know if the firsttime doesn't go well, well then that's, that's pretty darn hard to recover from.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, no, I uh, I have done it before.",
        "response":"Uh, OK, I mean uh, what, how are you gonna handle it. I mean, are, are ya gonna,are ya gonna talk about it before hand, are you just gonna pounce?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, no, I uh, I have done it before.",
        "response":"Uh, OK, I mean uh, what, how are you gonna handle it. I mean, are, are ya gonna,are ya gonna talk about it before hand, are you just gonna pounce?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I uh, I don't know, I guess I'm just gonna see, see what happens.",
        "response":"OK, gook luck.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, now I'm nervous.",
        "response":"Maybe you should put it off.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, gook luck.",
        "response":"Wha, uhh, what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe you should put it off.",
        "response":"No, no, I don't wanna put it off, I just, God I just, I spent last year being sounbelievably miserable, ya know, and now, now I'm actually happy. You know, I mean, reallyhappy. I just, I just don't wanna, I don't wanna mess it up, ya know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe you should put it off.",
        "response":"No, no, I don't wanna put it off, I just, God I just, I spent last year being sounbelievably miserable, ya know, and now, now I'm actually happy. You know, I mean, reallyhappy. I just, I just don't wanna, I don't wanna mess it up, ya know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, I don't wanna put it off, I just, God I just, I spent last year being sounbelievably miserable, ya know, and now, now I'm actually happy. You know, I mean, reallyhappy. I just, I just don't wanna, I don't wanna mess it up, ya know.",
        "response":"I know, yeah, sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, I don't wanna put it off, I just, God I just, I spent last year being sounbelievably miserable, ya know, and now, now I'm actually happy. You know, I mean, reallyhappy. I just, I just don't wanna, I don't wanna mess it up, ya know.",
        "response":"I know, yeah, sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What, it's not your fault.",
        "response":"Maybe it, maybe it doesn't have to be this tough. I mean, maybe you were on theright track with this whole, you know, spontaneous thing. I mean, women really like that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What, it's not your fault.",
        "response":"Maybe it, maybe it doesn't have to be this tough. I mean, maybe you were on theright track with this whole, you know, spontaneous thing. I mean, women really like that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, now I'm nervous.",
        "response":"Maybe you should put it off.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, yeah, sorry.",
        "response":"What, it's not your fault.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, yeah, sorry.",
        "response":"What, it's not your fault.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I mean, you know it, I mean, if it were me I, I, you know, I'd want you to,I don't know, like catch me off guard, you know, with like a really good kiss, you knowreally, sort of um, soft at first, then maybe um brush the hair away from my face, andlook far into my eyes in a way that let's me know that something amazing is about tohappen.",
        "response":"[being drawn in by her talk] Uh-huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I mean, you know it, I mean, if it were me I, I, you know, I'd want you to,I don't know, like catch me off guard, you know, with like a really good kiss, you knowreally, sort of um, soft at first, then maybe um brush the hair away from my face, andlook far into my eyes in a way that let's me know that something amazing is about tohappen.",
        "response":"[being drawn in by her talk] Uh-huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Yeah, I mean, you know it, I mean, if it were me I, I, you know, I'd want you to,I don't know, like catch me off guard, you know, with like a really good kiss, you knowreally, sort of um, soft at first, then maybe um brush the hair away from my face, andlook far into my eyes in a way that let's me know that something amazing is about tohappen.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Yeah, I mean, you know it, I mean, if it were me I, I, you know, I'd want you to,I don't know, like catch me off guard, you know, with like a really good kiss, you knowreally, sort of um, soft at first, then maybe um brush the hair away from my face, andlook far into my eyes in a way that let's me know that something amazing is about tohappen.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And then, I don't know, I mean you'd pull me really close to you so that, so thatI'd be pressed up, you know, right against you. And, um, it would get kind of sweaty anduh, and blurry, and then it's just happening.",
        "response":"Ohh. . . Thanks Rach, goodnight. [goes back in apartment]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[being drawn in by her talk] Uh-huh.",
        "response":"And then, I don't know, I mean you'd pull me really close to you so that, so thatI'd be pressed up, you know, right against you. And, um, it would get kind of sweaty anduh, and blurry, and then it's just happening.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[being drawn in by her talk] Uh-huh.",
        "response":"And then, I don't know, I mean you'd pull me really close to you so that, so thatI'd be pressed up, you know, right against you. And, um, it would get kind of sweaty anduh, and blurry, and then it's just happening.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe it, maybe it doesn't have to be this tough. I mean, maybe you were on theright track with this whole, you know, spontaneous thing. I mean, women really like that.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe it, maybe it doesn't have to be this tough. I mean, maybe you were on theright track with this whole, you know, spontaneous thing. I mean, women really like that.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OLD WOMAN: Well, somebody got some last night.",
        "response":"Twice.</font></p><p align=\"center\"><strong><font size=\"3\">END</font></strong></p><hr><p align=\"center\"><!--webbot bot=\"ImageMap\" startspanrectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/205fsae.htm\"rectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2.htm\"rectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/203towhd.htm\"src=\"contrl08.gif\" width=\"194\" height=\"60\"alt=\"Contrl08.gif \" --><MAP NAME=\"FrontPageMap0\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"138, 3, 197, 84\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/205fsae.htm\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"71, 3, 129, 84\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2.htm\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"0, 1, 58, 80\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/203towhd.htm\"></MAP><img src=\"contrl08.gif\" width=\"194\" height=\"60\" alt=\"Contrl08.gif \" usemap=\"#FrontPageMap0\"><!--webbot bot=\"ImageMap\" i-checksum=\"18681\" endspan--></p><hr><center><img src=\"/cgi-bin/counter/204\"></center><hr></body></html>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And then, I don't know, I mean you'd pull me really close to you so that, so thatI'd be pressed up, you know, right against you. And, um, it would get kind of sweaty anduh, and blurry, and then it's just happening.",
        "response":"Ohh. . . Thanks Rach, goodnight. [goes back in apartment]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Don't be silly. Ben loves you. He's just being Mr. Crankypants.",
        "response":"You know, I once dated a Miss Crankypants. Lovely girl, kinda moody.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Who da wenny-Benny boy? You the Wenny-wenny-Benny-Benny boy, yes. Don't cry. Don'tcry. Why is he still crying?",
        "response":"Let me hold him for a sec. There.  Huh? There we are.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maye it's me.",
        "response":"Don't be silly. Ben loves you. He's just being Mr. Crankypants.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Good morning.",
        "response":"OLD WOMAN: Well, somebody got some last night.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohh. . . Thanks Rach, goodnight. [goes back in apartment]",
        "response":"Ohh, God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Let me hold him for a sec. There.  Huh? There we are.",
        "response":"Maye it's me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Let me hold him for a sec. There.  Huh? There we are.",
        "response":"Maye it's me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Kiwi? Kiwi? I thought it was a key lime pie.",
        "response":"No I didn't, I said kiwi lime. That's what makes it so special.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, I don't know, butter, eggs, flour, lime, kiwi--",
        "response":"Kiwi? Kiwi? I thought it was a key lime pie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, I don't know, butter, eggs, flour, lime, kiwi--",
        "response":"Kiwi? Kiwi? I thought it was a key lime pie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know, I once dated a Miss Crankypants. Lovely girl, kinda moody.",
        "response":"There we go. All better.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know. What's in this pie?",
        "response":"Uh, I don't know, butter, eggs, flour, lime, kiwi--",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Come on, don't do this.",
        "response":"What if my own baby hates me? Huh? What am I gonna do then?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He hates me. My nephew hates me.",
        "response":"Come on, don't do this.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That is so funny. Let me see that.",
        "response":"Are you ok, Ross?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Goo, goo, goo, waaah!",
        "response":"That is so funny. Let me see that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No I didn't, I said kiwi lime. That's what makes it so special.",
        "response":"And that's what's gonna kill me. I'm allergic to kiwi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No I didn't, I said kiwi lime. That's what makes it so special.",
        "response":"And that's what's gonna kill me. I'm allergic to kiwi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And that's what's gonna kill me. I'm allergic to kiwi.",
        "response":"No you're not. You're, you're allergic to lobster and peanuts and--oh my god.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And that's what's gonna kill me. I'm allergic to kiwi.",
        "response":"No you're not. You're, you're allergic to lobster and peanuts and--oh my god.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Kiwi? Kiwi? I thought it was a key lime pie.",
        "response":"No I didn't, I said kiwi lime. That's what makes it so special.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No you're not. You're, you're allergic to lobster and peanuts and--oh my god.",
        "response":"Ugh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No you're not. You're, you're allergic to lobster and peanuts and--oh my god.",
        "response":"Ugh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ugh.",
        "response":"Oh my god.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ugh.",
        "response":"Oh my god.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Either that or my mouth is getting smaller.",
        "response":"All right, get your coat, we're going to the hospital.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right, get your coat, we're going to the hospital.",
        "response":"Is he gonna be ok?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Is your tongue swelling up?",
        "response":"Either that or my mouth is getting smaller.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Is your tongue swelling up?",
        "response":"Either that or my mouth is getting smaller.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ugh. It's definitely getting worse.",
        "response":"Is your tongue swelling up?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ugh. It's definitely getting worse.",
        "response":"Is your tongue swelling up?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Is he gonna be ok?",
        "response":"Yeah, he's just gotta get a shot.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my god.",
        "response":"Ugh. It's definitely getting worse.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my god.",
        "response":"Ugh. It's definitely getting worse.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, well, if you do take him out for his walk, you might wanna bring his hat, andthere's extra milk in the fridge, and there's extra diapers in the bag.",
        "response":"Hat, milk, got it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, he's just gotta get a shot.",
        "response":"You know, you know, actually it's getting better. It is. It is. Let's not go. Anyonefor Thcrabble?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know, you know, actually it's getting better. It is. It is. Let's not go. Anyonefor Thcrabble?",
        "response":"Jacket now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know, you know, actually it's getting better. It is. It is. Let's not go. Anyonefor Thcrabble?",
        "response":"Jacket now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What about Ben? We can't bring a baby to a hospital.",
        "response":"We'll watch him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Jacket now.",
        "response":"What about Ben? We can't bring a baby to a hospital.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We'll watch him.",
        "response":"I don't think tho.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hat, milk, got it.",
        "response":"???  Thro up a thro thro--a thro thro!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hat, milk, got it.",
        "response":"???  Thro up a thro thro--a thro thro!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's up?",
        "response":"F.Y.I.. I've decided to pay a professional musician to play in here on Sundayafternoons. Her name is Stephanie... something. She's supposed to be very good.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok.",
        "response":"I'm in the shower and I'm writing a song. Stop me if you've heard it. Myskin is soapy, and my hair is wet, and Tegrin spelled backward is Nirget.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Rach, wanna hear the new song I'm thinkin' of singing this afternoon? I wroteit this morning in the shower.",
        "response":"Ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, my uncle Sal has a really big tongue.",
        "response":"Is he the one with the beautiful wife?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You understood that?",
        "response":"Yeah, my uncle Sal has a really big tongue.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You understood that?",
        "response":"Yeah, my uncle Sal has a really big tongue.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, Rachel, sweetheart, could I see ya for a minute?",
        "response":"What's up?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Consider it done.",
        "response":"You understood that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"???  Thro up a thro thro--a thro thro!",
        "response":"Consider it done.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rachel, it's not that your friend is bad, it's that she's so bad, she makes me wantto put my finger through my eye into my brain and swirl it around.",
        "response":"Ok, ok, so you're not a fan, but I mean, come on, you cannot do this to her.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rachel, it's not that your friend is bad, it's that she's so bad, she makes me wantto put my finger through my eye into my brain and swirl it around.",
        "response":"Ok, ok, so you're not a fan, but I mean, come on, you cannot do this to her.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"F.Y.I.. I've decided to pay a professional musician to play in here on Sundayafternoons. Her name is Stephanie... something. She's supposed to be very good.",
        "response":"But what about Phoebe?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"F.Y.I.. I've decided to pay a professional musician to play in here on Sundayafternoons. Her name is Stephanie... something. She's supposed to be very good.",
        "response":"But what about Phoebe?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But what about Phoebe?",
        "response":"Rachel, it's not that your friend is bad, it's that she's so bad, she makes me wantto put my finger through my eye into my brain and swirl it around.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But what about Phoebe?",
        "response":"Rachel, it's not that your friend is bad, it's that she's so bad, she makes me wantto put my finger through my eye into my brain and swirl it around.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's up?",
        "response":"F.Y.I.. I've decided to pay a professional musician to play in here on Sundayafternoons. Her name is Stephanie... something. She's supposed to be very good.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, ok, so you're not a fan, but I mean, come on, you cannot do this to her.",
        "response":"Uh--",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, ok, so you're not a fan, but I mean, come on, you cannot do this to her.",
        "response":"Uh--",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know, I don't think we brought enough stuff. Did you forget to pack thebaby's anvil?",
        "response":"It's gonna be worth it. It's a known fact that women love babies, all righ? Womenlove guys who love babies. It's that whole sensitive thing. Quick, aim him at that pack o'babes over there. Maybe one of them will break away. No, no wait, for get them, we gotone, hard left. All right, gimme the baby.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's gonna be worth it. It's a known fact that women love babies, all righ? Womenlove guys who love babies. It's that whole sensitive thing. Quick, aim him at that pack o'babes over there. Maybe one of them will break away. No, no wait, for get them, we gotone, hard left. All right, gimme the baby.",
        "response":"No, I got him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's gonna be worth it. It's a known fact that women love babies, all righ? Womenlove guys who love babies. It's that whole sensitive thing. Quick, aim him at that pack o'babes over there. Maybe one of them will break away. No, no wait, for get them, we gotone, hard left. All right, gimme the baby.",
        "response":"No, I got him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, seriously.",
        "response":"Oh, seriously you want him?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello.",
        "response":"And who is this little cutie pie?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh--",
        "response":"Oh, no no no no. Oh no no no no. I have to do this to her?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I got him.",
        "response":"No, seriously.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I got him.",
        "response":"No, seriously.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello.",
        "response":"Hello.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I assume we're talking about the baby now.",
        "response":"Oh, yeah. He's got that great baby smell. Get a whiff of his head.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I assume we're talking about the baby now.",
        "response":"Oh, yeah. He's got that great baby smell. Get a whiff of his head.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah. He's got that great baby smell. Get a whiff of his head.",
        "response":"I think my uterus just skipped a beat.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah. He's got that great baby smell. Get a whiff of his head.",
        "response":"I think my uterus just skipped a beat.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You wanna smell him?",
        "response":"I assume we're talking about the baby now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I think my uterus just skipped a beat.",
        "response":"What'd I tell you? What'd I tell you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I think my uterus just skipped a beat.",
        "response":"What'd I tell you? What'd I tell you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What'd I tell you? What'd I tell you?",
        "response":"I think it's great you guys are doing this.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And he's going to be paying this woman? Why doesn't he just give her like athrone, and a crown, and like a, you know, gold stick with a ball on top.",
        "response":"Terry is a jerk, ok? That's why we're always saying &quot;Terry's a jerk!&quot;That's where that came from.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And he's going to be paying this woman? Why doesn't he just give her like athrone, and a crown, and like a, you know, gold stick with a ball on top.",
        "response":"Terry is a jerk, ok? That's why we're always saying &quot;Terry's a jerk!&quot;That's where that came from.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Honey, I'm sorry.",
        "response":"And he's going to be paying this woman? Why doesn't he just give her like athrone, and a crown, and like a, you know, gold stick with a ball on top.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Honey, I'm sorry.",
        "response":"And he's going to be paying this woman? Why doesn't he just give her like athrone, and a crown, and like a, you know, gold stick with a ball on top.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, we are great guys.",
        "response":"You know, my brother and his boyfriend have been trying to adopt for threeyears. What agency did you two go through?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Terry is a jerk, ok? That's why we're always saying &quot;Terry's a jerk!&quot;That's where that came from.",
        "response":"Yeah, ok. You probably did everything you could.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Terry is a jerk, ok? That's why we're always saying &quot;Terry's a jerk!&quot;That's where that came from.",
        "response":"Yeah, ok. You probably did everything you could.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But, but this is my gig. This is where I play. My, my name is written out there inchalk. You know, you can't just erase chalk.",
        "response":"Honey, I'm sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I think it's great you guys are doing this.",
        "response":"Well, we are great guys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, ok. You probably did everything you could.",
        "response":"Ok, you know what, lemme, let me just see what else I can do. All right, look,look. Why don't you just let her go on after Stephanie whatever-her-name-is. I mean, youwon't even be here. You don't pay her. It's not gonna cost you anything.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, you know what, lemme, let me just see what else I can do. All right, look,look. Why don't you just let her go on after Stephanie whatever-her-name-is. I mean, youwon't even be here. You don't pay her. It's not gonna cost you anything.",
        "response":"I, I don't know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Come on, Terry, I'll even clean the cappuccino machine.",
        "response":"You don't clean the cappuccino machine?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Come on, Terry, I'll even clean the cappuccino machine.",
        "response":"You don't clean the cappuccino machine?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You don't clean the cappuccino machine?",
        "response":"Of course I clean it. I mean, I,I will cleeeean it. I mean, I will cleeeean it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You don't clean the cappuccino machine?",
        "response":"Of course I clean it. I mean, I,I will cleeeean it. I mean, I will cleeeean it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I, I don't know.",
        "response":"Come on, Terry, I'll even clean the cappuccino machine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I, I don't know.",
        "response":"Come on, Terry, I'll even clean the cappuccino machine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Of course I clean it. I mean, I,I will cleeeean it. I mean, I will cleeeean it.",
        "response":"Oh, all right, fine, fine, fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. Who's workin' for you babe?",
        "response":"Oh! Oh my god. This is so exciting. How much am I gonna get?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. Who's workin' for you babe?",
        "response":"Oh! Oh my god. This is so exciting. How much am I gonna get?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Of course I clean it. I mean, I,I will cleeeean it. I mean, I will cleeeean it.",
        "response":"Oh, all right, fine, fine, fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh! Oh my god. This is so exciting. How much am I gonna get?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh! Oh my god. This is so exciting. How much am I gonna get?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Yeah. Who's workin' for you babe?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Yeah. Who's workin' for you babe?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, all right, fine, fine, fine.",
        "response":"Done.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Done.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, but Pheebs.",
        "response":"No, huh uh, I'm sorry, no. No, I'm not some like sloppy second, charity band. Youknow what, there are thousands of places in this city where people would be happy to payto hear me play.  When I play, I play for me, I don't needyour charity.  Thank you! La la la la la la la....",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, no, no no. I meant that he's gonna be paying that other woman beause she's aprofessional.",
        "response":"Well, I'm not gonna be the only one who's not getting paid.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, no, no no. I meant that he's gonna be paying that other woman beause she's aprofessional.",
        "response":"Well, I'm not gonna be the only one who's not getting paid.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well you said that he's paying the people who are playing.",
        "response":"Oh, no, no no. I meant that he's gonna be paying that other woman beause she's aprofessional.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well you said that he's paying the people who are playing.",
        "response":"Oh, no, no no. I meant that he's gonna be paying that other woman beause she's aprofessional.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I'm not gonna be the only one who's not getting paid.",
        "response":"Well, but Pheebs.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I'm not gonna be the only one who's not getting paid.",
        "response":"Well, but Pheebs.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Well you said that he's paying the people who are playing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Well you said that he's paying the people who are playing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Doctor, can I see you for just a minute please? My brother has a slight phobiaabout needles.",
        "response":"Did you tell him about my thquirt gun idea?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's a good plan, Joe. Next time we wanna pick up women, we should just go tothe park and make out. Taxi, taxi!",
        "response":"Hey, hey, look at that talent.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok.",
        "response":"Ok. Oh boy. You are doin' so good. You wanna squeeze my hand? All right, Ross,don't squeeze it so hard. Honey, really, don't squeeze it so hard! Oh, Ross! Let go of myhand!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohhh.",
        "response":"That's good, have a seat. Um, the doctor says it's gotta be a needle. You're justgonna have to be brave, ok? Can you do that for me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did you tell him about my thquirt gun idea?",
        "response":"My brother, the PhD would like to know if there's any way to treat this orally.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's good, have a seat. Um, the doctor says it's gotta be a needle. You're justgonna have to be brave, ok? Can you do that for me?",
        "response":"Ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's good, have a seat. Um, the doctor says it's gotta be a needle. You're justgonna have to be brave, ok? Can you do that for me?",
        "response":"Ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Just practicing. You're good. Carry on.",
        "response":"GIRL 1 ON BUS: Hey, you. He's just adorable.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, hey, look at that talent.",
        "response":"Just practicing. You're good. Carry on.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh we're not out. No, no. We're just uh, two heterosexual guys, hanging with the sonof our other heterosexual friend, doin' the usual straight guy stuff.",
        "response":"You done?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"GIRL 1 ON BUS: Hey, you. He's just adorable.",
        "response":"Ok, but can you tell him that, because he thinks he's too pink.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know it?",
        "response":"Hey, look, since we're neighbors and all, what do you say we uh, get together for adrink?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"GIRL 2: You guys live around here too?",
        "response":"Oh, yeah, yeah, sure. We live in the building by the uh sidewalk.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Get outta here. This is our stop too.",
        "response":"GIRL 2: You guys live around here too?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah, yeah, sure. We live in the building by the uh sidewalk.",
        "response":"You know it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"GIRL 1: Oh, there's our stop.",
        "response":"Get outta here. This is our stop too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"GIRL 1: Oh, there's our stop.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You done?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. I'm Stephanie.",
        "response":"Right. My name was on there, but now it just says &quot;carrot cake&quot;. So, um,so um, how many chords do you know?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. I'm Stephanie.",
        "response":"Right. My name was on there, but now it just says &quot;carrot cake&quot;. So, um,so um, how many chords do you know?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right. My name was on there, but now it just says &quot;carrot cake&quot;. So, um,so um, how many chords do you know?",
        "response":"All of them.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right. My name was on there, but now it just says &quot;carrot cake&quot;. So, um,so um, how many chords do you know?",
        "response":"All of them.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"... with the double double double-jointed boy. Hey. So um, are you theprofessional guitar player?",
        "response":"Yeah. I'm Stephanie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All of them.",
        "response":"Oh yeah, so you know D?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All of them.",
        "response":"Oh yeah, so you know D?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah, so you know D?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah, so you know D?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Ok, do you know how to go from D to A minor?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Ok, do you know how to go from D to A minor?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, do you know how to go from D to A minor?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, do you know how to go from D to A minor?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Ok. Um, so does your guitar have a strap?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Ok, do you know A minor?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Ok, do you know A minor?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, do you know A minor?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, do you know A minor?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, everybody, let's give a uh nice warm Central Perk welcome to--",
        "response":"Terry's a jerk, and he won't let me work, and I hate CentralPerk!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Terry's a jerk, and he won't let me work, and I hate CentralPerk!",
        "response":"Uh, to Stephanie Schiffer.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Ok. Um, so does your guitar have a strap?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm him.",
        "response":"Actually, uh, we're both the father.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's me.",
        "response":"I'm him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Oh. Mine does.  Stephanie knows all the chords.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok. Um, so does your guitar have a strap?",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok. Um, so does your guitar have a strap?",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Please tell me you know which one is our baby.",
        "response":"Well, well that one has ducks on his t-shirt, and this one has clowns. And Ben wasdefinitely wearing ducks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Or clowns. Oh, oh wait. That one's definitely Ben. Remember, he had that cute littlemole by his mouth.",
        "response":"Yeah?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Or clowns. Oh, oh wait. That one's definitely Ben. Remember, he had that cute littlemole by his mouth.",
        "response":"Yeah?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok.",
        "response":"Or clowns. Oh, oh wait. That one's definitely Ben. Remember, he had that cute littlemole by his mouth.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok.",
        "response":"Or clowns. Oh, oh wait. That one's definitely Ben. Remember, he had that cute littlemole by his mouth.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, well that one has ducks on his t-shirt, and this one has clowns. And Ben wasdefinitely wearing ducks.",
        "response":"Ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, well that one has ducks on his t-shirt, and this one has clowns. And Ben wasdefinitely wearing ducks.",
        "response":"Ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"BOTH : Oh, Ben! Hey, buddy!",
        "response":"Please tell me you know which one is our baby.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Actually, uh, we're both the father.",
        "response":"BOTH : Oh, Ben! Hey, buddy!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What're we gonna do? What're we gonna do?",
        "response":"Uh, uh, we'll flip for it. Ducks or clowns.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Hey, Ben, remember us? Ok, the mole came off.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Hey, Ben, remember us? Ok, the mole came off.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, Ben, remember us? Ok, the mole came off.",
        "response":"Ahh!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, Ben, remember us? Ok, the mole came off.",
        "response":"Ahh!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahh!",
        "response":"What're we gonna do? What're we gonna do?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahh!",
        "response":"What're we gonna do? What're we gonna do?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, uh, we'll flip for it. Ducks or clowns.",
        "response":"Oh, we're gonna flip for the baby?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, uh, we'll flip for it. Ducks or clowns.",
        "response":"Oh, we're gonna flip for the baby?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What're we gonna do? What're we gonna do?",
        "response":"Uh, uh, we'll flip for it. Ducks or clowns.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, we're gonna flip for the baby?",
        "response":"You got a better idea?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, we're gonna flip for the baby?",
        "response":"You got a better idea?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You got a better idea?",
        "response":"All right, call it in the air.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You got a better idea?",
        "response":"All right, call it in the air.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right, call it in the air.",
        "response":"Heads.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right, call it in the air.",
        "response":"Heads.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right. Ok, ok, uh, ducks is heads, because ducks have heads.",
        "response":"What kind of scary-ass clowns came to your birthday?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We have to assign heads to something.",
        "response":"Right. Ok, ok, uh, ducks is heads, because ducks have heads.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We have to assign heads to something.",
        "response":"Right. Ok, ok, uh, ducks is heads, because ducks have heads.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes! Whew!",
        "response":"We have to assign heads to something.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes! Whew!",
        "response":"We have to assign heads to something.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Heads it is.",
        "response":"Yes! Whew!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Heads it is.",
        "response":"Yes! Whew!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Heads.",
        "response":"Heads it is.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Heads.",
        "response":"Heads it is.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whoa, look at you, you did pretty well.",
        "response":"Eight dollars and 27 cents. But not really, 'cause I put in the first two, justto, you know, get the ball rolling, and to make myself feel better.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whoa, look at you, you did pretty well.",
        "response":"Eight dollars and 27 cents. But not really, 'cause I put in the first two, justto, you know, get the ball rolling, and to make myself feel better.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thank you.",
        "response":"Whoa, look at you, you did pretty well.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thank you.",
        "response":"Whoa, look at you, you did pretty well.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Here. I thought you might be cold.",
        "response":"Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Here. I thought you might be cold.",
        "response":"Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, hi.",
        "response":"Here. I thought you might be cold.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, hi.",
        "response":"Here. I thought you might be cold.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Oh, hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. This whole like playing-for-money thing is so not good for me. You know, Idon't know, when I sang &quot;Su-Su-Suicide&quot;, I got a dollar seventy-five. But then,&quot;Smelly Cat&quot;, I got 25 cents and a condom. So you know, now I just feel reallybad for Smelly Cat.",
        "response":"Well, you know, honey, I don't think everybody gets Smelly Cat. You know, I mean,if all you've ever actually had are healthy pets, then, whoosh!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. This whole like playing-for-money thing is so not good for me. You know, Idon't know, when I sang &quot;Su-Su-Suicide&quot;, I got a dollar seventy-five. But then,&quot;Smelly Cat&quot;, I got 25 cents and a condom. So you know, now I just feel reallybad for Smelly Cat.",
        "response":"Well, you know, honey, I don't think everybody gets Smelly Cat. You know, I mean,if all you've ever actually had are healthy pets, then, whoosh!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you know, honey, I don't think everybody gets Smelly Cat. You know, I mean,if all you've ever actually had are healthy pets, then, whoosh!",
        "response":"It's not even that. I used to do my songs because it made me happy, but now it'slike, it's just all about the money.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you know, honey, I don't think everybody gets Smelly Cat. You know, I mean,if all you've ever actually had are healthy pets, then, whoosh!",
        "response":"It's not even that. I used to do my songs because it made me happy, but now it'slike, it's just all about the money.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Do you?",
        "response":"No. This whole like playing-for-money thing is so not good for me. You know, Idon't know, when I sang &quot;Su-Su-Suicide&quot;, I got a dollar seventy-five. But then,&quot;Smelly Cat&quot;, I got 25 cents and a condom. So you know, now I just feel reallybad for Smelly Cat.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Do you?",
        "response":"No. This whole like playing-for-money thing is so not good for me. You know, Idon't know, when I sang &quot;Su-Su-Suicide&quot;, I got a dollar seventy-five. But then,&quot;Smelly Cat&quot;, I got 25 cents and a condom. So you know, now I just feel reallybad for Smelly Cat.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's not even that. I used to do my songs because it made me happy, but now it'slike, it's just all about the money.",
        "response":"Well, people missed you in there. And in fact, there was actually a request for&quot;Smelly Cat&quot;.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Eight dollars and 27 cents. But not really, 'cause I put in the first two, justto, you know, get the ball rolling, and to make myself feel better.",
        "response":"Do you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Eight dollars and 27 cents. But not really, 'cause I put in the first two, justto, you know, get the ball rolling, and to make myself feel better.",
        "response":"Do you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's not even that. I used to do my songs because it made me happy, but now it'slike, it's just all about the money.",
        "response":"Well, people missed you in there. And in fact, there was actually a request for&quot;Smelly Cat&quot;.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I just wanna thank you for being there for me today. And I'm sorry I,I almost brokeyour hand.",
        "response":"That's ok. I'm sorry I poisoned you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi. Uh, did I accidentally drop a condom in your case? It's kind of an emergency.",
        "response":"Yeah. Here you go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's ok. I'm sorry I poisoned you.",
        "response":"Yeah. Hey, remember the time I jammed that pencil into your hand?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's ok. I'm sorry I poisoned you.",
        "response":"Yeah. Hey, remember the time I jammed that pencil into your hand?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, people missed you in there. And in fact, there was actually a request for&quot;Smelly Cat&quot;.",
        "response":"Really? From who?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, people missed you in there. And in fact, there was actually a request for&quot;Smelly Cat&quot;.",
        "response":"Really? From who?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really? From who?",
        "response":"Well, from me. And I know it's not your big money song, but it's my favorite.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. Here you go.",
        "response":"Thanks a lot. Hey Christine, I got it!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wait, what about the time I hit you in the face with the Silvian's pumpkin?",
        "response":"Oh, man. Oh, remember when I stuck that broom in your bike spokes, and you flippedover and hit your head on the curb?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wait, what about the time I hit you in the face with the Silvian's pumpkin?",
        "response":"Oh, man. Oh, remember when I stuck that broom in your bike spokes, and you flippedover and hit your head on the curb?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, man. Oh, remember when I stuck that broom in your bike spokes, and you flippedover and hit your head on the curb?",
        "response":"No. But I remember people telling me about it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. Hey, remember the time I jammed that pencil into your hand?",
        "response":"Remember it? What do you think this is, a freckle?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. Hey, remember the time I jammed that pencil into your hand?",
        "response":"Remember it? What do you think this is, a freckle?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh.",
        "response":"Wait, what about the time I hit you in the face with the Silvian's pumpkin?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh.",
        "response":"Wait, what about the time I hit you in the face with the Silvian's pumpkin?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Remember it? What do you think this is, a freckle?",
        "response":"Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Remember it? What do you think this is, a freckle?",
        "response":"Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, man. Oh, remember when I stuck that broom in your bike spokes, and you flippedover and hit your head on the curb?",
        "response":"No. But I remember people telling me about it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. I hope she can kick his ass.",
        "response":"I'm gonna get a new band-aid. Hey, how 'bout the time I cut the legs off your MalibuKen?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. I hope she can kick his ass.",
        "response":"I'm gonna get a new band-aid. Hey, how 'bout the time I cut the legs off your MalibuKen?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm gonna get a new band-aid. Hey, how 'bout the time I cut the legs off your MalibuKen?",
        "response":"That was you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm gonna get a new band-aid. Hey, how 'bout the time I cut the legs off your MalibuKen?",
        "response":"That was you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. But I remember people telling me about it.",
        "response":"I hope Ben has a little sister.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. But I remember people telling me about it.",
        "response":"I hope Ben has a little sister.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I hope Ben has a little sister.",
        "response":"Yeah. I hope she can kick his ass.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I hope Ben has a little sister.",
        "response":"Yeah. I hope she can kick his ass.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm here. How's my little boy? Want Daddy to change your diaper? So, did you havefun with Uncle Joey and Uncle Chandler today?",
        "response":"Oh, yeah, he rode the bus today.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm here. How's my little boy? Want Daddy to change your diaper? So, did you havefun with Uncle Joey and Uncle Chandler today?",
        "response":"Oh, yeah, he rode the bus today.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes! There's still pie.",
        "response":"I'm here. How's my little boy? Want Daddy to change your diaper? So, did you havefun with Uncle Joey and Uncle Chandler today?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah, he rode the bus today.",
        "response":"Ohhh. Big boy, riding the bus--Hey, I have a question. How come it says Property ofHuman Services on his butt?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"They, uh, were infected. He wouldn't have made it.",
        "response":"Aw, my little nephew. Come here, little one. There's my little baby Ben. Hey, mylittle boy. Hey, he's not crying.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohhh. Big boy, riding the bus--Hey, I have a question. How come it says Property ofHuman Services on his butt?",
        "response":"You, you are gonna love this.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You, you are gonna love this.",
        "response":"Will you hold Ben for a sec? Come here. Come here.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That was you?",
        "response":"They, uh, were infected. He wouldn't have made it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That was you?",
        "response":"They, uh, were infected. He wouldn't have made it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Smelly cat, smelly cat, what are they feeding you?",
        "response":"No, no, no. I'm sorry. It's &quot;smelly cat, smel-ly cat&quot;.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Will you hold Ben for a sec? Come here. Come here.",
        "response":"Stay back, I've got kiwi. Run, Joey, Run!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, no. I'm sorry. It's &quot;smelly cat, smel-ly cat&quot;.",
        "response":"Smelly cat, smel-ly cat...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, no. I'm sorry. It's &quot;smelly cat, smel-ly cat&quot;.",
        "response":"Smelly cat, smel-ly cat...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You, you are gonna love this.",
        "response":"Will you hold Ben for a sec? Come here. Come here.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Smelly cat, smel-ly cat...",
        "response":"Better. Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Smelly cat, smel-ly cat...",
        "response":"Better. Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Better. Yeah.",
        "response":"Yeah?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Better. Yeah.",
        "response":"Yeah?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. From the top?",
        "response":"Ok, there is no top. That's the beauty of Smelly Cat. Um, why don't you justfollow me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, much better. And you know what, don't feel bad, because it's a hard song.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, much better. And you know what, don't feel bad, because it's a hard song.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah?",
        "response":"Yeah, much better. And you know what, don't feel bad, because it's a hard song.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah?",
        "response":"Yeah, much better. And you know what, don't feel bad, because it's a hard song.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You wanna try it again?",
        "response":"Yeah. From the top?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You wanna try it again?",
        "response":"Yeah. From the top?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"You wanna try it again?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"You wanna try it again?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Smelly Cat, Smelly Cat, what are they feeding you? Smelly Cat, Smelly Cat, it'snot your fault.",
        "response":"That's too much. Sorry.</font></p><p align=\"center\"><strong><font size=\"3\">END</font></strong></p><hr><p align=\"center\"><!--webbot bot=\"ImageMap\" startspanrectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/207rofo.htm\"rectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2.htm\"rectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/205fsae.htm\"src=\"www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/contrl08.gif\" width=\"194\" height=\"60\"alt=\"contrl08.gif \" --><MAP NAME=\"FrontPageMap0\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"139, 3, 197, 84\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/207rofo.htm\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"71, 2, 130, 84\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2.htm\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"1, 3, 56, 80\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/205fsae.htm\"></MAP><img src=\"contrl08.gif\" width=\"194\" height=\"60\" alt=\"contrl08.gif \" usemap=\"#FrontPageMap0\"><!--webbot bot=\"ImageMap\" i-checksum=\"20769\" endspan--></p><hr><center><img src=\"/cgi-bin/counter/206\"></center><hr></body></html>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well it couldn't have been worse. A woman literally passed <b>through</b> me. OK, sowhat is it, am I hideously unattractive?",
        "response":"No, you are not, you are very attractive. You know what, I go through the exact samething. Every time I put on a little weight, I start questioning everyting.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, how was the party?",
        "response":"Well it couldn't have been worse. A woman literally passed <b>through</b> me. OK, sowhat is it, am I hideously unattractive?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. From the top?",
        "response":"Ok, there is no top. That's the beauty of Smelly Cat. Um, why don't you justfollow me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, what is it about me? Do I not look fun enough? Is there something. . .repellant. . . about me?",
        "response":"So, how was the party?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, there is no top. That's the beauty of Smelly Cat. Um, why don't you justfollow me?",
        "response":"Ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, there is no top. That's the beauty of Smelly Cat. Um, why don't you justfollow me?",
        "response":"Ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mmmm hmmm.",
        "response":"Smelly Cat, Smelly Cat, what are they feeding you? Smelly Cat, Smelly Cat, it'snot your fault.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok.",
        "response":"Mmmm hmmm.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, you are not, you are very attractive. You know what, I go through the exact samething. Every time I put on a little weight, I start questioning everyting.",
        "response":"Woah, woah, I've put on a little weight?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, you are not, you are very attractive. You know what, I go through the exact samething. Every time I put on a little weight, I start questioning everyting.",
        "response":"Woah, woah, I've put on a little weight?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chandler, I'm unemployed and in dire need of a project. Ya wanna work out? I canremake you.",
        "response":"Oh, you know, I would, but that might get in the way of my lying around time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, let's do it. [Monica looks at him funny] What?",
        "response":"Nothing, just never seen you in little stretchy pants before.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nothing, just never seen you in little stretchy pants before.",
        "response":"And we're changing. [jogs back in his apartment]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, you know, I would, but that might get in the way of my lying around time.",
        "response":"Please.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Woah, woah, I've put on a little weight?",
        "response":"No, not wieght... y'know, more like insulation.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon give me five more. Five more.",
        "response":"[weakly] No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[weakly] No.",
        "response":"Five more and I'll flash you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Scene: Central Perk. Chandler and Joey are sitting on the couch. Rachel is working.]",
        "response":"[slowly lifts coffee cup to his mouth] Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow. [slowly sets thecup back down] Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow. [Joey intercepts the cup and puts it down for him].She's insane, the woman is insane. It's before work, it's after work, it's during work.She's got me doing butt clenches at my desk. And now, they won't bring me my mail anymore.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, I, y'know, I don't mind taking it slow, I like him a lot, y'know he's reallyinteresting and he's really sweet and why won't he give it up?",
        "response":"Maybe he, uhh... drives his car on the other side of the road, if ya know what Imean.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sorry Phoebs.",
        "response":"Look, I, y'know, I don't mind taking it slow, I like him a lot, y'know he's reallyinteresting and he's really sweet and why won't he give it up?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"One. . . two. . . two and a half. OK, just show me one of them.",
        "response":"[Scene: Central Perk. Chandler and Joey are sitting on the couch. Rachel is working.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, um, it was nice. Took him to a romantic restraunt, ordered champagne, nice.",
        "response":"The guy still won't put out, huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Five more and I'll flash you.",
        "response":"One. . . two. . . two and a half. OK, just show me one of them.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The guy still won't put out, huh?",
        "response":"Nope. Zilch, nothin', uh-uh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nope. Zilch, nothin', uh-uh.",
        "response":"Sorry Phoebs.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[weakly] No.",
        "response":"Five more and I'll flash you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oohh, um, no, I don't think that's the problem. 'Cause we went, um, dancing theother night and the way he held me so close, and the way he was looking into my eyes Ijust like... definitely felt something.",
        "response":"Yeah, but how much can you tell from a look?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe he's. . . gay.",
        "response":"Oohh, um, no, I don't think that's the problem. 'Cause we went, um, dancing theother night and the way he held me so close, and the way he was looking into my eyes Ijust like... definitely felt something.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe he, uhh... drives his car on the other side of the road, if ya know what Imean.",
        "response":"No, whad'ya mean? He's not British.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe he, uhh... drives his car on the other side of the road, if ya know what Imean.",
        "response":"No, whad'ya mean? He's not British.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? [looks, feigns indifference] C'mon you guys, I don't care, I have a datetonight.",
        "response":"Woah, woah, woah, you have a date?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, but how much can you tell from a look?",
        "response":"No, I felt it on my hip. You could tell.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Woah, woah, woah, you have a date?",
        "response":"Yeah, Monica's settin' me up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, whad'ya mean? He's not British.",
        "response":"Maybe he's. . . gay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, whad'ya mean? He's not British.",
        "response":"Maybe he's. . . gay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So you really OK about all this?",
        "response":"Oh yeah, c'mon, I'm movin' on. He can press her up against that window as much as hewants. For all I care, he can throw her through the damn thing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh what, my whole insane jealousy thing? Well, y'know, as much fun as that was, I'vedecided to opt for sanity.",
        "response":"So you really OK about all this?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But uh, uh, what about uh, Ross and uh. . .?",
        "response":"Oh what, my whole insane jealousy thing? Well, y'know, as much fun as that was, I'vedecided to opt for sanity.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, Monica, I figured I'd come by tomorrow morning and pick up Fluffy's old cat toy,OK?",
        "response":"Only if you say his full name.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Oh, Monica, I figured I'd come by tomorrow morning and pick up Fluffy's old cat toy,OK?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, Monica's settin' me up.",
        "response":"But uh, uh, what about uh, Ross and uh. . .?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, Monica's settin' me up.",
        "response":"But uh, uh, what about uh, Ross and uh. . .?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Woah, woah, woah, you have a date?",
        "response":"Yeah, Monica's settin' me up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi guys.",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Only if you say his full name.",
        "response":"[reluctantly] Can I come over tomorrow and pick up Fluffy Meowington's cat toy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Only if you say his full name.",
        "response":"[reluctantly] Can I come over tomorrow and pick up Fluffy Meowington's cat toy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[reluctantly] Can I come over tomorrow and pick up Fluffy Meowington's cat toy.",
        "response":"Alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, actually, we're getting a cat.",
        "response":"Together?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh huh.",
        "response":"Both of you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh huh.",
        "response":"Both of you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Together?",
        "response":"Uh huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Together?",
        "response":"Uh huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Both of you?",
        "response":"Yep.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hopefully.",
        "response":"Well. [looks at watch] Woah, look at that! I gotta go, I gotta date. With a man. Um,OK, you guys have a really, uh, have a really good night and you two have a, uh, have a,uh, really good cat. [she leaves carrying her tray then comes back in] OK, we're notsupposed to take these when we leave.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, we figure it'll live with Ross half the time, and with me half the time.",
        "response":"Ohh, well, isn't that just lovely. That's something the two of you will be able toenjoy for a really, really, really, really, really long time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know if Monica told you but this is the first date I've gone on since mydivorce so, if I seem a little nervous, I am.",
        "response":"[distracted] How long do cats live?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohh, well, isn't that just lovely. That's something the two of you will be able toenjoy for a really, really, really, really, really long time.",
        "response":"Hopefully.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Together.",
        "response":"Yeah, we figure it'll live with Ross half the time, and with me half the time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[distracted] How long do cats live?",
        "response":"[confused] I'm sorry?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[distracted] How long do cats live?",
        "response":"[confused] I'm sorry?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Both of you?",
        "response":"Yep.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yep.",
        "response":"Together.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Cats, how long do they live figuring you don't... y'know, throw 'em under a bus orsomething?",
        "response":"Um, maybe 15, 16 years.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Cats, how long do they live figuring you don't... y'know, throw 'em under a bus orsomething?",
        "response":"Um, maybe 15, 16 years.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[confused] I'm sorry?",
        "response":"Cats, how long do they live figuring you don't... y'know, throw 'em under a bus orsomething?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[confused] I'm sorry?",
        "response":"Cats, how long do they live figuring you don't... y'know, throw 'em under a bus orsomething?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, maybe 15, 16 years.",
        "response":"That's just great. [she picks up her champagne and starts drinking]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, maybe 15, 16 years.",
        "response":"That's just great. [she picks up her champagne and starts drinking]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's just great. [she picks up her champagne and starts drinking]",
        "response":"Um, cheers.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's just great. [she picks up her champagne and starts drinking]",
        "response":"Um, cheers.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, cheers.",
        "response":"Oh, right, clink. [downs her glass]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Monica told you I was cuter that this, didn't she?",
        "response":"Oh, no, Michael, it's not you. I'm sorry, it's just, it's this thing. It's probablynot as bad as it sounds but this friend of mine is, is getting a cat with his girlfriend.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Monica told you I was cuter that this, didn't she?",
        "response":"Oh, no, Michael, it's not you. I'm sorry, it's just, it's this thing. It's probablynot as bad as it sounds but this friend of mine is, is getting a cat with his girlfriend.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, no, Michael, it's not you. I'm sorry, it's just, it's this thing. It's probablynot as bad as it sounds but this friend of mine is, is getting a cat with his girlfriend.",
        "response":"Oh, that does sound. . .Ahh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, no, Michael, it's not you. I'm sorry, it's just, it's this thing. It's probablynot as bad as it sounds but this friend of mine is, is getting a cat with his girlfriend.",
        "response":"Oh, that does sound. . .Ahh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, right, clink. [downs her glass]",
        "response":"Monica told you I was cuter that this, didn't she?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, right, clink. [downs her glass]",
        "response":"Monica told you I was cuter that this, didn't she?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that does sound. . .Ahh.",
        "response":"I mean he just started going out with her.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that does sound. . .Ahh.",
        "response":"I mean he just started going out with her.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, cheers.",
        "response":"Oh, right, clink. [downs her glass]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Is this guy, uhh, an old boyfriend?",
        "response":"Ah, hah-hah-hah-ho, yeah, he wishes. Oh, I'm sorry, look at me. OK, Michael, let'stalk about you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Is this guy, uhh, an old boyfriend?",
        "response":"Ah, hah-hah-hah-ho, yeah, he wishes. Oh, I'm sorry, look at me. OK, Michael, let'stalk about you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ah, hah-hah-hah-ho, yeah, he wishes. Oh, I'm sorry, look at me. OK, Michael, let'stalk about you.",
        "response":"Alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ah, hah-hah-hah-ho, yeah, he wishes. Oh, I'm sorry, look at me. OK, Michael, let'stalk about you.",
        "response":"Alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Why Scott doesn't want to sleep with me. It's 'cause I'm not sexy enough.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I mean he just started going out with her.",
        "response":"Is this guy, uhh, an old boyfriend?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I mean he just started going out with her.",
        "response":"Is this guy, uhh, an old boyfriend?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright.",
        "response":"OK, OK. So, you ever get a pet with a girlfriend?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, I figured it out.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why Scott doesn't want to sleep with me. It's 'cause I'm not sexy enough.",
        "response":"Phoebe, that's crazy. When I first met you, you know what I said to Chandler? Isaid, &quot;Excellent butt, great rack.&quot;",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why Scott doesn't want to sleep with me. It's 'cause I'm not sexy enough.",
        "response":"Phoebe, that's crazy. When I first met you, you know what I said to Chandler? Isaid, &quot;Excellent butt, great rack.&quot;",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[obviously drunk] I mean, it's a cat, y'know, it's a <b>cat</b>. Why can't they getone of those bugs, y'know, one of those fruitflies, those things that live for like a dayor something? [belligerently] What're they called, what're they called, what're theycalled?",
        "response":"Fruitflies?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebe, that's crazy. When I first met you, you know what I said to Chandler? Isaid, &quot;Excellent butt, great rack.&quot;",
        "response":"Really? That's so sweet. I mean, I'm officially offended but, sweet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebe, that's crazy. When I first met you, you know what I said to Chandler? Isaid, &quot;Excellent butt, great rack.&quot;",
        "response":"Really? That's so sweet. I mean, I'm officially offended but, sweet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really? That's so sweet. I mean, I'm officially offended but, sweet.",
        "response":"Phoebs look, if you want to know what the deal is, you're just gonna have to askhim.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really? That's so sweet. I mean, I'm officially offended but, sweet.",
        "response":"Phoebs look, if you want to know what the deal is, you're just gonna have to askhim.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebs look, if you want to know what the deal is, you're just gonna have to askhim.",
        "response":"You're right, you're right. Ah, you are so yumm. [they hug]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Why Scott doesn't want to sleep with me. It's 'cause I'm not sexy enough.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, look at me, look at me. Oh, I'm on a date with a really great guy, all I canthink about is Ross and his cat and his... Julie. I just want to get over him. gosh, whycan't I do that?",
        "response":"Oy. Look, I've been through a divorce, trust me you're gonna be fine. You just can'tsee it now because you haven't had any closure.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, look at me, look at me. Oh, I'm on a date with a really great guy, all I canthink about is Ross and his cat and his... Julie. I just want to get over him. gosh, whycan't I do that?",
        "response":"Oy. Look, I've been through a divorce, trust me you're gonna be fine. You just can'tsee it now because you haven't had any closure.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, I am, but only because for the last hour and a half I've been playing themovie <i>Diner</i> in my head.",
        "response":"Oh, look at me, look at me. Oh, I'm on a date with a really great guy, all I canthink about is Ross and his cat and his... Julie. I just want to get over him. gosh, whycan't I do that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, I am, but only because for the last hour and a half I've been playing themovie <i>Diner</i> in my head.",
        "response":"Oh, look at me, look at me. Oh, I'm on a date with a really great guy, all I canthink about is Ross and his cat and his... Julie. I just want to get over him. gosh, whycan't I do that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oy. Look, I've been through a divorce, trust me you're gonna be fine. You just can'tsee it now because you haven't had any closure.",
        "response":"Yeah! Closure. That's what it is, that's what I need. God, you're brilliant! Whydidn't I think of that? How do I get that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, you're not having fun, are you?",
        "response":"No, no, I am, but only because for the last hour and a half I've been playing themovie <i>Diner</i> in my head.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, you're not having fun, are you?",
        "response":"No, no, I am, but only because for the last hour and a half I've been playing themovie <i>Diner</i> in my head.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No! No dessert, just a check, please.",
        "response":"Oh, you're not having fun, are you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Fruitflies?",
        "response":"Yes! Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you know, there's no one way really, it's just, you know, whatever it takes sothat you can finally say to him, &quot;I'm over you.&quot;",
        "response":"Closure, that's what it is. Closure. [she looks around the restaurant, spotting aguy with a cellular phone] Hello, excuse me. Excuse me, hel. . . woo [she almost falls outof her chair]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oy. Look, I've been through a divorce, trust me you're gonna be fine. You just can'tsee it now because you haven't had any closure.",
        "response":"Yeah! Closure. That's what it is, that's what I need. God, you're brilliant! Whydidn't I think of that? How do I get that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah! Closure. That's what it is, that's what I need. God, you're brilliant! Whydidn't I think of that? How do I get that?",
        "response":"Well, you know, there's no one way really, it's just, you know, whatever it takes sothat you can finally say to him, &quot;I'm over you.&quot;",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah! Closure. That's what it is, that's what I need. God, you're brilliant! Whydidn't I think of that? How do I get that?",
        "response":"Well, you know, there's no one way really, it's just, you know, whatever it takes sothat you can finally say to him, &quot;I'm over you.&quot;",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Closure, that's what it is. Closure. [she looks around the restaurant, spotting aguy with a cellular phone] Hello, excuse me. Excuse me, hel. . . woo [she almost falls outof her chair]",
        "response":"Hang on.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hang on.",
        "response":"Hello, excuse me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hang on.",
        "response":"Hello, excuse me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello, excuse me.",
        "response":"What.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello, excuse me.",
        "response":"What.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can see that. I... just one phone call, I'll be very quick, I'll even pay for itmyself. [man is still reluctant] OK, you're bein' a little weird about your phone.",
        "response":"Alright, fine. [on the phone] I'll call you back. [hands the phone to her]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can see that. I... just one phone call, I'll be very quick, I'll even pay for itmyself. [man is still reluctant] OK, you're bein' a little weird about your phone.",
        "response":"Alright, fine. [on the phone] I'll call you back. [hands the phone to her]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm talkin'!",
        "response":"I can see that. I... just one phone call, I'll be very quick, I'll even pay for itmyself. [man is still reluctant] OK, you're bein' a little weird about your phone.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm talkin'!",
        "response":"I can see that. I... just one phone call, I'll be very quick, I'll even pay for itmyself. [man is still reluctant] OK, you're bein' a little weird about your phone.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, fine. [on the phone] I'll call you back. [hands the phone to her]",
        "response":"Thank you. OK. [dials] [to Michael] Machine. Just waiting for the beep.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi, I'm sorry, I need to borrow your phone for just one minute.",
        "response":"I'm talkin'!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi, I'm sorry, I need to borrow your phone for just one minute.",
        "response":"I'm talkin'!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What.",
        "response":"Hi, I'm sorry, I need to borrow your phone for just one minute.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What.",
        "response":"Hi, I'm sorry, I need to borrow your phone for just one minute.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, stop.",
        "response":"No, c'mon, we can't stop, c'mon, we've got three more pounds to go. I am the energytrain and you are on board. Woo-woo, woo-woo, woo-woo [Chandler walks out of theapartment, leaving Monica] Woo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, no, no, no, no [opens door to Monica] No. Monica, it's Sunday morning. I'mnot running on a Sunday.",
        "response":"Why not?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Because it's Sunday. It's God's day.",
        "response":"OK, if you say stop, then we stop.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Because it's Sunday. It's God's day.",
        "response":"OK, if you say stop, then we stop.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why not?",
        "response":"Because it's Sunday. It's God's day.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why not?",
        "response":"Because it's Sunday. It's God's day.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, if you say stop, then we stop.",
        "response":"OK, stop.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, if you say stop, then we stop.",
        "response":"OK, stop.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Rach.",
        "response":"Ahhhh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Rachel looks at Ross as though she remembers something, but can't place what it is.]</p><p>ROSS: Wow, well uh, uh, actually, Julie's downstairs getting a cab, I just need the cattoy, did Monica say. . . What? Why, why are you looking at me like that?",
        "response":"I don't know, I, I feel like I had a dream about you last night but I, I don'tremember.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Umm, I think there was a restaurant... I know there was wine. . .",
        "response":"[Rachel looks at Ross as though she remembers something, but can't place what it is.]</p><p>ROSS: Wow, well uh, uh, actually, Julie's downstairs getting a cab, I just need the cattoy, did Monica say. . . What? Why, why are you looking at me like that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know, I, I feel like I had a dream about you last night but I, I don'tremember.",
        "response":"OK. Oh, oh, oh. [runs over and picks up the cat toy]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK. Oh, oh, oh. [runs over and picks up the cat toy]",
        "response":"Did we speak on the phone last night? Did you call me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK. Oh, oh, oh. [runs over and picks up the cat toy]",
        "response":"Did we speak on the phone last night? Did you call me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did we speak on the phone last night? Did you call me?",
        "response":"No, I stayed at Julie's last night.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh. And how was the date?",
        "response":"Umm, I think there was a restaurant... I know there was wine. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahhhh.",
        "response":"Oh. And how was the date?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahhhh.",
        "response":"Oh. And how was the date?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rach, I got a message from you. [pauses] Who's Michael?",
        "response":"[Rachel comes out of her room, suddenly she remembers leaving the message.]</p><p>RACH: Oh my God. Oh my God Ross, no, hang up the phone, give me the phone Ross, give methe phone, give me the phone, give me the. . . [jumps the couch and lands on Ross's back,finally getting the phone from him. Ross has a confused expression on his face.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, actually I haven't even been home yet. Do you mind if I check my messages?",
        "response":"Oh yeah, go ahead. [Rachel walks in her room. Ross picks up the phone and dials hismachine to check his messages.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, actually I haven't even been home yet. Do you mind if I check my messages?",
        "response":"Oh yeah, go ahead. [Rachel walks in her room. Ross picks up the phone and dials hismachine to check his messages.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah, go ahead. [Rachel walks in her room. Ross picks up the phone and dials hismachine to check his messages.]",
        "response":"Rach, I got a message from you. [pauses] Who's Michael?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh.",
        "response":"Oh, actually I haven't even been home yet. Do you mind if I check my messages?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh.",
        "response":"Oh, actually I haven't even been home yet. Do you mind if I check my messages?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did we speak on the phone last night? Did you call me?",
        "response":"No, I stayed at Julie's last night.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I stayed at Julie's last night.",
        "response":"Huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I stayed at Julie's last night.",
        "response":"Huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Rachel comes out of her room, suddenly she remembers leaving the message.]</p><p>RACH: Oh my God. Oh my God Ross, no, hang up the phone, give me the phone Ross, give methe phone, give me the phone, give me the. . . [jumps the couch and lands on Ross's back,finally getting the phone from him. Ross has a confused expression on his face.]",
        "response":"You're over me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"When, when were you... under me? Rach. Rachel do you, I mean, were you, uh. . .What?",
        "response":"Ohh, OK, OK, OK, well, basically, lately, I've uh, I've uh, sort of had feelings foryou.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohh, ohh.",
        "response":"When, when were you... under me? Rach. Rachel do you, I mean, were you, uh. . .What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohh, ohh.",
        "response":"When, when were you... under me? Rach. Rachel do you, I mean, were you, uh. . .What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohhhhhhhh God. [climbs off his back]",
        "response":"Wha... you're uh, you're, you're over me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohhhhhhhh God. [climbs off his back]",
        "response":"Wha... you're uh, you're, you're over me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're over me?",
        "response":"Ohhhhhhhh God. [climbs off his back]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wha... you're uh, you're, you're over me?",
        "response":"Ohh, ohh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wha... you're uh, you're, you're over me?",
        "response":"Ohh, ohh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"When, when were you... under me? Rach. Rachel do you, I mean, were you, uh. . .What?",
        "response":"Ohh, OK, OK, OK, well, basically, lately, I've uh, I've uh, sort of had feelings foryou.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, what, so? You had feelings for me first.",
        "response":"Woah. Huh. You know about my, I mean, you know I had... you know?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, what, so? You had feelings for me first.",
        "response":"Woah. Huh. You know about my, I mean, you know I had... you know?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohh, OK, OK, OK, well, basically, lately, I've uh, I've uh, sort of had feelings foryou.",
        "response":"You've had feelings for me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohh, OK, OK, OK, well, basically, lately, I've uh, I've uh, sort of had feelings foryou.",
        "response":"You've had feelings for me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Woah. Huh. You know about my, I mean, you know I had... you know?",
        "response":"Chandler told me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Woah. Huh. You know about my, I mean, you know I had... you know?",
        "response":"Chandler told me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You've had feelings for me?",
        "response":"Yeah, what, so? You had feelings for me first.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You've had feelings for me?",
        "response":"Yeah, what, so? You had feelings for me first.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Meeting Julie.",
        "response":"Julie. Julie. That. Oh God. Julie, right. OK, I need to lie down. No, ya know, I'mgonna stand. I'm gonna stand, I'm gonna walk, I'm walkin' and I am standing. OK so you uh,and now wha... and now, now, now you're over me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chandler. When did he... when did he... when did he?",
        "response":"When you were in China.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chandler. When did he... when did he... when did he?",
        "response":"When you were in China.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chandler told me.",
        "response":"Chandler. When did he... when did he... when did he?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chandler told me.",
        "response":"Chandler. When did he... when did he... when did he?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"When you were in China.",
        "response":"China.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"When you were in China.",
        "response":"China.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"China.",
        "response":"Meeting Julie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"China.",
        "response":"Meeting Julie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Julie. Julie. That. Oh God. Julie, right. OK, I need to lie down. No, ya know, I'mgonna stand. I'm gonna stand, I'm gonna walk, I'm walkin' and I am standing. OK so you uh,and now wha... and now, now, now you're over me?",
        "response":"Are you over me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Meeting Julie.",
        "response":"Julie. Julie. That. Oh God. Julie, right. OK, I need to lie down. No, ya know, I'mgonna stand. I'm gonna stand, I'm gonna walk, I'm walkin' and I am standing. OK so you uh,and now wha... and now, now, now you're over me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wait, so, you're going?",
        "response":"Well, OK, I uh, I have to. I can't deal with this right now. I mean, I've uh,y'know, I've got a cab, I've got a girlfriend, I'm... I'm gonna go get a cat.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wait, so, you're going?",
        "response":"Well, OK, I uh, I have to. I can't deal with this right now. I mean, I've uh,y'know, I've got a cab, I've got a girlfriend, I'm... I'm gonna go get a cat.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, OK, I uh, I have to. I can't deal with this right now. I mean, I've uh,y'know, I've got a cab, I've got a girlfriend, I'm... I'm gonna go get a cat.",
        "response":"OK, OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, OK, I uh, I have to. I can't deal with this right now. I mean, I've uh,y'know, I've got a cab, I've got a girlfriend, I'm... I'm gonna go get a cat.",
        "response":"OK, OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[doorbell buzzes] That's, that's Julie. Ju... Julie, Julie. [talks on intercom] HiJulie.",
        "response":"[over intercom] Hi honey, I've got a cab waiting.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[over intercom] Hi honey, I've got a cab waiting.",
        "response":"[perky] I'll be right down.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[perky] I'll be right down.",
        "response":"Wait, so, you're going?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't find the remote. [Phoebe turns off the TV] Thank you.",
        "response":"So, Scott asked me to come over for lunch today and I did.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't find the remote. [Phoebe turns off the TV] Thank you.",
        "response":"So, Scott asked me to come over for lunch today and I did.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How come you're watching a rabbi play electric guitar?",
        "response":"I can't find the remote. [Phoebe turns off the TV] Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How come you're watching a rabbi play electric guitar?",
        "response":"I can't find the remote. [Phoebe turns off the TV] Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Phoebs.",
        "response":"How come you're watching a rabbi play electric guitar?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Phoebs.",
        "response":"How come you're watching a rabbi play electric guitar?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, Scott asked me to come over for lunch today and I did.",
        "response":"And?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Joey.",
        "response":"Hey Phoebs.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, OK.",
        "response":"Cat. [leaves]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And we did.",
        "response":"All right Phoebs, way to go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And we did.",
        "response":"All right Phoebs, way to go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right Phoebs, way to go.",
        "response":"Yay me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right Phoebs, way to go.",
        "response":"Yay me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yay me.",
        "response":"So, so how did it happen?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yay me.",
        "response":"So, so how did it happen?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, Scott asked me to come over for lunch today and I did.",
        "response":"And?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And?",
        "response":"And we did.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And?",
        "response":"And we did.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And what did he say?",
        "response":"He said that, um, he understands how sex can be like, a very emotional thing for awoman and he was just afraid that I was gonna get all, y'know, like, 'ohh, is he gonnacall me the next day' and, y'know, 'where is this going' and, ya know, blah-la-la-la-la.So he said he wanted to hold off until he was prepared to be really serious.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And what did he say?",
        "response":"He said that, um, he understands how sex can be like, a very emotional thing for awoman and he was just afraid that I was gonna get all, y'know, like, 'ohh, is he gonnacall me the next day' and, y'know, 'where is this going' and, ya know, blah-la-la-la-la.So he said he wanted to hold off until he was prepared to be really serious.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He said that, um, he understands how sex can be like, a very emotional thing for awoman and he was just afraid that I was gonna get all, y'know, like, 'ohh, is he gonnacall me the next day' and, y'know, 'where is this going' and, ya know, blah-la-la-la-la.So he said he wanted to hold off until he was prepared to be really serious.",
        "response":"Wow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He said that, um, he understands how sex can be like, a very emotional thing for awoman and he was just afraid that I was gonna get all, y'know, like, 'ohh, is he gonnacall me the next day' and, y'know, 'where is this going' and, ya know, blah-la-la-la-la.So he said he wanted to hold off until he was prepared to be really serious.",
        "response":"Wow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow.",
        "response":"Yeah, so I said, &quot;OK, relax please,&quot; y'know, I mean, sex can be just abouttwo people right there in the moment, y'know, it's, if he wants to see me again he cancall and if not, that's fine too. So after a looooot of talking. . . I convinced him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, so how did it happen?",
        "response":"Well, I finally took your advice and asked him what was going on.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, so how did it happen?",
        "response":"Well, I finally took your advice and asked him what was going on.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I finally took your advice and asked him what was going on.",
        "response":"And what did he say?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I finally took your advice and asked him what was going on.",
        "response":"And what did he say?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, so I said, &quot;OK, relax please,&quot; y'know, I mean, sex can be just abouttwo people right there in the moment, y'know, it's, if he wants to see me again he cancall and if not, that's fine too. So after a looooot of talking. . . I convinced him.",
        "response":"Let me get this straight. He got you to beg to sleep with him, he got you to say henever has to call you again, and he got you thinking this was a great idea.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, so I said, &quot;OK, relax please,&quot; y'know, I mean, sex can be just abouttwo people right there in the moment, y'know, it's, if he wants to see me again he cancall and if not, that's fine too. So after a looooot of talking. . . I convinced him.",
        "response":"Let me get this straight. He got you to beg to sleep with him, he got you to say henever has to call you again, and he got you thinking this was a great idea.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow.",
        "response":"Yeah, so I said, &quot;OK, relax please,&quot; y'know, I mean, sex can be just abouttwo people right there in the moment, y'know, it's, if he wants to see me again he cancall and if not, that's fine too. So after a looooot of talking. . . I convinced him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Let me get this straight. He got you to beg to sleep with him, he got you to say henever has to call you again, and he got you thinking this was a great idea.",
        "response":"Um-hum.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Let me get this straight. He got you to beg to sleep with him, he got you to say henever has to call you again, and he got you thinking this was a great idea.",
        "response":"Um-hum.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I didn't get a cat.",
        "response":"Oh, that's um, interesting.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I didn't get a cat.",
        "response":"Oh, that's um, interesting.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"I didn't get a cat.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um-hum.",
        "response":"This man is my God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no it's not interesting. OK, it's very, very not interesting. In fact it'sactually 100 percent completely opposite of interesting.",
        "response":"Alright, I got it Ross.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no it's not interesting. OK, it's very, very not interesting. In fact it'sactually 100 percent completely opposite of interesting.",
        "response":"Alright, I got it Ross.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that's um, interesting.",
        "response":"No, no it's not interesting. OK, it's very, very not interesting. In fact it'sactually 100 percent completely opposite of interesting.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that's um, interesting.",
        "response":"No, no it's not interesting. OK, it's very, very not interesting. In fact it'sactually 100 percent completely opposite of interesting.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, I got it Ross.",
        "response":"You had no right to tell me you ever had feelings for me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, I got it Ross.",
        "response":"You had no right to tell me you ever had feelings for me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[hurt] What?",
        "response":"I was doing great with Julie before I found out about you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You had no right to tell me you ever had feelings for me.",
        "response":"[hurt] What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You had no right to tell me you ever had feelings for me.",
        "response":"[hurt] What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, I was doin' great before I found out about you. You think it's easy for me tosee you with Julie?",
        "response":"Then you should have said something before I met her.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, I was doin' great before I found out about you. You think it's easy for me tosee you with Julie?",
        "response":"Then you should have said something before I met her.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I was doing great with Julie before I found out about you.",
        "response":"Hey, I was doin' great before I found out about you. You think it's easy for me tosee you with Julie?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I was doing great with Julie before I found out about you.",
        "response":"Hey, I was doin' great before I found out about you. You think it's easy for me tosee you with Julie?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Then you should have said something before I met her.",
        "response":"I didn't know then. And how come you never said anything to me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Then you should have said something before I met her.",
        "response":"I didn't know then. And how come you never said anything to me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I didn't know then. And how come you never said anything to me.",
        "response":"There was never a good time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I didn't know then. And how come you never said anything to me.",
        "response":"There was never a good time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[hurt] What?",
        "response":"I was doing great with Julie before I found out about you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The point is I... I don't need this right now, OK. It, it's too late, I'm withsomebody else, I'm happy. This ship has sailed.",
        "response":"Yeah, what're you saying, you just sort of put away feelings or whatever the hell itwas you felt for me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right, you, you only had a year. We only hung out every night.",
        "response":"Not, not, not <b>every night</b>. You know, and... and it's not like I didn't try,Rachel, but things got in the way, y'know? Like, like Italian guys or ex-fiances or, or,or Italian guys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right, you, you only had a year. We only hung out every night.",
        "response":"Not, not, not <b>every night</b>. You know, and... and it's not like I didn't try,Rachel, but things got in the way, y'know? Like, like Italian guys or ex-fiances or, or,or Italian guys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Not, not, not <b>every night</b>. You know, and... and it's not like I didn't try,Rachel, but things got in the way, y'know? Like, like Italian guys or ex-fiances or, or,or Italian guys.",
        "response":"Hey, there was one Italian guy, OK, and do you even have a point?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Not, not, not <b>every night</b>. You know, and... and it's not like I didn't try,Rachel, but things got in the way, y'know? Like, like Italian guys or ex-fiances or, or,or Italian guys.",
        "response":"Hey, there was one Italian guy, OK, and do you even have a point?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, there was one Italian guy, OK, and do you even have a point?",
        "response":"The point is I... I don't need this right now, OK. It, it's too late, I'm withsomebody else, I'm happy. This ship has sailed.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, there was one Italian guy, OK, and do you even have a point?",
        "response":"The point is I... I don't need this right now, OK. It, it's too late, I'm withsomebody else, I'm happy. This ship has sailed.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"There was never a good time.",
        "response":"Right, you, you only had a year. We only hung out every night.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"There was never a good time.",
        "response":"Right, you, you only had a year. We only hung out every night.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The point is I... I don't need this right now, OK. It, it's too late, I'm withsomebody else, I'm happy. This ship has sailed.",
        "response":"Yeah, what're you saying, you just sort of put away feelings or whatever the hell itwas you felt for me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, what're you saying, you just sort of put away feelings or whatever the hell itwas you felt for me?",
        "response":"Hey, I've been doin' it since the ninth grade, I've gotten pretty damn good at it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, what're you saying, you just sort of put away feelings or whatever the hell itwas you felt for me?",
        "response":"Hey, I've been doin' it since the ninth grade, I've gotten pretty damn good at it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, I've been doin' it since the ninth grade, I've gotten pretty damn good at it.",
        "response":"Alright, fine, you go ahead and you do that, alright Ross.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, I've been doin' it since the ninth grade, I've gotten pretty damn good at it.",
        "response":"Alright, fine, you go ahead and you do that, alright Ross.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, fine, you go ahead and you do that, alright Ross.",
        "response":"Fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, fine, you go ahead and you do that, alright Ross.",
        "response":"Fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Fine.",
        "response":"'Cause I don't need your stupid ship.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Fine.",
        "response":"'Cause I don't need your stupid ship.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No way, with one pound to go, c'mon. We're workin', we're movin', we're in the zonewe're groovin'.",
        "response":"OK, I don't, I don't mind the last pound. OK, in fact I kind of like the last pound.OK, so don't make me do anything that I'll regret.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No way, with one pound to go, c'mon. We're workin', we're movin', we're in the zonewe're groovin'.",
        "response":"OK, I don't, I don't mind the last pound. OK, in fact I kind of like the last pound.OK, so don't make me do anything that I'll regret.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, I don't, I don't mind the last pound. OK, in fact I kind of like the last pound.OK, so don't make me do anything that I'll regret.",
        "response":"Ooh, what'cha gonna do, fat boy, huh? What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, I don't, I don't mind the last pound. OK, in fact I kind of like the last pound.OK, so don't make me do anything that I'll regret.",
        "response":"Ooh, what'cha gonna do, fat boy, huh? What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Good.",
        "response":"Good. [Ross leaves] </p><p>[Rachel gets up and opens the door, yelling after him.]</p><p align=\"left\">RACH: And ya know what, now I've got closure.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh, what'cha gonna do, fat boy, huh? What?",
        "response":"Nothing, except tell you, uh, I think it's wonderful how much energy you have.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Monica, it's 6:30 in the morning. We're not working out, it's over.",
        "response":"No way, with one pound to go, c'mon. We're workin', we're movin', we're in the zonewe're groovin'.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"'Cause I don't need your stupid ship.",
        "response":"Good.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"'Cause I don't need your stupid ship.",
        "response":"Good.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh, what'cha gonna do, fat boy, huh? What?",
        "response":"Nothing, except tell you, uh, I think it's wonderful how much energy you have.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you know.",
        "response":"You know, I mean, you can't tell your parents you were fired because they'd bedisappointed.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you know.",
        "response":"You know, I mean, you can't tell your parents you were fired because they'd bedisappointed.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nothing, except tell you, uh, I think it's wonderful how much energy you have.",
        "response":"Well, thanks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nothing, except tell you, uh, I think it's wonderful how much energy you have.",
        "response":"Well, thanks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I mean, especially considering how tough it's been for you to find work.",
        "response":"Well, you know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I mean, especially considering how tough it's been for you to find work.",
        "response":"Well, you know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, thanks.",
        "response":"I mean, especially considering how tough it's been for you to find work.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, thanks.",
        "response":"I mean, especially considering how tough it's been for you to find work.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I mean, if it were me, I think I'd have difficulty just getting out of bed at all.",
        "response":"Y'know, I try to stay positive. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know, I mean, you can't tell your parents you were fired because they'd bedisappointed.",
        "response":"[sad] Uh-huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know, I mean, you can't tell your parents you were fired because they'd bedisappointed.",
        "response":"[sad] Uh-huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well no, but um.",
        "response":"I mean, if it were me, I think I'd have difficulty just getting out of bed at all.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well no, but um.",
        "response":"I mean, if it were me, I think I'd have difficulty just getting out of bed at all.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[sad] Uh-huh.",
        "response":"And it's not as if you have a boyfriend's shoulder to cry on.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[sad] Uh-huh.",
        "response":"And it's not as if you have a boyfriend's shoulder to cry on.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And it's not as if you have a boyfriend's shoulder to cry on.",
        "response":"Well no, but um.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And it's not as if you have a boyfriend's shoulder to cry on.",
        "response":"Well no, but um.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I mean, if it were me, I think I'd have difficulty just getting out of bed at all.",
        "response":"Y'know, I try to stay positive. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Because, you know, you don't have to. If you want, you could just take a nap righthere.",
        "response":"OK. Just for a little while.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Because, you know, you don't have to. If you want, you could just take a nap righthere.",
        "response":"OK. Just for a little while.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright.",
        "response":"Because, you know, you don't have to. If you want, you could just take a nap righthere.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright.",
        "response":"Because, you know, you don't have to. If you want, you could just take a nap righthere.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Y'know, I try to stay positive. . .",
        "response":"So, you feel like goin' for a run?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Y'know, I try to stay positive. . .",
        "response":"So, you feel like goin' for a run?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, you feel like goin' for a run?",
        "response":"Alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, you feel like goin' for a run?",
        "response":"Alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK. Just for a little while.",
        "response":"OK. [Puts an afghan over her and dances into his room]</font></p><p align=\"center\"><strong><font size=\"3\">END</font></strong></p><hr><p align=\"center\"><!--webbot bot=\"ImageMap\" startspanrectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/208list.htm\"rectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2.htm\"rectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/206baby.htm\"src=\"contrl08.gif\" width=\"194\" height=\"60\"alt=\"contrl08.gif \" --><MAP NAME=\"FrontPageMap0\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"138, 2, 197, 84\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/208list.htm\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"69, 2, 131, 84\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2.htm\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"1, 2, 58, 80\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/206baby.htm\"></MAP><img src=\"file:///C:/Friends%20Script%20Index/contrl08.gif\" width=\"194\" height=\"60\" alt=\"contrl08.gif \" usemap=\"#FrontPageMap0\"><!--webbot bot=\"ImageMap\" i-checksum=\"5504\" endspan--></p><hr><center><img src=\"/cgi-bin/counter/207\"></center><hr></body></html>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Rach. I, uh, got you a little present. [Rachel is not impressed]. . I'll openit. It's a Slinky! Remember, huh. [sings] <i>Walks down stairs, alone or in pairs,everyone knows it's</i>. . . just a big spring. Alright, you still mad at me becuase ofthe whole. . .",
        "response":"Horrible and degrading list of reasons not to be with me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Horrible and degrading list of reasons not to be with me?",
        "response":"How 'bout from now on we just call it the 'unfortunate incident'? [Rachel walks off]Hey Gunther, you got stairs in your place?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, we were gonna give fifty, but if you guys gave more, we don't wanna lookbad.",
        "response":"Oh, actually this year we just made him homemade cookies.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebs, let me ask you something, were, were these, uh, funny brownies?",
        "response":"Not especially. But you know what, I think they had pot in them.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can see that. A plate of brownies once told me a limerick.",
        "response":"Phoebs, let me ask you something, were, were these, uh, funny brownies?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, actually this year we just made him homemade cookies.",
        "response":"And twenty-five it is.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Uhhh, I don't think you're gonna like this.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How 'bout from now on we just call it the 'unfortunate incident'? [Rachel walks off]Hey Gunther, you got stairs in your place?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon show us what you bought. . . You know you want to.",
        "response":"[childishly] OK. OK, this is a picture frame from Ben to my parents, huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah?",
        "response":"Look at these authentic fake medals. I tell ya, mom's gonna be voted best dressedat the make-believe military academy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, just some presents.",
        "response":"C'mon show us what you bought. . . You know you want to.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Cute.",
        "response":"I got some, uh, hers and hers towels for Susan and Carol. And, uh, I got this blousefor mom.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Here, go nuts. [gives him the Slinky and goes and sits with others at the couches]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[childishly] OK. OK, this is a picture frame from Ben to my parents, huh.",
        "response":"Cute.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ross, that is gorgeous!",
        "response":"Yeah?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey. Hi Phoebe.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Happy Christmas Eve Eve. [sees Ross's picture frame] Oh my God, where did you getthis?",
        "response":"Uh, Macy's, third floor, home furnishings.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebe, I thought your dad was in prison.",
        "response":"No, that's my stepdad. My real dad's the one that ran out on us before I was born.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebe, I thought your dad was in prison.",
        "response":"No, that's my stepdad. My real dad's the one that ran out on us before I was born.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, that's my stepdad. My real dad's the one that ran out on us before I was born.",
        "response":"How have you never been on Oprah?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey. Hi Phoebe.",
        "response":"Happy Christmas Eve Eve. [sees Ross's picture frame] Oh my God, where did you getthis?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nah, Phoebs, that's the guy that comes in the frame.",
        "response":"No it isn't, this is my dad, alright, I'll show you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No it isn't, this is my dad, alright, I'll show you.",
        "response":"Phoebe, I thought your dad was in prison.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This is my father, this is a picture of my dad.",
        "response":"Nah, Phoebs, that's the guy that comes in the frame.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, Macy's, third floor, home furnishings.",
        "response":"This is my father, this is a picture of my dad.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Honey, uh, this is a picture of the frame guy posing in front of a bright bluescreen with a collie.",
        "response":"It's not a blue screen... it's just, maybe it was just really clear that day. OK,I have to talk to my grandmother. [turns to leave]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Honey, uh, this is a picture of the frame guy posing in front of a bright bluescreen with a collie.",
        "response":"It's not a blue screen... it's just, maybe it was just really clear that day. OK,I have to talk to my grandmother. [turns to leave]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[showing her pictures] OK, look, see, this is him. My mother gave me this picturebefore she died, same guy.",
        "response":"Honey, uh, this is a picture of the frame guy posing in front of a bright bluescreen with a collie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's not a blue screen... it's just, maybe it was just really clear that day. OK,I have to talk to my grandmother. [turns to leave]",
        "response":"Oh, wait a minute honey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How have you never been on Oprah?",
        "response":"[showing her pictures] OK, look, see, this is him. My mother gave me this picturebefore she died, same guy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, that's my stepdad. My real dad's the one that ran out on us before I was born.",
        "response":"How have you never been on Oprah?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So anyway, I'm trying to get my boss's ex-wife to sleep with me. . .",
        "response":"Joey!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, wait a minute honey.",
        "response":"Phoebs. [Phoebe leaves]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebs. [Phoebe leaves]",
        "response":"Wow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, gram, um, can I see the pictures of my dad again?",
        "response":"[nervously] Oh. Oh, sure, sure, uh, uh, how come?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, just updating the phonebook.",
        "response":"Um, gram, um, can I see the pictures of my dad again?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, just updating the phonebook.",
        "response":"Um, gram, um, can I see the pictures of my dad again?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Esther Livingston. [scratches out name] Gone.",
        "response":"[Phoebe enters.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey!",
        "response":"Oh, but when Phoebe has a problem, everyone's all ears!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi Gram. Whatcha doin'?",
        "response":"Oh, just updating the phonebook.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi Gram. Whatcha doin'?",
        "response":"Oh, just updating the phonebook.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi, Phoe.",
        "response":"Hi Gram. Whatcha doin'?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Phoebe enters.]",
        "response":"Hi, Phoe.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Just, you know, to see... um.",
        "response":"Oh, sure, yeah. [gets a box with the pictures] This is the one of you fatherin a meadow, and, uh, helping a little boy fly a kite, and here he is at a graduation. . .another graduation. . . another graduation.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Just, you know, to see... um.",
        "response":"Oh, sure, yeah. [gets a box with the pictures] This is the one of you fatherin a meadow, and, uh, helping a little boy fly a kite, and here he is at a graduation. . .another graduation. . . another graduation.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, sure, yeah. [gets a box with the pictures] This is the one of you fatherin a meadow, and, uh, helping a little boy fly a kite, and here he is at a graduation. . .another graduation. . . another graduation.",
        "response":"OK, is this really my father?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, sure, yeah. [gets a box with the pictures] This is the one of you fatherin a meadow, and, uh, helping a little boy fly a kite, and here he is at a graduation. . .another graduation. . . another graduation.",
        "response":"OK, is this really my father?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, gram, um, can I see the pictures of my dad again?",
        "response":"[nervously] Oh. Oh, sure, sure, uh, uh, how come?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, is this really my father?",
        "response":"Is it really your fa--I can't... well of course it is.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, is this really my father?",
        "response":"Is it really your fa--I can't... well of course it is.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[nervously] Oh. Oh, sure, sure, uh, uh, how come?",
        "response":"Just, you know, to see... um.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[nervously] Oh. Oh, sure, sure, uh, uh, how come?",
        "response":"Just, you know, to see... um.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ya know, in all the years that we have been grandmother and granddaughter, youhave never lied to me.",
        "response":"Alright, that is not your father, that's just a picture of a guy in a frame.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ya know, in all the years that we have been grandmother and granddaughter, youhave never lied to me.",
        "response":"Alright, that is not your father, that's just a picture of a guy in a frame.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Is it really your fa--I can't... well of course it is.",
        "response":"OK, I smell smoke. Maybe that's 'cause someone's pants are on fire.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Is it really your fa--I can't... well of course it is.",
        "response":"OK, I smell smoke. Maybe that's 'cause someone's pants are on fire.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, I. . .",
        "response":"Ya know, in all the years that we have been grandmother and granddaughter, youhave never lied to me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, I. . .",
        "response":"Ya know, in all the years that we have been grandmother and granddaughter, youhave never lied to me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, I smell smoke. Maybe that's 'cause someone's pants are on fire.",
        "response":"Look, I. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, I smell smoke. Maybe that's 'cause someone's pants are on fire.",
        "response":"Look, I. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, that is not your father, that's just a picture of a guy in a frame.",
        "response":"Oh God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It was your mother's idea. Ya know, she didn't want you to know your realfather because it hurt her so much when he left, and, I didn't want to go along with it,but, well then she died and, and it was harder to argue with her. Not impossible, butharder.",
        "response":"Alright, so, what, he's not a famous tree surgeon? And then, I guess, OK, hedoesn't live in a hut in Burma where there's no phones?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It was your mother's idea. Ya know, she didn't want you to know your realfather because it hurt her so much when he left, and, I didn't want to go along with it,but, well then she died and, and it was harder to argue with her. Not impossible, butharder.",
        "response":"Alright, so, what, he's not a famous tree surgeon? And then, I guess, OK, hedoesn't live in a hut in Burma where there's no phones?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God.",
        "response":"It was your mother's idea. Ya know, she didn't want you to know your realfather because it hurt her so much when he left, and, I didn't want to go along with it,but, well then she died and, and it was harder to argue with her. Not impossible, butharder.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God.",
        "response":"It was your mother's idea. Ya know, she didn't want you to know your realfather because it hurt her so much when he left, and, I didn't want to go along with it,but, well then she died and, and it was harder to argue with her. Not impossible, butharder.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, so, what, he's not a famous tree surgeon? And then, I guess, OK, hedoesn't live in a hut in Burma where there's no phones?",
        "response":"Last I heard, he was a pharmacist somewhere upstate.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, so, what, he's not a famous tree surgeon? And then, I guess, OK, hedoesn't live in a hut in Burma where there's no phones?",
        "response":"Last I heard, he was a pharmacist somewhere upstate.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Last I heard, he was a pharmacist somewhere upstate.",
        "response":"OK, that makes no sense. Why would the villagers worship a pharmacist?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Last I heard, he was a pharmacist somewhere upstate.",
        "response":"OK, that makes no sense. Why would the villagers worship a pharmacist?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, that is not your father, that's just a picture of a guy in a frame.",
        "response":"Oh God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ya know I remember my father, all dressed up in the red suit, the big blackboots, and the patent leather belt, sneakin around downstairs. He didn't want anybody tosee him but he'd be drunk so he'd stumble, crash into something and wake everybody up.",
        "response":"Well, that doesn't sound like a very merry Christmas.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[realizes] Oh.",
        "response":"Anyway, that's all I know. That, and this. [pulls apart a frame and pulls apicture out] This is the real him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[realizes] Oh.",
        "response":"Anyway, that's all I know. That, and this. [pulls apart a frame and pulls apicture out] This is the real him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Anyway, that's all I know. That, and this. [pulls apart a frame and pulls apicture out] This is the real him.",
        "response":"Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, that doesn't sound like a very merry Christmas.",
        "response":"Who said anything about Christmas?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, that makes no sense. Why would the villagers worship a pharmacist?",
        "response":"Honey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, that makes no sense. Why would the villagers worship a pharmacist?",
        "response":"Honey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Honey.",
        "response":"[realizes] Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Honey.",
        "response":"[realizes] Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon Rachel.",
        "response":"OK, you're whiney, you are, you're obsessive, you are insecure, you're, you'regutless, you know, you don't ever, you don't just sort of seize the day, you know. Youlike me for what, a year, you didn't do anything about it. And, uh, oh, you wear too muchof that gel in your hair.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, what're you guys doin' here, aren't you supposed to be Christmas shopping?",
        "response":"You guys haven't gotten your presents yet? Tomorrow's Christmas Eve, what're yagonna do?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Just some stuff for the party.",
        "response":"Yeah, what're you guys doin' here, aren't you supposed to be Christmas shopping?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I know exactly what she's goin' through.",
        "response":"How do you know exactly what she's going through?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I know exactly what she's goin' through.",
        "response":"How do you know exactly what she's going through?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wha... forget it Ross, no, I am not gonna stand here and make a list of. . .",
        "response":"C'mon Rachel.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I hope she's OK.",
        "response":"Yeah, I know exactly what she's goin' through.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How do you know exactly what she's going through?",
        "response":"She told us.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, you're whiney, you are, you're obsessive, you are insecure, you're, you'regutless, you know, you don't ever, you don't just sort of seize the day, you know. Youlike me for what, a year, you didn't do anything about it. And, uh, oh, you wear too muchof that gel in your hair.",
        "response":"See there, you uhh, alright, ya, you did what I said.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, you're whiney, you are, you're obsessive, you are insecure, you're, you'regutless, you know, you don't ever, you don't just sort of seize the day, you know. Youlike me for what, a year, you didn't do anything about it. And, uh, oh, you wear too muchof that gel in your hair.",
        "response":"See there, you uhh, alright, ya, you did what I said.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon Rachel.",
        "response":"OK, you're whiney, you are, you're obsessive, you are insecure, you're, you'regutless, you know, you don't ever, you don't just sort of seize the day, you know. Youlike me for what, a year, you didn't do anything about it. And, uh, oh, you wear too muchof that gel in your hair.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"See there, you uhh, alright, ya, you did what I said.",
        "response":"Yeah, and you know what? You're right, I do feel better, thank you Ross. [shewalks off and Ross puts his hand to his hair]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon now Phoe, don't still be mad at me. How's it going?",
        "response":"Well, not so good. Upstate's pretty big, he's pretty small, you do the math.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon now Phoe, don't still be mad at me. How's it going?",
        "response":"Well, not so good. Upstate's pretty big, he's pretty small, you do the math.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello grandma, if that is in fact your real name.",
        "response":"C'mon now Phoe, don't still be mad at me. How's it going?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello grandma, if that is in fact your real name.",
        "response":"C'mon now Phoe, don't still be mad at me. How's it going?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hello grandma, if that is in fact your real name.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, not so good. Upstate's pretty big, he's pretty small, you do the math.",
        "response":"Well, I think you're better off without him. Oh honey, I know he's your daddybut, but to me he's still the irresponsible creep who knocked up your mom and stole herGremlin.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, not so good. Upstate's pretty big, he's pretty small, you do the math.",
        "response":"Well, I think you're better off without him. Oh honey, I know he's your daddybut, but to me he's still the irresponsible creep who knocked up your mom and stole herGremlin.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I think you're better off without him. Oh honey, I know he's your daddybut, but to me he's still the irresponsible creep who knocked up your mom and stole herGremlin.",
        "response":"No I just, just wanted to know who he was, ya know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I think you're better off without him. Oh honey, I know he's your daddybut, but to me he's still the irresponsible creep who knocked up your mom and stole herGremlin.",
        "response":"No I just, just wanted to know who he was, ya know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No I just, just wanted to know who he was, ya know.",
        "response":"I know. OK, I wasn't completely honest with you when I told you that, uh, Ididn't know exactly where he lived.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No I just, just wanted to know who he was, ya know.",
        "response":"I know. OK, I wasn't completely honest with you when I told you that, uh, Ididn't know exactly where he lived.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whattaya mean?",
        "response":"He lives at 74 Laurel Drive in Middletown. If you hit the Dairy Queen, you'vegone too far. You can take my cab.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know. OK, I wasn't completely honest with you when I told you that, uh, Ididn't know exactly where he lived.",
        "response":"Whattaya mean?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know. OK, I wasn't completely honest with you when I told you that, uh, Ididn't know exactly where he lived.",
        "response":"Whattaya mean?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Now, remember, nobody else drives that cab.",
        "response":"Uh-huh, got it. Ooh, I'm gonna see my dad. Wish me luck, Grandpa! [blows a kiss toa picture of Einstein]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He lives at 74 Laurel Drive in Middletown. If you hit the Dairy Queen, you'vegone too far. You can take my cab.",
        "response":"Wow. Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He lives at 74 Laurel Drive in Middletown. If you hit the Dairy Queen, you'vegone too far. You can take my cab.",
        "response":"Wow. Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whattaya mean?",
        "response":"He lives at 74 Laurel Drive in Middletown. If you hit the Dairy Queen, you'vegone too far. You can take my cab.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, she, she brought the invisible cab. . . hop in.",
        "response":"Well she better get here soon, the outlet stores close at 7.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, she, she brought the invisible cab. . . hop in.",
        "response":"Well she better get here soon, the outlet stores close at 7.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebe here with the cab yet?",
        "response":"Yeah, she, she brought the invisible cab. . . hop in.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow. Thank you.",
        "response":"Now, remember, nobody else drives that cab.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow. Thank you.",
        "response":"Now, remember, nobody else drives that cab.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well she better get here soon, the outlet stores close at 7.",
        "response":"Hey, don't worry. I figure it'll be 2 hours to Phoebe's dad's house, they'llmeet, they'll chat, they'll swap life stories, we'll still have plenty of time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Can you believe this. In, like, two hours I'm gonna have a dad. Eeeshk.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK.",
        "response":"Alright, here, you have to hold this. [hands Chandler a piece of paper]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK.",
        "response":"Alright, here, you have to hold this. [hands Chandler a piece of paper]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, here she comes.",
        "response":"Chandler: Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chandler: Hey.",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, let's go.",
        "response":"OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[grabs for seat belt] Where's my seat belt?",
        "response":"Oh, no no, that side doesn't have one, the paramedics had to cut through it.[Chandler jumps out of the car]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[grabs for seat belt] Where's my seat belt?",
        "response":"Oh, no no, that side doesn't have one, the paramedics had to cut through it.[Chandler jumps out of the car]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, no no, that side doesn't have one, the paramedics had to cut through it.[Chandler jumps out of the car]",
        "response":"[Chandler gets in the back seat] Hey!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, here, you have to hold this. [hands Chandler a piece of paper]",
        "response":"OK. [reads paper] Brake left, gas right?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, here, you have to hold this. [hands Chandler a piece of paper]",
        "response":"OK. [reads paper] Brake left, gas right?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK. [reads paper] Brake left, gas right?",
        "response":"Uh-huh, yeah, that's my cheat sheet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK. [reads paper] Brake left, gas right?",
        "response":"Uh-huh, yeah, that's my cheat sheet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh, yeah, that's my cheat sheet.",
        "response":"[grabs for seat belt] Where's my seat belt?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh, yeah, that's my cheat sheet.",
        "response":"[grabs for seat belt] Where's my seat belt?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rach, get the heat. [Rachel holds up her hand with wet fingernail polish] Ross,could you turn the heat down please?",
        "response":"Sure. By the way, there's a difference between being obsessive and. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Fine, OK! Heat, heat, heat, and I'm the obsessive one. [goes to the radiator andstarts turning the knob] OK, this way is on, so this is. . . [breaks off the knob] off.",
        "response":"Did you just break the radiator?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ross, the heat!",
        "response":"Fine, OK! Heat, heat, heat, and I'm the obsessive one. [goes to the radiator andstarts turning the knob] OK, this way is on, so this is. . . [breaks off the knob] off.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Here, let me try.",
        "response":"Oh, oh that's right, I forgot about your ability to fuse metal.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sure. By the way, there's a difference between being obsessive and. . .",
        "response":"Ross, the heat!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sure. By the way, there's a difference between being obsessive and. . .",
        "response":"Ross, the heat!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did you just break the radiator?",
        "response":"No, no, I was turnin' the knob and, and. . . here it is.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, I was turnin' the knob and, and. . . here it is.",
        "response":"Well put it back.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well put it back.",
        "response":"It uhh, it won't go back.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[sitting at table talking to a girl] It's hard to tell because I'm sweating, but Iuse exactly what the gel bottle says, an amount about the size of a pea. How, how can thatbe too much?",
        "response":"[carrying an ice cube tray] Ice, ice, ice squares anyone? Take a napkin. Alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, if he doesn't like our cookies, too bad, I am not gonna be blackmailed. Lookif worse comes to worse, it gets a little warm, we'll call it a theme party.",
        "response":"Hey, here's a theme: Come on in, live like bacon.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, tip the man.",
        "response":"No, if he doesn't like our cookies, too bad, I am not gonna be blackmailed. Lookif worse comes to worse, it gets a little warm, we'll call it a theme party.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[carrying an ice cube tray] Ice, ice, ice squares anyone? Take a napkin. Alright.",
        "response":"Monica, Monica, your guest are turning into jerky, OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh, this is it, 74. [screeches to a halt, Joey and Chandler are thrown into theplexiglass wall in the cab]",
        "response":"Oh, so that's what this is for.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, so that's what this is for.",
        "response":"Wow, this is it, I'm gonna meet my dad. This is like the biggest thing ever, huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, so that's what this is for.",
        "response":"Wow, this is it, I'm gonna meet my dad. This is like the biggest thing ever, huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, oh that's right, I forgot about your ability to fuse metal.",
        "response":"Hey, it's Funny's cousin, Not Funny.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow, this is it, I'm gonna meet my dad. This is like the biggest thing ever, huh.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, alright, you know how you say I never seize the day? Well, alright, eventhough he's your super, I'm seizing. [approaches Mr. Treeger] Mr. Treeger, here is 50bucks, merry Christmas.",
        "response":"[Gives him the cash.]</p><p align=\"left\">MR. TREEGER: Oh wow, I didn't get you anything. Here's five back.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Gives him the cash.]</p><p align=\"left\">MR. TREEGER: Oh wow, I didn't get you anything. Here's five back.",
        "response":"No no, no, that, that's your Christmas tip, alright. Oh, hey, do you think there's achance you could fix that radiator now?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Monica, Monica, your guest are turning into jerky, OK.",
        "response":"Really? I'm perfectly comfortable. [one of the guest opens the refrigerator] Hey,hey, hey, get in line buddy, I was next. [she opens the refrigerator and leans into it]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[carrying an ice cube tray] Ice, ice, ice squares anyone? Take a napkin. Alright.",
        "response":"Monica, Monica, your guest are turning into jerky, OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. TREEGER: Uhh, you said there was a party.",
        "response":"Oh, yeah, well hey, welcome to our sauna.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[answering the door] Mr. Treeger.",
        "response":"MR. TREEGER: Uhh, you said there was a party.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"[to Ross] Looks like he's playin' baseball.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"[to Ross] Looks like he's playin' baseball.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ross.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. TREEGER: [to Rachel who is standing under mistletoe] So, uh, is this, uh, mistletoe?",
        "response":"Huh-huh, no act--no, uhh, that, that is basil.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nice seizing. . . gel boy.",
        "response":"MR. TREEGER: [to Rachel who is standing under mistletoe] So, uh, is this, uh, mistletoe?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. TREEGER: Ahh, if it was mistletoe, I was gonna kiss ya.",
        "response":"Huh-hoo, yeah, no, it's still basil.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh-huh, no act--no, uhh, that, that is basil.",
        "response":"MR. TREEGER: Ahh, if it was mistletoe, I was gonna kiss ya.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[to Ross] Looks like he's playin' baseball.",
        "response":"You mean hardball?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[to Ross] Looks like he's playin' baseball.",
        "response":"You mean hardball?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You mean hardball?",
        "response":"Whatever.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK.",
        "response":"How far'd ya get?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, maybe he's, maybe he's this really cool pharmacist guy.",
        "response":"Yeah, maybe, yeah. You know, and, and I'll knock on the door and, and he'll hug meand I'll have a dad. Ya know and I'll, I'll go to his pharmacy and everyone will be reallynice to me 'cause, you know, I'm Franks daughter.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, it's just like, ya know, it's a whole mess of stuff, ya know. It's like,yesterday, ya know, my dad was this, like, famous Burma tree surgeon guy and, ya know, nowhe's a, a pharmacist guy and. . .",
        "response":"Well, maybe he's, maybe he's this really cool pharmacist guy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, it's just like, ya know, it's a whole mess of stuff, ya know. It's like,yesterday, ya know, my dad was this, like, famous Burma tree surgeon guy and, ya know, nowhe's a, a pharmacist guy and. . .",
        "response":"Well, maybe he's, maybe he's this really cool pharmacist guy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebs, what's goin' on?",
        "response":"No, it's just like, ya know, it's a whole mess of stuff, ya know. It's like,yesterday, ya know, my dad was this, like, famous Burma tree surgeon guy and, ya know, nowhe's a, a pharmacist guy and. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebs, what's goin' on?",
        "response":"No, it's just like, ya know, it's a whole mess of stuff, ya know. It's like,yesterday, ya know, my dad was this, like, famous Burma tree surgeon guy and, ya know, nowhe's a, a pharmacist guy and. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mailbox.",
        "response":"Alright, we're gettin' closer.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, we're gettin' closer.",
        "response":"Uh-huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How far'd ya get?",
        "response":"Mailbox.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh.",
        "response":"Phoebs, what's goin' on?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, 'cause, I mean, what if, what if he's not this great dad guy? I mean, whatif, what if he's just still the dirtbag who ran out on my mom and us? You know what? I'vealready lost a fake dad this week and I don't think I'm ready to lose a real one.",
        "response":"Phoebs, that's OK. You took a big step today.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, so why not go knock?",
        "response":"Well, 'cause, I mean, what if, what if he's not this great dad guy? I mean, whatif, what if he's just still the dirtbag who ran out on my mom and us? You know what? I'vealready lost a fake dad this week and I don't think I'm ready to lose a real one.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, maybe, yeah. You know, and, and I'll knock on the door and, and he'll hug meand I'll have a dad. Ya know and I'll, I'll go to his pharmacy and everyone will be reallynice to me 'cause, you know, I'm Franks daughter.",
        "response":"Well, so why not go knock?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wiper blades. I don't even have a car.",
        "response":"No, but with this new car smell, you'll think you do.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahh, toilet seat covers! Is that what you were doing while I was getting gas?",
        "response":"Uh-huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rach, these are for you.",
        "response":"Wiper blades. I don't even have a car.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebs, that's OK. You took a big step today.",
        "response":"Yeah?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh.",
        "response":"You guuuyys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh.",
        "response":"You guuuyys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, Ross, you had to, I mean, he was humping everything in sight. I mean, I have aMalibu Barbi that will no longer be wearing white to her wedding.",
        "response":"Remember when sometimes he'd borrow your hat, and, and when you got it back there'dbe little monkey raisins in it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sometimes I wonder if I did the right thing, ya know, giving him away.",
        "response":"Oh, Ross, you had to, I mean, he was humping everything in sight. I mean, I have aMalibu Barbi that will no longer be wearing white to her wedding.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, but then the guy opens his beer and those girls run at him, so, everythingseems to work out OK.",
        "response":"I meant because the monkey in it reminds me of Marcel.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That commercial always makes me so sad.",
        "response":"Yeah, but then the guy opens his beer and those girls run at him, so, everythingseems to work out OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well this, this is too much, I feel like I should get you another sweater.",
        "response":"And last but not least.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And, a lemon lime.",
        "response":"Well this, this is too much, I feel like I should get you another sweater.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And, a lemon lime.",
        "response":"Well this, this is too much, I feel like I should get you another sweater.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You got me a cola drink?",
        "response":"And, a lemon lime.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You guuuyys.",
        "response":"And for Ross, Mr. Sweet-tooth.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[reading] 'Dear Dr. Remore, know that I love you and would do anything to haveyou.' Gosh. 'Your not-so-secretive admirer, Erica Ford.' Ooh wait, 'PS enclosed pleasefind 14 of my eyelashes.'",
        "response":"Ya know, in crazy world, that means you're married.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ya know, in crazy world, that means you're married.",
        "response":"This wasn't addressed to <i>Days of Our Lives</i>, this is, this came to yourapartment. There's no stamp on it, this woman was in our building.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, oh, OK, so everyone, pretend like I'm telling you a story, OK. And, and it'sreally funny. So everyone just laugh, now.",
        "response":"[Everyone laughs]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, hey, check it out, guess what I got.",
        "response":"Rhythm?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, I know. [to Rob] Hello.",
        "response":"Hi. I'm Rob Dohnen.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Everyone laughs]",
        "response":"I know, I know. [to Rob] Hello.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi. I'm Rob Dohnen.",
        "response":"Hi Rob Dohnen.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi. I'm Rob Dohnen.",
        "response":"Hi Rob Dohnen.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rhythm?",
        "response":"No, my first fan mail.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Anyway, I schedule performers for the childrens libraries around the city and I wasjust thinking, have you ever thought about playing your songs for kids?",
        "response":"Oh, I would love to have kids. . . you're, you're the, you're, me play the songsthat I will write for them.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, wow.",
        "response":"Anyway, I schedule performers for the childrens libraries around the city and I wasjust thinking, have you ever thought about playing your songs for kids?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, wow.",
        "response":"Anyway, I schedule performers for the childrens libraries around the city and I wasjust thinking, have you ever thought about playing your songs for kids?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well we could just stay in and cook for ourselves. [both laugh hysterically]",
        "response":"[door buzzer goes off]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi Rob Dohnen.",
        "response":"I don't know anything about music, but I think you're really, really great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi Rob Dohnen.",
        "response":"I don't know anything about music, but I think you're really, really great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know anything about music, but I think you're really, really great.",
        "response":"Oh, wow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know anything about music, but I think you're really, really great.",
        "response":"Oh, wow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[door buzzer goes off]",
        "response":"Hello.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi, Dean Lipson, zoo administrator. I was told you had a question.",
        "response":"Well, I uh, I can't seem to find the monkey I donated last year. He's a capuchan,answers to the name Marcel.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I uh, I can't seem to find the monkey I donated last year. He's a capuchan,answers to the name Marcel.",
        "response":"Ahh, I'm afraid I have some bad news. Marcel has passed on.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I uh, I can't seem to find the monkey I donated last year. He's a capuchan,answers to the name Marcel.",
        "response":"Ahh, I'm afraid I have some bad news. Marcel has passed on.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, we'll just leave, and when we pass her on the stairs, she won't know it's me'cause we've never met.",
        "response":"That's how radio stars escape stalkers.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, we'll just leave, and when we pass her on the stairs, she won't know it's me'cause we've never met.",
        "response":"That's how radio stars escape stalkers.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The one time they're not home.",
        "response":"OK, we'll just leave, and when we pass her on the stairs, she won't know it's me'cause we've never met.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's how radio stars escape stalkers.",
        "response":"She's comin'.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ah, the stalker.",
        "response":"Never mind, it's open.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's Erica.",
        "response":"Ah, the stalker.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry Mr. Geller. But ya know, there's an old saying, 'Sometimes monkeys die.'It's not a great saying but it certainly is fitting today.",
        "response":"Well, ya know, someone should have called me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't believe this.",
        "response":"I'm sorry Mr. Geller. But ya know, there's an old saying, 'Sometimes monkeys die.'It's not a great saying but it certainly is fitting today.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't believe this.",
        "response":"I'm sorry Mr. Geller. But ya know, there's an old saying, 'Sometimes monkeys die.'It's not a great saying but it certainly is fitting today.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahh, I'm afraid I have some bad news. Marcel has passed on.",
        "response":"Oh my God, what happened?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahh, I'm afraid I have some bad news. Marcel has passed on.",
        "response":"Oh my God, what happened?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God, what happened?",
        "response":"Well he got sick, and then he got sicker, and then he got a little better but thenhe died.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God, what happened?",
        "response":"Well he got sick, and then he got sicker, and then he got a little better but thenhe died.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well he got sick, and then he got sicker, and then he got a little better but thenhe died.",
        "response":"I can't believe this.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well he got sick, and then he got sicker, and then he got a little better but thenhe died.",
        "response":"I can't believe this.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry Mr. Geller. But ya know, there's an old saying, 'Sometimes monkeys die.'It's not a great saying but it certainly is fitting today.",
        "response":"Well, ya know, someone should have called me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, ya know, someone should have called me.",
        "response":"I'm sorry. Look, I know this can't bring him back but here, it's just a gesture.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, ya know, someone should have called me.",
        "response":"I'm sorry. Look, I know this can't bring him back but here, it's just a gesture.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Zoo dollars?",
        "response":"Yes, and come see the bird show at 4. The macaws wear hats. Well it's a lot cuterif your monkey hasn't just died.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry. Look, I know this can't bring him back but here, it's just a gesture.",
        "response":"Zoo dollars?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry. Look, I know this can't bring him back but here, it's just a gesture.",
        "response":"Zoo dollars?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you remember Cathy Bates in <i>Misery</i>?",
        "response":"RACHEL AND MONICA: Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"RACHEL AND MONICA: Yeah.",
        "response":"Well, she looks the exact opposite of that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, she looks the exact opposite of that.",
        "response":"And she's not crazy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's not a good idea, that's kinda the reason the last guy got fired.",
        "response":"I'm just, I'm, I'm, I'm used to playing for grown-ups. Ya know, they just,grown-ups drink their coffee and do their grown-up thing, ya know, and kids listen. Thisis a huge responsibility. What? Are you gonna kiss me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm just, I'm, I'm, I'm used to playing for grown-ups. Ya know, they just,grown-ups drink their coffee and do their grown-up thing, ya know, and kids listen. Thisis a huge responsibility. What? Are you gonna kiss me?",
        "response":"I was thinkin' about it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, uh-uh, I'm just, I'm nervous. So, you know what, maybe if I just, if I picturethem all in their underwear.",
        "response":"That's not a good idea, that's kinda the reason the last guy got fired.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, uh-uh, I'm just, I'm nervous. So, you know what, maybe if I just, if I picturethem all in their underwear.",
        "response":"That's not a good idea, that's kinda the reason the last guy got fired.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You OK?",
        "response":"No, uh-uh, I'm just, I'm nervous. So, you know what, maybe if I just, if I picturethem all in their underwear.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I was thinkin' about it.",
        "response":"OK. [they kiss] OK, alrighty, let's play some tunes. Hi everybody, I'm Phoebe",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And she's not crazy?",
        "response":"Oh no no no, she's a total wack job. Yeah, she thinks that Joey is actually Dr.Drake Remore.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And she's not crazy?",
        "response":"Oh no no no, she's a total wack job. Yeah, she thinks that Joey is actually Dr.Drake Remore.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh no no no, she's a total wack job. Yeah, she thinks that Joey is actually Dr.Drake Remore.",
        "response":"Oh my God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, here we sit, devil may care, just a little while ago you were reattachingsomeone's spinal cord.",
        "response":"Yeah, that was a tricky one. In reality, that operation takes like, over 10 hours,but they only showed it for 2 minites.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, here we sit, devil may care, just a little while ago you were reattachingsomeone's spinal cord.",
        "response":"Yeah, that was a tricky one. In reality, that operation takes like, over 10 hours,but they only showed it for 2 minites.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah it is. . . what?",
        "response":"Well, here we sit, devil may care, just a little while ago you were reattachingsomeone's spinal cord.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah it is. . . what?",
        "response":"Well, here we sit, devil may care, just a little while ago you were reattachingsomeone's spinal cord.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, that was a tricky one. In reality, that operation takes like, over 10 hours,but they only showed it for 2 minites.",
        "response":"Who's they?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK. [they kiss] OK, alrighty, let's play some tunes. Hi everybody, I'm Phoebe",
        "response":"Hi Phoebe.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi Phoebe.",
        "response":"OK, um, I'm gonna play, um, some songs about grandparents, OK. [singing]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, Drake, isn't it amazing?",
        "response":"Yeah it is. . . what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh Drake, you are so talented, let me see those hands. Oh these hands, thesebeautiful hands, oh I could just eat them. . . but I won't.",
        "response":"Good, otherwise my watch would fall off. [laughs hysterically]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh Drake, you are so talented, let me see those hands. Oh these hands, thesebeautiful hands, oh I could just eat them. . . but I won't.",
        "response":"Good, otherwise my watch would fall off. [laughs hysterically]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Good, otherwise my watch would fall off. [laughs hysterically]",
        "response":"No, seriously. These hands. These miracle, magical, life-giving hands. Oh, just tobe near them, touch them, maybe even lick one?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Good, otherwise my watch would fall off. [laughs hysterically]",
        "response":"No, seriously. These hands. These miracle, magical, life-giving hands. Oh, just tobe near them, touch them, maybe even lick one?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No one.",
        "response":"Oh Drake, you are so talented, let me see those hands. Oh these hands, thesebeautiful hands, oh I could just eat them. . . but I won't.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No one.",
        "response":"Oh Drake, you are so talented, let me see those hands. Oh these hands, thesebeautiful hands, oh I could just eat them. . . but I won't.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, that was a tricky one. In reality, that operation takes like, over 10 hours,but they only showed it for 2 minites.",
        "response":"Who's they?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Who's they?",
        "response":"No one.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Who's they?",
        "response":"No one.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uhh, cause, uhh, I'm a neurosurgeon and that was clearly a case of, uh, uh, foodalchokage. Alright, look, I got to tell you something.",
        "response":"No, no no no, you don't have to tell me anything. You don't have to explainyourself to me. Ooh, who am I to question the great Dr. Drake Remore?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uhh, cause, uhh, I'm a neurosurgeon and that was clearly a case of, uh, uh, foodalchokage. Alright, look, I got to tell you something.",
        "response":"No, no no no, you don't have to tell me anything. You don't have to explainyourself to me. Ooh, who am I to question the great Dr. Drake Remore?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, seriously. These hands. These miracle, magical, life-giving hands. Oh, just tobe near them, touch them, maybe even lick one?",
        "response":"Alright, just one. [she licks his hands rather emphatically] Wow, you're good atthat.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't understand, why didn't you help that man?",
        "response":"Uhh, cause, uhh, I'm a neurosurgeon and that was clearly a case of, uh, uh, foodalchokage. Alright, look, I got to tell you something.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no no no, you don't have to tell me anything. You don't have to explainyourself to me. Ooh, who am I to question the great Dr. Drake Remore?",
        "response":"But that's what...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no no no, you don't have to tell me anything. You don't have to explainyourself to me. Ooh, who am I to question the great Dr. Drake Remore?",
        "response":"But that's what...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Meet me in the nocturnal house in 15 minutes.",
        "response":"Uhh, hey look, I don't really enjoy being with other men <i>that</i> way. But, um,zoo dollars?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uhh, hey look, I don't really enjoy being with other men <i>that</i> way. But, um,zoo dollars?",
        "response":"It's about your monkey. It's alive.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But that's what...",
        "response":"I should just be happy to be near you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey what?",
        "response":"That's it, just hey. Like at the end of a dance, HEY! [she starts nibbling his hand]Hey. He-hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thank you for coming everybody. There're cookies in the back.",
        "response":"That was great, the kids loved you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I should just be happy to be near you.",
        "response":"Hey I- [she cuts him off with a kiss]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I should just be happy to be near you.",
        "response":"Hey I- [she cuts him off with a kiss]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But that's what...",
        "response":"I should just be happy to be near you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey I- [she cuts him off with a kiss]",
        "response":"Hey what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey I- [she cuts him off with a kiss]",
        "response":"Hey what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That was great, the kids loved you.",
        "response":"Yay, I rock.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That was great, the kids loved you.",
        "response":"Yay, I rock.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I sense these things. It was either but or butter.",
        "response":"The thing is, I think some of the parents, they were kinda hopin' that you'd playmore songs about like, barnyard animals.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yay, I rock.",
        "response":"And you know why? Because you told the truth, and nobody ever tells kids thetruth.You were incredible.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yay, I rock.",
        "response":"And you know why? Because you told the truth, and nobody ever tells kids thetruth.You were incredible.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How did you know there was a but?",
        "response":"I sense these things. It was either but or butter.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How did you know there was a but?",
        "response":"I sense these things. It was either but or butter.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And you know why? Because you told the truth, and nobody ever tells kids thetruth.You were incredible.",
        "response":"But.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And you know why? Because you told the truth, and nobody ever tells kids thetruth.You were incredible.",
        "response":"But.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But.",
        "response":"How did you know there was a but?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But.",
        "response":"How did you know there was a but?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I sense these things. It was either but or butter.",
        "response":"The thing is, I think some of the parents, they were kinda hopin' that you'd playmore songs about like, barnyard animals.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The thing is, I think some of the parents, they were kinda hopin' that you'd playmore songs about like, barnyard animals.",
        "response":"I can do that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The thing is, I think some of the parents, they were kinda hopin' that you'd playmore songs about like, barnyard animals.",
        "response":"I can do that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Because that would be fantastic. What? You wanna kiss me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Because that would be fantastic. What? You wanna kiss me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can do that.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can do that.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah, right. There was a break-in, few months back, inside job. Your monkeywas taken.",
        "response":"Oh my God. But the zoo told me that my monkey was dead.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah, right. There was a break-in, few months back, inside job. Your monkeywas taken.",
        "response":"Oh my God. But the zoo told me that my monkey was dead.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahh, the bat. Ambassador of darkness, flitting out of his cave like a wingedmessenger, sightless spectre of the macabe.",
        "response":"Buddy, my monkey?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Buddy, my monkey?",
        "response":"Oh, yeah, right. There was a break-in, few months back, inside job. Your monkeywas taken.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Buddy, my monkey?",
        "response":"Oh, yeah, right. There was a break-in, few months back, inside job. Your monkeywas taken.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God. But the zoo told me that my monkey was dead.",
        "response":"The zoo! Do you believe everything the zoo tells ya?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God. But the zoo told me that my monkey was dead.",
        "response":"The zoo! Do you believe everything the zoo tells ya?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The zoo! Do you believe everything the zoo tells ya?",
        "response":"That, that's the only thing the zoo's ever told me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Because that would be fantastic. What? You wanna kiss me?",
        "response":"Thinkin' about it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That, that's the only thing the zoo's ever told me.",
        "response":"Of course they're gonna say he's dead. They don't want the bad publicity. It'sall a great big cover-up. Do you have any idea how high up this thing goes?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That, that's the only thing the zoo's ever told me.",
        "response":"Of course they're gonna say he's dead. They don't want the bad publicity. It'sall a great big cover-up. Do you have any idea how high up this thing goes?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Of course they're gonna say he's dead. They don't want the bad publicity. It'sall a great big cover-up. Do you have any idea how high up this thing goes?",
        "response":"That guy Lipson?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Of course they're gonna say he's dead. They don't want the bad publicity. It'sall a great big cover-up. Do you have any idea how high up this thing goes?",
        "response":"That guy Lipson?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The zoo! Do you believe everything the zoo tells ya?",
        "response":"That, that's the only thing the zoo's ever told me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Lipson knows. Do you have any idea who else knows?",
        "response":"No, I, I only know Lipson.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Lipson knows. Do you have any idea who else knows?",
        "response":"No, I, I only know Lipson.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That guy Lipson?",
        "response":"Lipson knows. Do you have any idea who else knows?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That guy Lipson?",
        "response":"Lipson knows. Do you have any idea who else knows?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I, I only know Lipson.",
        "response":"Hmm, Lipson knows huh? Ahh, hello Mr. Opossum, enigma of the trees, upside-downdenizen of the night, taunting gravity with...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I, I only know Lipson.",
        "response":"Hmm, Lipson knows huh? Ahh, hello Mr. Opossum, enigma of the trees, upside-downdenizen of the night, taunting gravity with...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hmm, Lipson knows huh? Ahh, hello Mr. Opossum, enigma of the trees, upside-downdenizen of the night, taunting gravity with...",
        "response":"Buddy, my monkey, my monkey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hmm, Lipson knows huh? Ahh, hello Mr. Opossum, enigma of the trees, upside-downdenizen of the night, taunting gravity with...",
        "response":"Buddy, my monkey, my monkey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Buddy, my monkey, my monkey.",
        "response":"Word on the street - well, when I say street, I mean those little pretend streetsthey have here at the zoo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Buddy, my monkey, my monkey.",
        "response":"Word on the street - well, when I say street, I mean those little pretend streetsthey have here at the zoo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Word on the street - well, when I say street, I mean those little pretend streetsthey have here at the zoo.",
        "response":"Of course.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Word on the street - well, when I say street, I mean those little pretend streetsthey have here at the zoo.",
        "response":"Of course.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Of course.",
        "response":"Your monkey found a new career, in the entertainment field. That's all I know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Your monkey found a new career, in the entertainment field. That's all I know.",
        "response":"This is unbelievable.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Your monkey found a new career, in the entertainment field. That's all I know.",
        "response":"This is unbelievable.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Of course.",
        "response":"Your monkey found a new career, in the entertainment field. That's all I know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, what is this information worth to you, my friend?",
        "response":"Are you trying to get me to bribe you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, what is this information worth to you, my friend?",
        "response":"Are you trying to get me to bribe you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This is unbelievable.",
        "response":"So, what is this information worth to you, my friend?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This is unbelievable.",
        "response":"So, what is this information worth to you, my friend?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you trying to get me to bribe you?",
        "response":"Maybe.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you trying to get me to bribe you?",
        "response":"Maybe.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, so what're you gonna do?",
        "response":"Well, I guess I'm gonna call the beer company and try to find out where he is.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<b>[Scene: Library. Ross show up with a MonkeyShine Beer poster.]</b>",
        "response":"Check it out, he actually is the MonkeyShine monkey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But you already told me everything.",
        "response":"<b>[Scene: Library. Ross show up with a MonkeyShine Beer poster.]</b>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No no no, wait, I wanna see what happens.",
        "response":"Uh, I get Leslie out of the coma and then we make out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Check it out, he actually is the MonkeyShine monkey.",
        "response":"Well, so what're you gonna do?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi Phoebe.",
        "response":"Today we're gonna start with some songs about barnyard animals.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God, quick turn off the TV.",
        "response":"No no no, wait, I wanna see what happens.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe.",
        "response":"But you already told me everything.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, hi again.",
        "response":"Hi Phoebe.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right, they uh, they choppered me in. What's up?",
        "response":"Ohh, and I see you're having a little party too. Is she here, huh, huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right, they uh, they choppered me in. What's up?",
        "response":"Ohh, and I see you're having a little party too. Is she here, huh, huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How did you get here so fast, I just saw you in Salem?",
        "response":"Right, they uh, they choppered me in. What's up?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How did you get here so fast, I just saw you in Salem?",
        "response":"Right, they uh, they choppered me in. What's up?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, I get Leslie out of the coma and then we make out.",
        "response":"Well how can that be, you were just kissing Sabrina?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No no no, wait, I wanna see what happens.",
        "response":"Uh, I get Leslie out of the coma and then we make out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Erica, c'mon in.",
        "response":"How did you get here so fast, I just saw you in Salem?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohh, and I see you're having a little party too. Is she here, huh, huh?",
        "response":"Who?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohh, and I see you're having a little party too. Is she here, huh, huh?",
        "response":"Who?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You told me I was the only one. [throws a glass of water in his face]",
        "response":"Alright look, that's it. I don't think we should see each other anymore, alright.Look, I know I should have told you this a long time ago but I am not Drake Remore, OK.I'm not even a doctor, I'm an actor. I just pretend to be a doctor.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You told me I was the only one. [throws a glass of water in his face]",
        "response":"Alright look, that's it. I don't think we should see each other anymore, alright.Look, I know I should have told you this a long time ago but I am not Drake Remore, OK.I'm not even a doctor, I'm an actor. I just pretend to be a doctor.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright look, that's it. I don't think we should see each other anymore, alright.Look, I know I should have told you this a long time ago but I am not Drake Remore, OK.I'm not even a doctor, I'm an actor. I just pretend to be a doctor.",
        "response":"Oh my God. Do the people at the hospital know about this?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sabrina. I know about you two. I saw you today kissing in the doctor's lounge.",
        "response":"It's not what you think, that was...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sabrina. I know about you two. I saw you today kissing in the doctor's lounge.",
        "response":"It's not what you think, that was...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's not what you think, that was...",
        "response":"You told me I was the only one. [throws a glass of water in his face]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's not what you think, that was...",
        "response":"You told me I was the only one. [throws a glass of water in his face]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Who?",
        "response":"Sabrina. I know about you two. I saw you today kissing in the doctor's lounge.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Who?",
        "response":"Sabrina. I know about you two. I saw you today kissing in the doctor's lounge.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright look, that's it. I don't think we should see each other anymore, alright.Look, I know I should have told you this a long time ago but I am not Drake Remore, OK.I'm not even a doctor, I'm an actor. I just pretend to be a doctor.",
        "response":"Oh my God. Do the people at the hospital know about this?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, I'm afraid it is. You deserve much better than me Erica. You deserve to be withthe real Drake, he's the one you fell in love with. Go to Salem, find him, he's the guyfor you.",
        "response":"Oh Hans. [They kiss]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Is all this true?",
        "response":"Yes, I'm afraid it is. You deserve much better than me Erica. You deserve to be withthe real Drake, he's the one you fell in love with. Go to Salem, find him, he's the guyfor you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right. Goodbye Erica, good luck in Salem. Take care",
        "response":"I'll never forget you Hans. [Joey shuts the door in her face]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God. Do the people at the hospital know about this?",
        "response":"Somebody wanna help me out here?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"'Cause it's a television show.",
        "response":"Drake, what're you getting at?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"'Cause it's a television show.",
        "response":"Drake, what're you getting at?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How, how can you be here and there.",
        "response":"'Cause it's a television show.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Drake, what're you getting at?",
        "response":"I'm not Drake.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The library board has had a lot of complaints from parents about some of the stuff inyour songs.",
        "response":"I can't believe it. Did you tell your board about how kids want to hear the truth?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The library board has had a lot of complaints from parents about some of the stuff inyour songs.",
        "response":"I can't believe it. Did you tell your board about how kids want to hear the truth?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Fired! Why?",
        "response":"The library board has had a lot of complaints from parents about some of the stuff inyour songs.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'll never forget you Hans. [Joey shuts the door in her face]",
        "response":"OK, alright, the people who threw the water.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I see.",
        "response":"Maybe if you just played some regular kiddie songs.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't believe it. Did you tell your board about how kids want to hear the truth?",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't believe it. Did you tell your board about how kids want to hear the truth?",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"I see.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"I see.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe if you just played some regular kiddie songs.",
        "response":"No. What do you, what do you want me to be, like some stupid, big, like, purpledinosaur?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe if you just played some regular kiddie songs.",
        "response":"No. What do you, what do you want me to be, like some stupid, big, like, purpledinosaur?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. What do you, what do you want me to be, like some stupid, big, like, purpledinosaur?",
        "response":"I'm not saying you have to be Barney.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. What do you, what do you want me to be, like some stupid, big, like, purpledinosaur?",
        "response":"I'm not saying you have to be Barney.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Excuse me. Is this where the singing lady is that tells the truth?",
        "response":"Um, yeah I guess that's me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I see.",
        "response":"Maybe if you just played some regular kiddie songs.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know.",
        "response":"I finally get a part on TV and the monkey's makin' movies.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm not saying you have to be Barney.",
        "response":"Who's Barney.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This is amazing.",
        "response":"I know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Closed set. We know but we're friends with the monkey. [guard lets them in]",
        "response":"Good morning. Hey pal, look who I brought. It's your old friend Harry Elefante.[Marcel grabs the elephant doll and throws it to the ground]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Good morning. Hey pal, look who I brought. It's your old friend Harry Elefante.[Marcel grabs the elephant doll and throws it to the ground]",
        "response":"Woah, dude, burn.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Good morning. Hey pal, look who I brought. It's your old friend Harry Elefante.[Marcel grabs the elephant doll and throws it to the ground]",
        "response":"Woah, dude, burn.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"SECURITY GUARD: I'm sorry guys, closed set.",
        "response":"Uh, I'm sorry, you don't understand, I'm, I'm, I'm a friend of his. We uh, we usedto live together.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey don't take it personal, he's under a lot of pressure, ya know, starring in amovie and all.",
        "response":"Now just how big of a star is Marcel?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, excuse me, uh, where can we find the monkey?",
        "response":"SECURITY GUARD: I'm sorry guys, closed set.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Woah, dude, burn.",
        "response":"I don't get it, he seemed so happy to see me yesterday.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Now just how big of a star is Marcel?",
        "response":"In human terms, I'd say Cybill Shepard.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, yeah I guess that's me.",
        "response":"[shouting out the door] She's here.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK. Um, how come I'm walking with you?",
        "response":"Well, we're, we're just goin' over here so that we can get away from the <b>horribleflesh eating virus, for the love of God woman, listen to me.</b> Is he lookin', is helookin'?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It looks like one of her eyebrows fell down. Now unless someone convinces her tolet me bleach it, Jean-Claude Van Damme is gonna be making out with Gabe Kaplan.",
        "response":"DIRECTOR'S ASSISTANT: I'll talk to her.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DIRECTOR'S ASSISTANT: Is it bad?",
        "response":"It looks like one of her eyebrows fell down. Now unless someone convinces her tolet me bleach it, Jean-Claude Van Damme is gonna be making out with Gabe Kaplan.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DIRECTOR'S ASSISTANT: Tell me.",
        "response":"I can't do Chris's makeup. She refuses to acknowledge that she has a moustasche.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't do Chris's makeup. She refuses to acknowledge that she has a moustasche.",
        "response":"DIRECTOR'S ASSISTANT: Is it bad?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, excuse me. Jerry is the director, which one's he?",
        "response":"DIRECTOR'S ASSISTANT: The one in the director's chair.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DIRECTOR'S ASSISTANT: The one in the director's chair.",
        "response":"Gotcha. Phoebs, walk with me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Gotcha. Phoebs, walk with me.",
        "response":"OK. Um, how come I'm walking with you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We've got a problem.",
        "response":"DIRECTOR'S ASSISTANT: Tell me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I hate actors.",
        "response":"[to an extra in fatigues] Nice camoflauge man, for a minute there I almostdidn't see ya.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[to an extra in fatigues] Nice camoflauge man, for a minute there I almostdidn't see ya.",
        "response":"Excuse me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[to an extra in fatigues] Nice camoflauge man, for a minute there I almostdidn't see ya.",
        "response":"Excuse me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DIRECTOR'S ASSISTANT: I'll talk to her.",
        "response":"I hate actors.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, is your name Chandler?",
        "response":"Uh, yes, yes it is.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahhhh.",
        "response":"Uh, is your name Chandler?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahhhh.",
        "response":"Uh, is your name Chandler?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Excuse me.",
        "response":"Ahhhh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Excuse me.",
        "response":"Ahhhh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm Susie Moss. Fourth grade, glasses, I used to carry around a box of animalcrackers like a purse.",
        "response":"Susie Moss, right, yeah, wow, you look. . . great job growing up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm Susie Moss. Fourth grade, glasses, I used to carry around a box of animalcrackers like a purse.",
        "response":"Susie Moss, right, yeah, wow, you look. . . great job growing up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Do you know me or are you just really good at this game?",
        "response":"I'm Susie Moss. Fourth grade, glasses, I used to carry around a box of animalcrackers like a purse.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Do you know me or are you just really good at this game?",
        "response":"I'm Susie Moss. Fourth grade, glasses, I used to carry around a box of animalcrackers like a purse.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chandler Bing?",
        "response":"Do you know me or are you just really good at this game?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chandler Bing?",
        "response":"Do you know me or are you just really good at this game?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, is your name Chandler?",
        "response":"Uh, yes, yes it is.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, yes, yes it is.",
        "response":"Chandler Bing?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, yes, yes it is.",
        "response":"Chandler Bing?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Remember the class play? You, you pulled up my skirt and the entire auditorium sawmy underpants.",
        "response":"Yes, back then I, uh, used humor as a defense mechanism. Thank God I don't dothat anymore.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, right, well yeah, I graduated fourth grade and realized I wasn't a pimp.",
        "response":"Remember the class play? You, you pulled up my skirt and the entire auditorium sawmy underpants.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, right, well yeah, I graduated fourth grade and realized I wasn't a pimp.",
        "response":"Remember the class play? You, you pulled up my skirt and the entire auditorium sawmy underpants.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's nice to see you're not still wearing that denim cap with all the littlemirrors on it.",
        "response":"Oh, right, well yeah, I graduated fourth grade and realized I wasn't a pimp.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's nice to see you're not still wearing that denim cap with all the littlemirrors on it.",
        "response":"Oh, right, well yeah, I graduated fourth grade and realized I wasn't a pimp.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Susie Moss, right, yeah, wow, you look. . . great job growing up.",
        "response":"It's nice to see you're not still wearing that denim cap with all the littlemirrors on it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Susie Moss, right, yeah, wow, you look. . . great job growing up.",
        "response":"It's nice to see you're not still wearing that denim cap with all the littlemirrors on it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What what what what?",
        "response":"Jean-Claude Van Damme. I didn't know he was in this movie, he is so hot.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.",
        "response":"What what what what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The muscles from Brussels, wham bam Van Damme, did you see <i>Time Cop</i>?",
        "response":"No, was he any good in it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The muscles from Brussels, wham bam Van Damme, did you see <i>Time Cop</i>?",
        "response":"No, was he any good in it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ya think?",
        "response":"The muscles from Brussels, wham bam Van Damme, did you see <i>Time Cop</i>?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ya think?",
        "response":"The muscles from Brussels, wham bam Van Damme, did you see <i>Time Cop</i>?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Jean-Claude Van Damme. I didn't know he was in this movie, he is so hot.",
        "response":"Ya think?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Jean-Claude Van Damme. I didn't know he was in this movie, he is so hot.",
        "response":"Ya think?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What what what what?",
        "response":"Jean-Claude Van Damme. I didn't know he was in this movie, he is so hot.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, was he any good in it?",
        "response":"Rachel, he like, totally changed time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, was he any good in it?",
        "response":"Rachel, he like, totally changed time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What, so you go over there, you tell him you think he's cute, what's the worstthat could happen?",
        "response":"He could hear me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What, so you go over there, you tell him you think he's cute, what's the worstthat could happen?",
        "response":"He could hear me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah.",
        "response":"What, so you go over there, you tell him you think he's cute, what's the worstthat could happen?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah.",
        "response":"What, so you go over there, you tell him you think he's cute, what's the worstthat could happen?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rachel, he like, totally changed time.",
        "response":"Wow, so why don't you go talk to him?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rachel, he like, totally changed time.",
        "response":"Wow, so why don't you go talk to him?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow, so why don't you go talk to him?",
        "response":"Oh, yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow, so why don't you go talk to him?",
        "response":"Oh, yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He could hear me.",
        "response":"OK, I'm doin' it for ya.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"VAN DAMME: You don't think I'm cute?",
        "response":"I, I don't know, um, do you think you're cute? OK, we're kinda gettin' off thetrack here. Um, I was supposed to come here and tell you my friend thinks you're cute. Sowhat should I tell her?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, this is gonna sound kinda goofy but uhhm, my friend over there, who cooks bythe way, um, she thinks you're cute.",
        "response":"VAN DAMME: You don't think I'm cute?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, Stephen Hurs was the kid who would eat anything for money, David Stein wasthe guy who had no elbows.",
        "response":"OK, well then who was the kid that got caught masturbating?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"VAN DAMME: Hi.",
        "response":"Um, this is gonna sound kinda goofy but uhhm, my friend over there, who cooks bythe way, um, she thinks you're cute.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, I'm doin' it for ya.",
        "response":"Oh Rachel don't, don't you dare, don't, <b>don't</b>. Tell him I cook.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, I'm doin' it for ya.",
        "response":"Oh Rachel don't, don't you dare, don't, <b>don't</b>. Tell him I cook.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh Rachel don't, don't you dare, don't, <b>don't</b>. Tell him I cook.",
        "response":"Excuse me. Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He could hear me.",
        "response":"OK, I'm doin' it for ya.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Excuse me. Hi.",
        "response":"VAN DAMME: Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, so listen, how many times am I gonna have to touch you on the arm before youask me on a date.",
        "response":"Well, uh, let's try one more. . . there you go, say Ernie's, 8 o'clock.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, so listen, how many times am I gonna have to touch you on the arm before youask me on a date.",
        "response":"Well, uh, let's try one more. . . there you go, say Ernie's, 8 o'clock.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, uh, let's try one more. . . there you go, say Ernie's, 8 o'clock.",
        "response":"I'll be there, and who knows, if things go well, maybe this time I'll get to seeyour underwear.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, uh, let's try one more. . . there you go, say Ernie's, 8 o'clock.",
        "response":"I'll be there, and who knows, if things go well, maybe this time I'll get to seeyour underwear.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh uh, o, OK.",
        "response":"Um, so listen, how many times am I gonna have to touch you on the arm before youask me on a date.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh uh, o, OK.",
        "response":"Um, so listen, how many times am I gonna have to touch you on the arm before youask me on a date.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, well then who was the kid that got caught masturbating?",
        "response":"OK that's not what he was doing. Alright, he was looking for his bus money.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'll be there, and who knows, if things go well, maybe this time I'll get to seeyour underwear.",
        "response":"No one was around to hear that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh that's me, I gotta go.",
        "response":"Oh uh, o, OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rachel if you, if you want to go out with him, you can. Sound like a big jerk tome but if that's what you want to do...",
        "response":"Jean-Claude she said yes, I'll see you tonight. Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He just kept asking, and asking, and asking, and asking, and asking, and asking.",
        "response":"Rachel if you, if you want to go out with him, you can. Sound like a big jerk tome but if that's what you want to do...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He just kept asking, and asking, and asking, and asking, and asking, and asking.",
        "response":"Rachel if you, if you want to go out with him, you can. Sound like a big jerk tome but if that's what you want to do...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Agh, what a jerk. I kept talking about you and he kept asking me out. I mean,naturally, you know, I said no.",
        "response":"Well, thanks anyway.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Agh, what a jerk. I kept talking about you and he kept asking me out. I mean,naturally, you know, I said no.",
        "response":"Well, thanks anyway.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So what'd he say?",
        "response":"Agh, what a jerk. I kept talking about you and he kept asking me out. I mean,naturally, you know, I said no.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Jean-Claude she said yes, I'll see you tonight. Thank you.",
        "response":"<b>[Scene: Central Perk. Joey and the girls are sitting at the couches.]</b>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, thanks anyway.",
        "response":"He just kept asking, and asking, and asking, and asking, and asking, and asking.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, thanks anyway.",
        "response":"He just kept asking, and asking, and asking, and asking, and asking, and asking.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And then Jean-Claude took me to that place Crossroads and that's where we hung outwith Drew Barrymore.",
        "response":"Oh man, she's so smokin, she has got the greatest set of. . . no guys around, huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<b>[Scene: Central Perk. Joey and the girls are sitting at the couches.]</b>",
        "response":"And then Jean-Claude took me to that place Crossroads and that's where we hung outwith Drew Barrymore.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Joey I have to cancel racketball for tonight, that was Marcel's trainer. He'sgonna let me have him for a couple of hours.",
        "response":"You're blowin' me off for a monkey?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Does anybody need anything?",
        "response":"Oh, I'll have an espresso. Oh acutally, I'll get it. If I ask you to, you'llprobably end up drinking it yourself.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I'll have an espresso. Oh acutally, I'll get it. If I ask you to, you'llprobably end up drinking it yourself.",
        "response":"That is so unfair.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh man, she's so smokin, she has got the greatest set of. . . no guys around, huh.",
        "response":"Does anybody need anything?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, we can rescedule for Saturday.",
        "response":"Yeah, unless you hook up with a bunch of pigeons.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're blowin' me off for a monkey?",
        "response":"Hey, we can rescedule for Saturday.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're blowin' me off for a monkey?",
        "response":"Hey, we can rescedule for Saturday.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well then, how do you know when vegetables are done?",
        "response":"Well you know, you juist, you eat them and you can tell.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well then, how do you know when vegetables are done?",
        "response":"Well you know, you juist, you eat them and you can tell.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, OK, I don't eat meat.",
        "response":"Well then, how do you know when vegetables are done?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, OK, I don't eat meat.",
        "response":"Well then, how do you know when vegetables are done?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Like, when you're cooking a steak.",
        "response":"Oh, OK, I don't eat meat.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Like, when you're cooking a steak.",
        "response":"Oh, OK, I don't eat meat.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, stick a fork in me, I am done.",
        "response":"Stick a fork what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Stick a fork what?",
        "response":"Like, when you're cooking a steak.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Stick a fork what?",
        "response":"Like, when you're cooking a steak.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I've met the perfect woman. OK, we're sitting on her couch, we're foolingaround, and then suddenly she turns to me and says, 'Do you ever want to do it in anelevator?'",
        "response":"What did you say?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What did you say?",
        "response":"Ahh, I believe my exact words were, 'Flaign,en - sten'. I mean I didn't knowwhat to say, how do you know if you wanna do it on an elevator?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, ye, yes, actually, but, uh, they were my Aunt Edna's, and there were threeof us in there.",
        "response":"Well I was thinking it would be um, kind of sexy if you wore mine tonight, atdinner.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, ye, yes, actually, but, uh, they were my Aunt Edna's, and there were threeof us in there.",
        "response":"Well I was thinking it would be um, kind of sexy if you wore mine tonight, atdinner.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, shoot, we gotta go, got a reservation in 30 minutes.",
        "response":"Oh no no no no, no no no no no no, you see, what I had planned shouldn't takemore that 2, 3 minutes tops.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But um, here's an idea, have you ever worn women's underwear?",
        "response":"Well, ye, yes, actually, but, uh, they were my Aunt Edna's, and there were threeof us in there.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh no no no no, no no no no no no, you see, what I had planned shouldn't takemore that 2, 3 minutes tops.",
        "response":"Oh, 200 seconds of passion. We gotta go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well I was thinking it would be um, kind of sexy if you wore mine tonight, atdinner.",
        "response":"You want me to wear your panties?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well you know, you juist, you eat them and you can tell.",
        "response":"OK, then, eat me, I'm done.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, Rachel, why don't you start talking first.",
        "response":"Alright, I feel that this is totally unjustified. [Monica starts making facesbehind her back] She gave me the green light, I did nothing but-. Do you think I can't seeyou in the TV set?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well I was thinking it would be um, kind of sexy if you wore mine tonight, atdinner.",
        "response":"You want me to wear your panties?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, got the music, got the dinner. Oh and check it out, I made Marcel's favoritedish, banannacake.",
        "response":"Oooh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"With mealworms.",
        "response":"Yaaahhh. Ahhh, candles. What'dya thinks gonna happen here tonight?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Could ya?",
        "response":"Well, if I was wearing your underwear then, uh, what would you be wearing?. . .You're swell.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You want me to wear your panties?",
        "response":"Could ya?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You want me to wear your panties?",
        "response":"Could ya?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oooh.",
        "response":"With mealworms.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oooh.",
        "response":"With mealworms.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, I feel that this is totally unjustified. [Monica starts making facesbehind her back] She gave me the green light, I did nothing but-. Do you think I can't seeyou in the TV set?",
        "response":"Alright Monica, if there is something that you would like to share...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes you did. Absolutely.",
        "response":"Would you let me talk. [flicks Monica on the forehead]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ya know, you had no right to go out with him.",
        "response":"That is the most ridiculous.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I did not sell you out.",
        "response":"Yes you did. Absolutely.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I did not sell you out.",
        "response":"Yes you did. Absolutely.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You sold me out.",
        "response":"I did not sell you out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You sold me out.",
        "response":"I did not sell you out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That is the most ridiculous.",
        "response":"You sold me out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That is the most ridiculous.",
        "response":"You sold me out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did you just flick me?",
        "response":"OK, well, you wouldn't let me finish and I was jus- [Monica flicks her back] Ow.That hurt [flicks Monica]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did you just flick me?",
        "response":"OK, well, you wouldn't let me finish and I was jus- [Monica flicks her back] Ow.That hurt [flicks Monica]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, well, you wouldn't let me finish and I was jus- [Monica flicks her back] Ow.That hurt [flicks Monica]",
        "response":"Quit flicking [flicks]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, well, you wouldn't let me finish and I was jus- [Monica flicks her back] Ow.That hurt [flicks Monica]",
        "response":"Quit flicking [flicks]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Would you let me talk. [flicks Monica on the forehead]",
        "response":"Did you just flick me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Would you let me talk. [flicks Monica on the forehead]",
        "response":"Did you just flick me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes you did. Absolutely.",
        "response":"Would you let me talk. [flicks Monica on the forehead]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Quit flicking [flicks]",
        "response":"Ow, you stop flicking.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Quit flicking [flicks]",
        "response":"Ow, you stop flicking.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh.",
        "response":"You want me to just call him up and tell him that you're seeing him instead?That's what you want?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh.",
        "response":"You want me to just call him up and tell him that you're seeing him instead?That's what you want?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You want me to just call him up and tell him that you're seeing him instead?That's what you want?",
        "response":"OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You want me to just call him up and tell him that you're seeing him instead?That's what you want?",
        "response":"OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, what do you, you want me to stop seeing him, is that what you want?",
        "response":"Uh-huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ow, you stop flicking.",
        "response":"You flicked me first.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh that's what you want.",
        "response":"Yes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK.",
        "response":"Oh that's what you want.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK.",
        "response":"Oh that's what you want.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, assistant to the director. That's a really exciting job, I mean, you must have aton of cool responsibilities.",
        "response":"DIRECTOR'S ASSISTANT: I have nothing to do with casting.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How come all I can think about is putting that ice in my mouth and licking you allover?",
        "response":"Because I went to an all boys high school and God is making up for it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Because I went to an all boys high school and God is making up for it.",
        "response":"I want you right here, right now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Because I went to an all boys high school and God is making up for it.",
        "response":"I want you right here, right now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DIRECTOR'S ASSISTANT: I have nothing to do with casting.",
        "response":"So what're you guys gonna eat?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh that's what you want.",
        "response":"Yes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Fine.",
        "response":"Fine,",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes.",
        "response":"Fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes.",
        "response":"Fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right now, right here. Don't ya think we're in kind of a public plaaaa [Susiegrabs him under the table] They do have the shrimp.",
        "response":"Meet me in the bathroom. [she leaves for the bathroom]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right now, right here. Don't ya think we're in kind of a public plaaaa [Susiegrabs him under the table] They do have the shrimp.",
        "response":"Meet me in the bathroom. [she leaves for the bathroom]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I want you right here, right now.",
        "response":"Right now, right here. Don't ya think we're in kind of a public plaaaa [Susiegrabs him under the table] They do have the shrimp.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I want you right here, right now.",
        "response":"Right now, right here. Don't ya think we're in kind of a public plaaaa [Susiegrabs him under the table] They do have the shrimp.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright mister, let's see those panties.",
        "response":"Alrighty. [we see Chandler's pants drop from under the stall door]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't believe we're doing this.",
        "response":"Alright mister, let's see those panties.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't believe we're doing this.",
        "response":"Alright mister, let's see those panties.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Meet me in the bathroom. [she leaves for the bathroom]",
        "response":"I'm going to the bathroom now. [leaves for the bathroom]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon.",
        "response":"I can't believe we're doing this.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alrighty. [we see Chandler's pants drop from under the stall door]",
        "response":"Ooh. Ooh. But ya know what would be even sexier?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alrighty. [we see Chandler's pants drop from under the stall door]",
        "response":"Ooh. Ooh. But ya know what would be even sexier?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright mister, let's see those panties.",
        "response":"Alrighty. [we see Chandler's pants drop from under the stall door]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"If you didn't have your shirt tucked into them.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"If you didn't have your shirt tucked into them.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh. Ooh. But ya know what would be even sexier?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh. Ooh. But ya know what would be even sexier?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"If you didn't have your shirt tucked into them.",
        "response":"Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"If you didn't have your shirt tucked into them.",
        "response":"Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright. Now I would like to see you wearing nothing but them. Take your clothesoff.",
        "response":"OK, but uh, I hope you realize this means we're gonna miss hearing about thespecials.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright. Now I would like to see you wearing nothing but them. Take your clothesoff.",
        "response":"OK, but uh, I hope you realize this means we're gonna miss hearing about thespecials.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, but uh, I hope you realize this means we're gonna miss hearing about thespecials.",
        "response":"C'mon hurry, hurry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, but uh, I hope you realize this means we're gonna miss hearing about thespecials.",
        "response":"C'mon hurry, hurry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh.",
        "response":"Alright. Now I would like to see you wearing nothing but them. Take your clothesoff.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh.",
        "response":"Alright. Now I would like to see you wearing nothing but them. Take your clothesoff.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's your name?",
        "response":"My name is Cassandra. You can ask me anything.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon hurry, hurry.",
        "response":"Hey, do you want this done quick, or do you want this done right?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon hurry, hurry.",
        "response":"Hey, do you want this done quick, or do you want this done right?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, somebody's been doing his buns of steel video.",
        "response":"Well, you want me to uh, clench anything, or-... Susie? Susie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, do you want this done quick, or do you want this done right?",
        "response":"Alright, turn around. Time to see you from behind.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, do you want this done quick, or do you want this done right?",
        "response":"Alright, turn around. Time to see you from behind.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh? Where, whaddya mean?",
        "response":"Whaddo I mean. Whaddya mean, whaddo I mean? I mean underpants, mister, that's whatI mean.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you want me to uh, clench anything, or-... Susie? Susie.",
        "response":"This is for the fourth grade.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you want me to uh, clench anything, or-... Susie? Susie.",
        "response":"This is for the fourth grade.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, turn around. Time to see you from behind.",
        "response":"OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This is for the fourth grade.",
        "response":"Huh? Where, whaddya mean?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This is for the fourth grade.",
        "response":"Huh? Where, whaddya mean?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That was in the fourth grade. How could you still be upset about that?",
        "response":"Well um, why don't you call me in 20 years and tell me if you're still upset aboutthis. [she leaves with his clothes]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That was in the fourth grade. How could you still be upset about that?",
        "response":"Well um, why don't you call me in 20 years and tell me if you're still upset aboutthis. [she leaves with his clothes]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"My skirt, you lifted, kids laughing. I was Susie Underpants 'till I was 18.",
        "response":"That was in the fourth grade. How could you still be upset about that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"My skirt, you lifted, kids laughing. I was Susie Underpants 'till I was 18.",
        "response":"That was in the fourth grade. How could you still be upset about that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What, what's what you mean?",
        "response":"My skirt, you lifted, kids laughing. I was Susie Underpants 'till I was 18.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What, what's what you mean?",
        "response":"My skirt, you lifted, kids laughing. I was Susie Underpants 'till I was 18.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh? Where, whaddya mean?",
        "response":"Whaddo I mean. Whaddya mean, whaddo I mean? I mean underpants, mister, that's whatI mean.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whaddo I mean. Whaddya mean, whaddo I mean? I mean underpants, mister, that's whatI mean.",
        "response":"What, what's what you mean?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whaddo I mean. Whaddya mean, whaddo I mean? I mean underpants, mister, that's whatI mean.",
        "response":"What, what's what you mean?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't believe this, just like 2 weeks ago I was watching <i>Sudden Death</i>,now I'm on a date with Jean-Claude Van Damme. Can you beat up that guy? [he nods] Can youbeat up that guy?",
        "response":"VAN DAMME: Sure.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well um, why don't you call me in 20 years and tell me if you're still upset aboutthis. [she leaves with his clothes]",
        "response":"Alright, I hope you realize you're not getting these underpants back.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This is so wild. Ya know, I gotta admit, I was kinda surprised that you agreed togo on a blind date.",
        "response":"VAN DAMME: Normally, I would not do it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"VAN DAMME: Sure.",
        "response":"This is so wild. Ya know, I gotta admit, I was kinda surprised that you agreed togo on a blind date.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"VAN DAMME: Normally, I would not do it.",
        "response":"Well, what made you make the exception for me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Say you're sorry.",
        "response":"No. [hitting each other]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. [hitting each other]",
        "response":"Say it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. [hitting each other]",
        "response":"Say it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Say it.",
        "response":"No. [hitting again]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, you wanna play? OK, let's play, let's play. [She grabs a jar of tomato sauceand Monica's purse]",
        "response":"What're you gonna do?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, you wanna play? OK, let's play, let's play. [She grabs a jar of tomato sauceand Monica's purse]",
        "response":"What're you gonna do?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Say you're sorry.",
        "response":"OK, you wanna play? OK, let's play, let's play. [She grabs a jar of tomato sauceand Monica's purse]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Say you're sorry.",
        "response":"OK, you wanna play? OK, let's play, let's play. [She grabs a jar of tomato sauceand Monica's purse]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rachel, you say you're sorry or your sweater gets it.",
        "response":"OK, OK, that is my favorite sweater, that is my third date sweater.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What're you gonna do?",
        "response":"You give me back my sweater or it's handbag marinara.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What're you gonna do?",
        "response":"You give me back my sweater or it's handbag marinara.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, OK, that is my favorite sweater, that is my third date sweater.",
        "response":"Say you're sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, OK, that is my favorite sweater, that is my third date sweater.",
        "response":"Say you're sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh alright, stop, <b>STOP THE MADNESS</b>. This is crazy. Who can even rememberwhy this even started in the first place?",
        "response":"[Monica and Rachel start yelling at the same time]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Monica and Rachel start yelling at the same time]",
        "response":"Yes that's right. But still, I-, look at your purse, look at your sweater, look atyourselves.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You don't have the guts.",
        "response":"Oh yeah. Well, at least I wasn't too chicken to tell some guy I thought he wascute.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry that I made you stop seeing him.",
        "response":"Well, I'm sorry I went out with him when I knew you liked him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'll help you throw out your purse.",
        "response":"I'm sorry that I made you stop seeing him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'll help you throw out your purse.",
        "response":"I'm sorry that I made you stop seeing him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You give me back my sweater or it's handbag marinara.",
        "response":"You don't have the guts.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You give me back my sweater or it's handbag marinara.",
        "response":"You don't have the guts.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'll help you fix your sweater.",
        "response":"I'll help you throw out your purse.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I'm sorry I went out with him when I knew you liked him.",
        "response":"I'm sorry that I borrowed your gloves [pulls Rachel's gloves out of her purse]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chandler? What're you still doin' here, I though you guys took off.",
        "response":"Oh, no no no, she took off with my clothes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chandler? What're you still doin' here, I though you guys took off.",
        "response":"Oh, no no no, she took off with my clothes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry that I made you stop seeing him.",
        "response":"Well, I'm sorry I went out with him when I knew you liked him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey!",
        "response":"Chandler? What're you still doin' here, I though you guys took off.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey!",
        "response":"Chandler? What're you still doin' here, I though you guys took off.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey?",
        "response":"Ma?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ma?",
        "response":"Joey!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ma?",
        "response":"Joey!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, this is the first time.",
        "response":"Wow, talk about your bad luck, I mean, the first time you try panties and someonewalks off with your clothes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Not exactly. . . I'm wearin panties.",
        "response":"Huh, you uh, you always wear panties?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Not exactly. . . I'm wearin panties.",
        "response":"Huh, you uh, you always wear panties?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh, you uh, you always wear panties?",
        "response":"No, no, this is the first time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh, you uh, you always wear panties?",
        "response":"No, no, this is the first time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, no no no, she took off with my clothes.",
        "response":"Are you naked in there?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, no no no, she took off with my clothes.",
        "response":"Are you naked in there?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you naked in there?",
        "response":"Not exactly. . . I'm wearin panties.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you naked in there?",
        "response":"Not exactly. . . I'm wearin panties.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow, talk about your bad luck, I mean, the first time you try panties and someonewalks off with your clothes.",
        "response":"I was not trying them out, Susie asked me to wear them.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow, talk about your bad luck, I mean, the first time you try panties and someonewalks off with your clothes.",
        "response":"I was not trying them out, Susie asked me to wear them.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. I'm not letting you or anybody else see, ever.",
        "response":"Alright, alright. [climbs up in the next stall and looks over at Chandler] Woah,someone's flossing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, this is the first time.",
        "response":"Wow, talk about your bad luck, I mean, the first time you try panties and someonewalks off with your clothes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[to Joey who's looking over a toilet stall] Joey, some people don't like that.",
        "response":"Chandler's wearing panties.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I was not trying them out, Susie asked me to wear them.",
        "response":"Well, let me see.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I was not trying them out, Susie asked me to wear them.",
        "response":"Well, let me see.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, let me see.",
        "response":"No. I'm not letting you or anybody else see, ever.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, let me see.",
        "response":"No. I'm not letting you or anybody else see, ever.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How can you not be wearing any underwear?",
        "response":"Oh, I'm gettin' heat from the guy in the hot pink thong.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? Let me see. [climbs up in the other adjoining stall]",
        "response":"No, no, you don't have to see.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chandler's wearing panties.",
        "response":"What? Let me see. [climbs up in the other adjoining stall]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, one of you give me your underpants.",
        "response":"Can't help you, I'm not wearing any.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Can't help you, I'm not wearing any.",
        "response":"How can you not be wearing any underwear?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Can't help you, I'm not wearing any.",
        "response":"How can you not be wearing any underwear?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi Tushie.",
        "response":"Alright, one of you give me your underpants.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, you don't have to see.",
        "response":"Hi Tushie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, you don't have to see.",
        "response":"Hi Tushie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"One of the virus victims called in sick, so Cathy recommended me and boom, I'm dyingon the gurney. Oh Ross, Marcel just finished his last scene if you want to go down thereand say goodbye.",
        "response":"Ahh, oh that's OK, I mean, he's probably got, you know, parties to go to and stuff.But, ya know, he's moved on. Hey, that, that's the way it goes right.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What happened?",
        "response":"One of the virus victims called in sick, so Cathy recommended me and boom, I'm dyingon the gurney. Oh Ross, Marcel just finished his last scene if you want to go down thereand say goodbye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What happened?",
        "response":"One of the virus victims called in sick, so Cathy recommended me and boom, I'm dyingon the gurney. Oh Ross, Marcel just finished his last scene if you want to go down thereand say goodbye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahh, oh that's OK, I mean, he's probably got, you know, parties to go to and stuff.But, ya know, he's moved on. Hey, that, that's the way it goes right.",
        "response":"[sees Marcel at the window] Oh my God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I'm gettin' heat from the guy in the hot pink thong.",
        "response":"Alright look Ross I'll give you 50 dollars for your underpants.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How can you not be wearing any underwear?",
        "response":"Oh, I'm gettin' heat from the guy in the hot pink thong.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, bye for me too. [kisses him]",
        "response":"OK, well, bye-bye again. [kisses him again]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[sees Marcel at the window] Oh my God.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, hey, and I'm in the movie.",
        "response":"What happened?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Who are you?",
        "response":"I'm Cassandra. An intelligent dialogue system. What else do you what to know?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey. Hold on a second. [shoots a goal] Huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. Oh, except one of the strings on my guitar is broken. Hey, Chandler, can Iborrow your G-string?",
        "response":"How long you been waitin' to say that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah.",
        "response":"Yeah. Oh, except one of the strings on my guitar is broken. Hey, Chandler, can Iborrow your G-string?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey. Hold on a second. [shoots a goal] Huh?",
        "response":"Nice, nice. Hey I got somethin' for you. [hands Chandler an envelope.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nice, nice. Hey I got somethin' for you. [hands Chandler an envelope.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line07\"></a> CHANDLER: What's this?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How long you been waitin' to say that?",
        "response":"About 20 minutes. <font size=\"4\"><b>CLOSING CREDITS</b></font>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know, I think I want to write a song about all this.",
        "response":"Oh yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line07\"></a> CHANDLER: What's this?",
        "response":"Eight hundred and twelve bucks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, well, bye-bye again. [kisses him again]",
        "response":"OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I don't know what Big Leon told ya but it's an even thousand if you wantme for the whole night. What is this for?",
        "response":"Well, I'm makin money now and this is payin' you back for head shots, electricbills, and so many slices of pizza I can't even count. I love ya man.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, this is a little extra somethin' for uh, ya know, always bein' there for me.[hands Chandler a jewelry box]",
        "response":"<a name=\"line09\"></a> CHANDLER: Wow, I don't know what to say. [opens the box and pullsout an incredibly gaudy gold bracelet] Wow, I, I don't know what to say.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I'm makin money now and this is payin' you back for head shots, electricbills, and so many slices of pizza I can't even count. I love ya man.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line08\"></a> CHANDLER: Well, thanks man. Now I can get my pony.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line08\"></a> CHANDLER: Well, thanks man. Now I can get my pony.",
        "response":"Hey, this is a little extra somethin' for uh, ya know, always bein' there for me.[hands Chandler a jewelry box]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line09\"></a> CHANDLER: Wow, I don't know what to say. [opens the box and pullsout an incredibly gaudy gold bracelet] Wow, I, I don't know what to say.",
        "response":"Heh, what d'ya say?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Eight hundred and twelve bucks.",
        "response":"Well, I don't know what Big Leon told ya but it's an even thousand if you wantme for the whole night. What is this for?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know. It's a bracelet.",
        "response":"Isn't it? And it's engraved too, check it out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know. It's a bracelet.",
        "response":"Isn't it? And it's engraved too, check it out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Heh, what d'ya say?",
        "response":"I don't know. It's a bracelet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, now? [puts it in his desk drawer] No, no, I think something this nice shouldbe saved for a special occasion. [sets a chair in front of the drawer]",
        "response":"<a name=\"line10\"></a> JOEY: Oh, no no, that's the beauty part, it goes with everything.[gets the bracelet from the drawer] You put this on, you're good to go. [puts the braceleton Chandler] Ohhh man, you are so wearin' that bracelet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line10\"></a> JOEY: Oh, no no, that's the beauty part, it goes with everything.[gets the bracelet from the drawer] You put this on, you're good to go. [puts the braceleton Chandler] Ohhh man, you are so wearin' that bracelet.",
        "response":"I so am.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line11\"></a> JOEY: You have any idea what this'll do for your sex life?",
        "response":"Well, it'll probably slow it down at first but, once I get used to the extraweight, I'll be back on track.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Put it on.",
        "response":"Oh, now? [puts it in his desk drawer] No, no, I think something this nice shouldbe saved for a special occasion. [sets a chair in front of the drawer]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Isn't it? And it's engraved too, check it out.",
        "response":"[reads] To my best bud. [puts it back in the case] Thanks best bud.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Isn't it? And it's engraved too, check it out.",
        "response":"[reads] To my best bud. [puts it back in the case] Thanks best bud.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I so am.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line11\"></a> JOEY: You have any idea what this'll do for your sex life?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[reads] To my best bud. [puts it back in the case] Thanks best bud.",
        "response":"Put it on.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[reads] To my best bud. [puts it back in the case] Thanks best bud.",
        "response":"Put it on.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, lets see if you're as good in person as you are on paper. Make me asalad.",
        "response":"A salad? Really I, I could do something a little more complicated if you like.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, lets see if you're as good in person as you are on paper. Make me asalad.",
        "response":"A salad? Really I, I could do something a little more complicated if you like.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that's there on the bottom, see the manager, Chandler Bing.",
        "response":"Alright, lets see if you're as good in person as you are on paper. Make me asalad.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line01\"></a> INTERVIEWER: And if I want to call for a reference on your last job?",
        "response":"Oh, that's there on the bottom, see the manager, Chandler Bing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"A salad? Really I, I could do something a little more complicated if you like.",
        "response":"No, just a salad will be fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"A salad? Really I, I could do something a little more complicated if you like.",
        "response":"No, just a salad will be fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Great.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line01\"></a> INTERVIEWER: And if I want to call for a reference on your last job?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, just a salad will be fine.",
        "response":"You got it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, just a salad will be fine.",
        "response":"You got it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Now, I want you to tell me what you're doing while you're doing it.",
        "response":"Alright, well I'm tearing the lettuce.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Now, I want you to tell me what you're doing while you're doing it.",
        "response":"Alright, well I'm tearing the lettuce.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You got it.",
        "response":"Now, I want you to tell me what you're doing while you're doing it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You got it.",
        "response":"Now, I want you to tell me what you're doing while you're doing it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh-oh, no no don't worry, I'm gonna wash it.",
        "response":"Don't, I like it dirty.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh. Is it dirty?",
        "response":"Oh-oh, no no don't worry, I'm gonna wash it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh. Is it dirty?",
        "response":"Oh-oh, no no don't worry, I'm gonna wash it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, well I'm tearing the lettuce.",
        "response":"Uh-huh. Is it dirty?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, well I'm tearing the lettuce.",
        "response":"Uh-huh. Is it dirty?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, uh, what are you going to do next?",
        "response":"Well, I thought that I would cut up the tomatos.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, uh, what are you going to do next?",
        "response":"Well, I thought that I would cut up the tomatos.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh-oh, no no don't worry, I'm gonna wash it.",
        "response":"Don't, I like it dirty.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I thought that I would cut up the tomatos.",
        "response":"Are they, uh, firm?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I thought that I would cut up the tomatos.",
        "response":"Are they, uh, firm?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's your call.",
        "response":"So, uh, what are you going to do next?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's your call.",
        "response":"So, uh, what are you going to do next?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Don't, I like it dirty.",
        "response":"That's your call.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Don't, I like it dirty.",
        "response":"That's your call.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You gonna slice them up real nice?",
        "response":"Actually, I was gonna do them jullienne.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You sure they haven't gone bad? You're sure they're not very, very bad?",
        "response":"No really, they're OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You sure they haven't gone bad? You're sure they're not very, very bad?",
        "response":"No really, they're OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"They'r alright.",
        "response":"You sure they haven't gone bad? You're sure they're not very, very bad?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"They'r alright.",
        "response":"You sure they haven't gone bad? You're sure they're not very, very bad?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No really, they're OK.",
        "response":"You gonna slice them up real nice?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No really, they're OK.",
        "response":"You gonna slice them up real nice?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are they, uh, firm?",
        "response":"They'r alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are they, uh, firm?",
        "response":"They'r alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, she's goin' somewhere.",
        "response":"C'mon you guys. It's a known fact that lobsters fall in love and mate for life.You know what, you can actually see old lobster couples walkin' around their tank, yaknow, holding claws like. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I think that fifth shower actually got the interview off me.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line03\"></a> PHOEBE: So, do you have any other possibilities?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line13\"></a> ROSS: Wha, OK, now how do you know that?",
        "response":"Because she's your lobster.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hang in there, it's gonna happen.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line13\"></a> ROSS: Wha, OK, now how do you know that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You gonna slice them up real nice?",
        "response":"Actually, I was gonna do them jullienne.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Actually, I was gonna do them jullienne.",
        "response":"Aaaahhhhhhh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Actually, I was gonna do them jullienne.",
        "response":"Aaaahhhhhhh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Because she's your lobster.",
        "response":"Oh, she's goin' somewhere.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Aaaahhhhhhh.",
        "response":"I'm outa here. [Monica leaves]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No no no, if I couldn't pay you back right away then I'd feel guilty and tenseevery time I saw you.",
        "response":"Oh OK. Well then why don't you, uhh, why don't you borrow it from mom and dad? Youfeel guilty and tense around them already. You might as well make some money off of them.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Man, man that is sharp. It must have cost you quite a few debloons.",
        "response":"<b>[Scene: Monica and Rachel's apartment. Monica answers the door and lets her parents in.They are carrying boxes.]</b>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Monica, if you want, I can lend you some money.",
        "response":"No no no, if I couldn't pay you back right away then I'd feel guilty and tenseevery time I saw you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Monica, if you want, I can lend you some money.",
        "response":"No no no, if I couldn't pay you back right away then I'd feel guilty and tenseevery time I saw you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line03\"></a> PHOEBE: So, do you have any other possibilities?",
        "response":"Oh yeah, well there's the possibility that I won't make rent.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ya know, the man's got a point. [gestures with his arm and the bracelet fallsoff]",
        "response":"<a name=\"line04\"></a> PHOEBE: What is that sparkly thing?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah, well there's the possibility that I won't make rent.",
        "response":"Monica, if you want, I can lend you some money.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<b>[Scene: Monica and Rachel's apartment. Monica answers the door and lets her parents in.They are carrying boxes.]</b>",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line04\"></a> PHOEBE: What is that sparkly thing?",
        "response":"That thing, it's a uhh. . . yeah it's, it's a little flashy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line06\"></a> PHOEBE: OK. Ooh, OK, you gotta give me a second, I wanna get thisjust right. [she sticks out her gut, clears her throat and sniffs her nose and then in herbest male voice. . .] Dude, 11 o'clock, totally hot babe checkin' you out. That was reallygood, I think I'm ready for my penis now.",
        "response":"[walks over to the woman] I know what you're thinking, Dave Thomas, founder ofWendy's.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I'm alright, thanks.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line06\"></a> PHOEBE: OK. Ooh, OK, you gotta give me a second, I wanna get thisjust right. [she sticks out her gut, clears her throat and sniffs her nose and then in herbest male voice. . .] Dude, 11 o'clock, totally hot babe checkin' you out. That was reallygood, I think I'm ready for my penis now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, well, you know, they're just separated so, you know, never know, we'll see.",
        "response":"MR. GELLER: Well, I can't say any of us were surprised. Your parents have been unhappyever since we've known them. Especially after that incident in Hawaii.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow, that is a surprise. Just one little question, uh, why not Ross's room?",
        "response":"MR. GELLER: Gosh, we talked about that but your brother has so many science trophies andplaques and merit badges, well we didn't want to disturb them.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. GELLER: Well, I can't say any of us were surprised. Your parents have been unhappyever since we've known them. Especially after that incident in Hawaii.",
        "response":"What, what incident?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. GELLER: Gosh, we talked about that but your brother has so many science trophies andplaques and merit badges, well we didn't want to disturb them.",
        "response":"Oh, God forbid.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GELLER: Oh, we were so sorry to hear about your parents splitting up, dear.",
        "response":"Oh, well, you know, they're just separated so, you know, never know, we'll see.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"MRS. GELLER: Oh, we were so sorry to hear about your parents splitting up, dear.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Who is your creator?",
        "response":"I was created by Yordan Petrov and Emanuela Mollova.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I think she's OK.",
        "response":"[Rachel, laughing, puts a hand on the guy's shoulder] Look at that, look at that,see how she's pushing him away and he won't budge. Alright, I'm gonna do something. [walksup in the middle of their conversation] Excuse me, are you Rachel?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Rachel, laughing, puts a hand on the guy's shoulder] Look at that, look at that,see how she's pushing him away and he won't budge. Alright, I'm gonna do something. [walksup in the middle of their conversation] Excuse me, are you Rachel?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Would you look at that guy, I mean how long has he been talking to her. It's like,back off buddy she's a waitress not a geisha.",
        "response":"I think she's OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah, easy for you to say, you don't have to walk around sporting somereject from the Mr. T collection. [Joey walks in behind Chandler]",
        "response":"Chandler, Chandler.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's not that bad.",
        "response":"Oh, yeah, easy for you to say, you don't have to walk around sporting somereject from the Mr. T collection. [Joey walks in behind Chandler]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chandler. [waves his arm around, exposing the bracelet]",
        "response":"I, I really have to be somewhere but it was nice meeting you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[walks over to the woman] I know what you're thinking, Dave Thomas, founder ofWendy's.",
        "response":"I'm Gail.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm Gail.",
        "response":"Chandler. [waves his arm around, exposing the bracelet]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm Gail.",
        "response":"Chandler. [waves his arm around, exposing the bracelet]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, oh my God, is this the wrong day? I don't believe it, uh, well, hey, I guess ifit works out we'll, we'll have something to tell the grandkids.",
        "response":"Sure will. I've uh, gotta go. Take care.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What are you, what are you doin'?",
        "response":"Oh, oh my God, is this the wrong day? I don't believe it, uh, well, hey, I guess ifit works out we'll, we'll have something to tell the grandkids.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sure will. I've uh, gotta go. Take care.",
        "response":"OK, see ya later, nice meeting you. [man leaves] You're welcome.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm Ross Geller. Wha, I'm, God in your add you said you were pretty but wow.",
        "response":"What are you, what are you doin'?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm Ross Geller. Wha, I'm, God in your add you said you were pretty but wow.",
        "response":"What are you, what are you doin'?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I'm Ross Geller. Wha, I'm, God in your add you said you were pretty but wow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I'm Ross Geller. Wha, I'm, God in your add you said you were pretty but wow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, see ya later, nice meeting you. [man leaves] You're welcome.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I was saving you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Saving, saving, saving me from the pleasant conversation with the interesting man,saving me?",
        "response":"Oh, see from where I was sitting I uh. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Saving, saving, saving me from the pleasant conversation with the interesting man,saving me?",
        "response":"Oh, see from where I was sitting I uh. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, see from where I was sitting I uh. . .",
        "response":"OK, Ross, listen to me, I am not yours to save.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, see from where I was sitting I uh. . .",
        "response":"OK, Ross, listen to me, I am not yours to save.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I was saving you.",
        "response":"Saving, saving, saving me from the pleasant conversation with the interesting man,saving me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I was saving you.",
        "response":"Saving, saving, saving me from the pleasant conversation with the interesting man,saving me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, Ross, listen to me, I am not yours to save.",
        "response":"But, you are.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, Ross, listen to me, I am not yours to save.",
        "response":"But, you are.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I was saving you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, you know what, are, are you being like, the blind date guy again?",
        "response":"No no, you're uh, you're my lobster. See um, lobsters, uhh, in the tank when, whenthey're old, uhh, they get with, uhh, they walk around holding the claws. In the tank, yaknow, with, with the holding and. . . Uhh, Phoebs you wanna help me out with the, thewhole lobster thing?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No no, you're uh, you're my lobster. See um, lobsters, uhh, in the tank when, whenthey're old, uhh, they get with, uhh, they walk around holding the claws. In the tank, yaknow, with, with the holding and. . . Uhh, Phoebs you wanna help me out with the, thewhole lobster thing?",
        "response":"Do the claws again.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, uh, well you're, umm, you're my lobster.",
        "response":"OK, you know what, are, are you being like, the blind date guy again?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, uh, well you're, umm, you're my lobster.",
        "response":"OK, you know what, are, are you being like, the blind date guy again?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Do the claws again.",
        "response":"Rach. OK, forget, forget the lobsters OK. We're, let's talk, what about us?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Uh, uh, well you're, umm, you're my lobster.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Uh, uh, well you're, umm, you're my lobster.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But, you are.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But, you are.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, listen to me. I fell for you and I get clobbered. You then fall for me and Iagain, somehow, get clobbered. I'm tired of being clobbered, ya know, it's, it's just notworth it.",
        "response":"Well, but, but. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, listen to me. I fell for you and I get clobbered. You then fall for me and Iagain, somehow, get clobbered. I'm tired of being clobbered, ya know, it's, it's just notworth it.",
        "response":"Well, but, but. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, but. . .",
        "response":"No, listen to me. I fell for you and I get clobbered. You then fall for me and Iagain, somehow, get clobbered. I'm tired of being clobbered, ya know, it's, it's just notworth it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, but. . .",
        "response":"No, listen to me. I fell for you and I get clobbered. You then fall for me and Iagain, somehow, get clobbered. I'm tired of being clobbered, ya know, it's, it's just notworth it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rach. OK, forget, forget the lobsters OK. We're, let's talk, what about us?",
        "response":"Ross, there is no us, OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, but, but. . .",
        "response":"NO but Ross. We are never gonna happen, OK. Accept that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, but, but. . .",
        "response":"NO but Ross. We are never gonna happen, OK. Accept that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ross, there is no us, OK.",
        "response":"No, but. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ross, there is no us, OK.",
        "response":"No, but. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line17\"></a> JOEY: Well, what about the fact that you insulted the bracelet andyou made fun of me?",
        "response":"OK, well that's the part where I'm a wank. But I was hoping we wouldn't focus onthat. [Joey goes to his room and shuts the door] Hey, c'mon man, I said I was sorry like ahundred times, I promise I will never take it off my. . . [notices the bracelet is missingfrom his wrist] wrist. But if, if you want to stay in there and be mad, you know, you justuh, you stay in there. [he starts searching the room, lifting up the couch cushions]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, doesn't the fact that I wore the bracelet even though I hated it saysomething about our friendship and how much it means to me?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line17\"></a> JOEY: Well, what about the fact that you insulted the bracelet andyou made fun of me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GELLER: Hi, darling. Where's my grandson, you didn't bring him?",
        "response":"No, he's at uh, Carol's and Susan's today.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey guys.",
        "response":"MRS. GELLER: Hi, darling. Where's my grandson, you didn't bring him?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"NO but Ross. We are never gonna happen, OK. Accept that.",
        "response":"E-except, except that what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"NO but Ross. We are never gonna happen, OK. Accept that.",
        "response":"E-except, except that what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"E-except, except that what?",
        "response":"No, no, ACC-cept that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"E-except, except that what?",
        "response":"No, no, ACC-cept that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, ACC-cept that.",
        "response":"Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line27\"></a> PHOEBE: Would you stop already? Get out of the bitter barn and playin the hay.",
        "response":"Oh, you're right I, I should play in the hay. Forget about the fact that I justdropped 400 dollars to replace a bracelet that I hated to begin with. Bring on the hay.[sits down at the bar]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, but that's probably 'cause I haven't asked them yet.",
        "response":"C'mon Monica, do it. Hey, you guys, um, Monica has some news.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't believe it.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line27\"></a> PHOEBE: Would you stop already? Get out of the bitter barn and playin the hay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Emotional hell. So, did they lend you the money yet?",
        "response":"No, but that's probably 'cause I haven't asked them yet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What am I gonna do, huh? [Joey walks in behind him]",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"How come you have two?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"How come you have two?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I can't. No no, listen, I, I know how much this means to you and I also knowthat this is about more than just jewelry, [puts bracelet on Joey] it's about you and meand the fact that we're [reading bracelet] best buds.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line20\"></a> JOEY: Wow, is this friendship? I think so. Check it out, we'rebracelet buddies.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line19\"></a> JOEY: Get out.",
        "response":"No, I can't. No no, listen, I, I know how much this means to you and I also knowthat this is about more than just jewelry, [puts bracelet on Joey] it's about you and meand the fact that we're [reading bracelet] best buds.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, yeah I mean, you get your money and you learn a little something, what's wrongwith that?",
        "response":"Nothin', nothin', hey you're a cheapasaurus. I'm kidding, I'm kidding, thank you,I'm very greatful.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line20\"></a> JOEY: Wow, is this friendship? I think so. Check it out, we'rebracelet buddies.",
        "response":"That's what they'll call us.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You have dinosaur checks?",
        "response":"Yeah, yeah I mean, you get your money and you learn a little something, what's wrongwith that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You have dinosaur checks?",
        "response":"Yeah, yeah I mean, you get your money and you learn a little something, what's wrongwith that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Here you go, you can pay me back whenever you like.",
        "response":"You have dinosaur checks?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well this one's for you.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line19\"></a> JOEY: Get out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How come you have two?",
        "response":"Well this one's for you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Shoot, I think I got mayonaise on you.",
        "response":"Oh, that's OK, it's just the shoulder, it's not my dress.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Shoot, I think I got mayonaise on you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Shoot, I think I got mayonaise on you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, dad, turn it off.",
        "response":"MR. GELLER: It is off.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahh, so do you, beautiful. [they hug]",
        "response":"Oops.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Rachel enters] Oh.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oops.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oops.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[the shoulders of her dress keep falling off her shoulders] Is my hook unhooked?These things keep falling down, I can't. . .",
        "response":"Uh, hold, let me see, I don't know. So what're you gonna do. . . [doorbell rings]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[the shoulders of her dress keep falling off her shoulders] Is my hook unhooked?These things keep falling down, I can't. . .",
        "response":"Uh, hold, let me see, I don't know. So what're you gonna do. . . [doorbell rings]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, you know, I'm just gonna, I'm gonna hang out, work on my music.",
        "response":"[the shoulders of her dress keep falling off her shoulders] Is my hook unhooked?These things keep falling down, I can't. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, you know, I'm just gonna, I'm gonna hang out, work on my music.",
        "response":"[the shoulders of her dress keep falling off her shoulders] Is my hook unhooked?These things keep falling down, I can't. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, thanks. So, uh, what are you gonna do this summer?",
        "response":"Oh, you know, I'm just gonna, I'm gonna hang out, work on my music.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, hold, let me see, I don't know. So what're you gonna do. . . [doorbell rings]",
        "response":"Oh, the guys are here.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, hold, let me see, I don't know. So what're you gonna do. . . [doorbell rings]",
        "response":"Oh, the guys are here.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. GELLER: It is off.",
        "response":"Dad, it is not. What's with the red light?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Who is your father?",
        "response":"My father is Yordan Petrov.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, alright, but you better be wearing clothes when I open my eyes.",
        "response":"Alright open your eyes. [opens his eyes to see two black leather recliners and a bigscreen TV]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. GELLER: Atta boy. [Ross scrambles upstairs to change]</i>",
        "response":"OK, you guys, ya know, I think we've seen enough, let's turn it off.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Dad, she won't want to go with me.",
        "response":"MR. GELLER: Of course she would, you're a college man.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, no peeking. No peeking, no peeking, no peeking.",
        "response":"Alright, alright, but you better be wearing clothes when I open my eyes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK. Hold my board.",
        "response":"MR. GELLER: Atta boy. [Ross scrambles upstairs to change]</i>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. GELLER: Of course she would, you're a college man.",
        "response":"I don't know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, you guys, ya know, I think we've seen enough, let's turn it off.",
        "response":"No, no, no.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, the guys are here.",
        "response":"this summer?</i>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, no.",
        "response":"OK, fine, well I'm not gonna watch, alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, alright, but you better be wearing clothes when I open my eyes.",
        "response":"Alright open your eyes. [opens his eyes to see two black leather recliners and a bigscreen TV]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright open your eyes. [opens his eyes to see two black leather recliners and a bigscreen TV]",
        "response":"Sweet mother of all that is good and pure.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright open your eyes. [opens his eyes to see two black leather recliners and a bigscreen TV]",
        "response":"Sweet mother of all that is good and pure.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know.",
        "response":"<a>chandler</a>: Now we can finally watch <i>Green Acres</i> the way it was meant to beseen.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sweet mother of all that is good and pure.",
        "response":"Huh? <i>Days of our Lives</i> picked up my option.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sweet mother of all that is good and pure.",
        "response":"Huh? <i>Days of our Lives</i> picked up my option.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh? <i>Days of our Lives</i> picked up my option.",
        "response":"Congratulations!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh? <i>Days of our Lives</i> picked up my option.",
        "response":"Congratulations!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Congratulations!",
        "response":"I know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So uh, which one is mine?",
        "response":"Whichever one you want, man. Whichever one you want. [Chandler starts to sit in oneof the chairs] Not that one.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So uh, which one is mine?",
        "response":"Whichever one you want, man. Whichever one you want. [Chandler starts to sit in oneof the chairs] Not that one.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whichever one you want, man. Whichever one you want. [Chandler starts to sit in oneof the chairs] Not that one.",
        "response":"[sits down] Ohh yes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whichever one you want, man. Whichever one you want. [Chandler starts to sit in oneof the chairs] Not that one.",
        "response":"[sits down] Ohh yes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a>chandler</a>: Now we can finally watch <i>Green Acres</i> the way it was meant to beseen.",
        "response":"Uh-huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[sits down] Ohh yeah, that's the stuff.",
        "response":"[reaches for the footrest lever] Do we dare?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[sits down] Ohh yes.",
        "response":"[sits down] Ohh yeah, that's the stuff.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[sits down] Ohh yes.",
        "response":"[sits down] Ohh yeah, that's the stuff.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh.",
        "response":"So uh, which one is mine?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[beeper goes off] Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got to get to the museum. So um, I'll see youtonight.",
        "response":"OK. [they go to kiss but everyone's watching so Ross just kisses her on the top ofher head and leaves]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK. [they go to kiss but everyone's watching so Ross just kisses her on the top ofher head and leaves]",
        "response":"Bye guys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[walks up to Rachel in front of the TV] Tonight?",
        "response":"CHANDLER and JOEY: Hey, yo. [they move from out of in front of the TV]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, uh, how was your day?",
        "response":"Oh you know, pretty much the usual, uh, sun shining, birds chirping.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh you know, pretty much the usual, uh, sun shining, birds chirping.",
        "response":"Really? Mine too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[sits down] Ohh yeah, that's the stuff.",
        "response":"[reaches for the footrest lever] Do we dare?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[reaches for the footrest lever] Do we dare?",
        "response":"We dare.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi you guys.",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Tonight you're supposed to waitress for me, my catering thing, any of those wordstrigger anything for you?",
        "response":"God, oh God Monica, I forgot. This is our first date.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Tonight you're supposed to waitress for me, my catering thing, any of those wordstrigger anything for you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Tonight you're supposed to waitress for me, my catering thing, any of those wordstrigger anything for you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"CHANDLER and JOEY: Hey, yo. [they move from out of in front of the TV]",
        "response":"What's tonight?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's tonight?",
        "response":"It is our first official date. Our first date.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It is our first official date. Our first date.",
        "response":"Uh, hello.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It is our first official date. Our first date.",
        "response":"Uh, hello.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, hello.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, hello.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I've been great, just great. How have you been? [tilting her head]",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: Oh, well obviously you know Barbara and I split up, otherwise you wouldn't havedone the head tilt.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: Monica? My God you used to be so. . . I mean you, you, you, you must have lostlike. . . You look great.",
        "response":"Thank you. This is my friend Phoebe. She's gonna be helping me tonight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thank you. This is my friend Phoebe. She's gonna be helping me tonight.",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: Hi Phoebe, nice to meet you. [Phoebe just giggles when they shake] So, how yabeen?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: Hi Phoebe, nice to meet you. [Phoebe just giggles when they shake] So, how yabeen?",
        "response":"I've been great, just great. How have you been? [tilting her head]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Tonight you're supposed to waitress for me, my catering thing, any of those wordstrigger anything for you?",
        "response":"God, oh God Monica, I forgot. This is our first date.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Dr. Burke, it, it's me.",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: Monica? My God you used to be so. . . I mean you, you, you, you must have lostlike. . . You look great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: Ah, that's OK, come on in. Um, I'm sorry, is Monica Geller coming? I was toldshe was.",
        "response":"Dr. Burke, it, it's me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sorry we're late.",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: Ah, that's OK, come on in. Um, I'm sorry, is Monica Geller coming? I was toldshe was.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"God, oh God Monica, I forgot. This is our first date.",
        "response":"Yes but my mom got me this job.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: No no, it, it's fine, believe me. I do it too. I always answer with the 'I'mOK' head bob. [demonstrates] 'I'm OK.' [tilts head] 'You sure?' [bobs head] 'Yeah, I'mfine.' Hey listen, I've got to set up the music. I got a new CD changer, of course thedivorce only left me with 4 CD's to change.",
        "response":"[her and Phoebe tilt their heads] Oh, that's too bad.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry.",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: No no, it, it's fine, believe me. I do it too. I always answer with the 'I'mOK' head bob. [demonstrates] 'I'm OK.' [tilts head] 'You sure?' [bobs head] 'Yeah, I'mfine.' Hey listen, I've got to set up the music. I got a new CD changer, of course thedivorce only left me with 4 CD's to change.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, two larges, extra cheese on both. But listen, don't ring the buzzer for 19,ring 20, Geller-Green, they'll let you in, OK. If you buzz our door, there's no tip foryou. OK, thanks. Pizza's on the way. I told you we wouldn't have to get up.",
        "response":"What if we have to pee?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: Yeah, since the divorce, when anybody asks me how I am, it's always with asympathetic head tilt. [demonstrating] 'How ya doin'? You OK?'",
        "response":"I'm sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The head tilt?",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: Yeah, since the divorce, when anybody asks me how I am, it's always with asympathetic head tilt. [demonstrating] 'How ya doin'? You OK?'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: Oh, well obviously you know Barbara and I split up, otherwise you wouldn't havedone the head tilt.",
        "response":"The head tilt?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You've got to get back out there, it's your party.",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: But they're so dull, they're all opthamologists.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Where are you?",
        "response":"I'm in Sofia, Bulgaria. Any clues?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What if we have to pee?",
        "response":"I'll cancel the sodas.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, you are so much the smitten kitten. You should ask him out.",
        "response":"Dr. Burke? I don't think so. I mean, like, he's a grown up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, you are so much the smitten kitten. You should ask him out.",
        "response":"Dr. Burke? I don't think so. I mean, like, he's a grown up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So. You two are totally into each other.",
        "response":"Phoebe, he's a friend of my parents. He's like 20 years older than me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Dr. Burke? I don't think so. I mean, like, he's a grown up.",
        "response":"So. You two are totally into each other.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Dr. Burke? I don't think so. I mean, like, he's a grown up.",
        "response":"So. You two are totally into each other.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: But they're so dull, they're all opthamologists.",
        "response":"You're an opthamologist.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I am not.",
        "response":"Oh, you are so much the smitten kitten. You should ask him out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I am not.",
        "response":"Oh, you are so much the smitten kitten. You should ask him out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You are so smitten.",
        "response":"I am not.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebe, he's a friend of my parents. He's like 20 years older than me.",
        "response":"OK, so what, you're just never gonna see him again?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebe, he's a friend of my parents. He's like 20 years older than me.",
        "response":"OK, so what, you're just never gonna see him again?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, so what, you're just never gonna see him again?",
        "response":"Not never. I mean, I'm gonna see him tomorrow at my eye appointment.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, so what, you're just never gonna see him again?",
        "response":"Not never. I mean, I'm gonna see him tomorrow at my eye appointment.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Not never. I mean, I'm gonna see him tomorrow at my eye appointment.",
        "response":"Didn't you like, just get your eyes checked?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Not never. I mean, I'm gonna see him tomorrow at my eye appointment.",
        "response":"Didn't you like, just get your eyes checked?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon, I'm not saying it was a bad movie, I'm just saying, you know, it was alittle. . . hard to follow.",
        "response":"I told you there was going to be sub-titles.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So. You two are totally into each other.",
        "response":"Phoebe, he's a friend of my parents. He's like 20 years older than me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Didn't you like, just get your eyes checked?",
        "response":"Well yeah, but, you know, uh, 27 is a dangerous eye age.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It would really help when I'm kissing you if you didn't shout out my sister's name.",
        "response":"Honey, I'm just checking.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It would really help when I'm kissing you if you didn't shout out my sister's name.",
        "response":"Honey, I'm just checking.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I told you there was going to be sub-titles.",
        "response":"I know, I just didn't want to wear my glasses on my first date.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Monica.",
        "response":"It would really help when I'm kissing you if you didn't shout out my sister's name.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, I just didn't want to wear my glasses on my first date.",
        "response":"[They start kissing.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Honey, I'm just checking.",
        "response":"Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Honey, I'm just checking.",
        "response":"Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[They start kissing.]",
        "response":"Monica.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh.",
        "response":"Monica.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What, what.",
        "response":"I'm sorry. Oh God, I'm sorry, it's just that when you moved your hands down to mybutt, it was like woah, Ross's hands are on my butt. Sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Since they're alone they start kissing and Ross's hands work their way down until they'reon Rachel's butt. Rachel starts laughing.]",
        "response":"What, what.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mon.",
        "response":"[Since they're alone they start kissing and Ross's hands work their way down until they'reon Rachel's butt. Rachel starts laughing.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Monica.",
        "response":"Mon.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Monica.",
        "response":"Mon.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mon.",
        "response":"Monica.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mon.",
        "response":"Monica.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Monica.",
        "response":"Mon.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh.",
        "response":"Monica.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well it's not, honey I'm sorry, I guess I'm just nervous. I mean, it's you, yaknow, it's us. I mean, we're crossing that line, sort of a big thing.",
        "response":"I, I know it's big, I just didn't know it was uh, ha-ha big.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well it's not, honey I'm sorry, I guess I'm just nervous. I mean, it's you, yaknow, it's us. I mean, we're crossing that line, sort of a big thing.",
        "response":"I, I know it's big, I just didn't know it was uh, ha-ha big.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And that's, that's funny why?",
        "response":"Well it's not, honey I'm sorry, I guess I'm just nervous. I mean, it's you, yaknow, it's us. I mean, we're crossing that line, sort of a big thing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And that's, that's funny why?",
        "response":"Well it's not, honey I'm sorry, I guess I'm just nervous. I mean, it's you, yaknow, it's us. I mean, we're crossing that line, sort of a big thing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry. Oh God, I'm sorry, it's just that when you moved your hands down to mybutt, it was like woah, Ross's hands are on my butt. Sorry.",
        "response":"And that's, that's funny why?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry. Oh God, I'm sorry, it's just that when you moved your hands down to mybutt, it was like woah, Ross's hands are on my butt. Sorry.",
        "response":"And that's, that's funny why?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I, I know it's big, I just didn't know it was uh, ha-ha big.",
        "response":"OK. [start kissing again and Rachel starts lauging again]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I, I know it's big, I just didn't know it was uh, ha-ha big.",
        "response":"OK. [start kissing again and Rachel starts lauging again]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK. [start kissing again and Rachel starts lauging again]",
        "response":"OK, my hands were no where near your butt.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, I know, I know, I know. I was just thinking about when they were there thelast time, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry. OK, OK, look, woah, I promise, I'm good, I'mnot gonna laugh anymore. OK put your hands back there.",
        "response":"No see now, now I can't because uh, I'm feeling too self conscious.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, my hands were no where near your butt.",
        "response":"I know, I know, I know, I know. I was just thinking about when they were there thelast time, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry. OK, OK, look, woah, I promise, I'm good, I'mnot gonna laugh anymore. OK put your hands back there.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, my hands were no where near your butt.",
        "response":"I know, I know, I know, I know. I was just thinking about when they were there thelast time, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry. OK, OK, look, woah, I promise, I'm good, I'mnot gonna laugh anymore. OK put your hands back there.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No see now, now I can't because uh, I'm feeling too self conscious.",
        "response":"</p><p>RACHEL: Just one cheek.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK. [start kissing again and Rachel starts lauging again]",
        "response":"OK, my hands were no where near your butt.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nuh, uh, the moment's gone.",
        "response":"Alright, just put your hands out and I'll back up into them.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, just put your hands out and I'll back up into them.",
        "response":"That's romantic.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, just put your hands out and I'll back up into them.",
        "response":"That's romantic.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"</p><p>RACHEL: Just one cheek.",
        "response":"Nuh, uh, the moment's gone.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's romantic.",
        "response":"C'mon touch it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's romantic.",
        "response":"C'mon touch it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Oh, come on squeeze it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Oh, come on squeeze it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, come on squeeze it.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, come on squeeze it.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon touch it.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon touch it.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Rub it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So how'd it go?",
        "response":"Oh. Listen, have you ever been uh, you know, foolin' around with a girl and uh, shestarted laughin'?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So how'd it go?",
        "response":"Oh. Listen, have you ever been uh, you know, foolin' around with a girl and uh, shestarted laughin'?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"CHANDLER and JOEY: Hey.",
        "response":"What're you doin' here? Aren't you supposed to be out with Rachel?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That was 14 hours ago.",
        "response":"So how'd it go?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"CHANDLER and JOEY: Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Oh, come on, would you just grab my ass.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Rub it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rub it.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rub it.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: Yeah, that's my job. Alright, look up. . . look down, now open your eyes, nowlook down. That's right, look into the light. Now look at me. . . OK. Your eyes look good.Those are good eyes.",
        "response":"Good, they feel good, in my head.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, you, ya know there's no need to make it u. . . how?",
        "response":"Well, I was thinking maybe a um, a romantic dinner with um, candles and wine andthen uh, maybe going back to my place for um, dessert.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, you, ya know there's no need to make it u. . . how?",
        "response":"Well, I was thinking maybe a um, a romantic dinner with um, candles and wine andthen uh, maybe going back to my place for um, dessert.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh. Listen, have you ever been uh, you know, foolin' around with a girl and uh, shestarted laughin'?",
        "response":"Yeah, but uh, it was 1982 and my flock of seagulls haircut was tickling herchin.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really.",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: Yeah, that's my job. Alright, look up. . . look down, now open your eyes, nowlook down. That's right, look into the light. Now look at me. . . OK. Your eyes look good.Those are good eyes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I was thinking maybe a um, a romantic dinner with um, candles and wine andthen uh, maybe going back to my place for um, dessert.",
        "response":"Humm, that sounds, I don't, perfect.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, listen, I'm sorry about last night and I really want to make it up to you.",
        "response":"No, you, ya know there's no need to make it u. . . how?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Good, they feel good, in my head.",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: So, it's great to see ya.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: So, it's great to see ya.",
        "response":"You too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thanks. So, I guess I better be going.",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: Oh, OK, yeah. I'll see ya later.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We have got to get you lazy boys out of these chairs.",
        "response":"CHANDLER and JOEY: Hey, woah, hey, woah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: Drops. Here, they're free.",
        "response":"Thanks. So, I guess I better be going.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: Oh, OK, yeah. I'll see ya later.",
        "response":"Thanks again.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: Drops. Here, they're free.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: You too.",
        "response":"OK, um. Goodbye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, um. Goodbye.",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: Drops!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You too.",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: You too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: Drops!",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"CHANDLER and JOEY: Hey, woah, hey, woah.",
        "response":"You know you should go outside and be with the three-dimensional people.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know you should go outside and be with the three-dimensional people.",
        "response":"No, inside good, outside bad.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well we just wanted to stop by and uh, say goodnight.",
        "response":"CHANDLER, JOEY, and PHOEBE: Goodnight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"CHANDLER, JOEY, and PHOEBE: Hey.",
        "response":"Well we just wanted to stop by and uh, say goodnight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, why're you all dressed up?",
        "response":"You're not the only one who has a date tonight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"CHANDLER, JOEY, and PHOEBE: Goodnight.",
        "response":"Look at that, they won't even turn their heads.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're not the only one who has a date tonight.",
        "response":"What? You have a date? Who with?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, inside good, outside bad.",
        "response":"You guys are so pathetic, I, oh, OH, XANADU! OH.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"CHANDLER, JOEY, and PHOEBE: Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Come on, tell me.",
        "response":"Alright, but I'm very excited about this OK, so you gotta promise you won't getall big-brothery and judgmental.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Come on, tell me.",
        "response":"Alright, but I'm very excited about this OK, so you gotta promise you won't getall big-brothery and judgmental.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? You have a date? Who with?",
        "response":"No one.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon, what's his name?",
        "response":"Nothing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon, what's his name?",
        "response":"Nothing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No one.",
        "response":"C'mon, what's his name?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No one.",
        "response":"C'mon, what's his name?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nothing.",
        "response":"Come on, tell me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nothing.",
        "response":"Come on, tell me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Who's Richard Burke? Doc, Doctor Burke? You have a date with Doctor Burke? Why, why,why should that bother me? I, I love that man, he's like a uh, brother to dad.",
        "response":"Well for your information he happens to be one of the brightest, mostsophisticated, sexiest men I've ever been with.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Who's Richard Burke? Doc, Doctor Burke? You have a date with Doctor Burke? Why, why,why should that bother me? I, I love that man, he's like a uh, brother to dad.",
        "response":"Well for your information he happens to be one of the brightest, mostsophisticated, sexiest men I've ever been with.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's Richard Burke.",
        "response":"Who's Richard Burke? Doc, Doctor Burke? You have a date with Doctor Burke? Why, why,why should that bother me? I, I love that man, he's like a uh, brother to dad.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's Richard Burke.",
        "response":"Who's Richard Burke? Doc, Doctor Burke? You have a date with Doctor Burke? Why, why,why should that bother me? I, I love that man, he's like a uh, brother to dad.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, but I'm very excited about this OK, so you gotta promise you won't getall big-brothery and judgmental.",
        "response":"Oh, I promise, what.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, but I'm very excited about this OK, so you gotta promise you won't getall big-brothery and judgmental.",
        "response":"Oh, I promise, what.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well for your information he happens to be one of the brightest, mostsophisticated, sexiest men I've ever been with.",
        "response":"Doctor Burke is sexy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I promise, what.",
        "response":"It's Richard Burke.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I promise, what.",
        "response":"It's Richard Burke.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh look, I can't believe this. Look, homo-habilus hasn't even learned how to usetools yet and they've got him here wi, with clay pots. Why don't, why don't they just givehim a microwave? I'm sorry, I'm sorry this is taking so long, ya know, I, I, it's justit's longer than I expected, we will have dinner.",
        "response":"It's OK, it's fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"When I was um, 7, I crashed my bike right out in front of his house and to stop mefrom crying he kissed me right here. [points to the tip of her nose]",
        "response":"Oh you are so lucky.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"When?",
        "response":"When I was um, 7, I crashed my bike right out in front of his house and to stop mefrom crying he kissed me right here. [points to the tip of her nose]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"RACHEL and PHOEBE: Oh God, absolutely.",
        "response":"[his beeper goes off] It's the museum again, can I, oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Doctor Burke is sexy?",
        "response":"RACHEL and PHOEBE: Oh God, absolutely.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ya know, Dr. Burke kissed me once.",
        "response":"When?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow, is that Michelle?",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: Yep.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh you are so lucky.",
        "response":"I know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's OK, it's fine.",
        "response":"KARL!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I thought she just had one.",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: No no. Henry's almost two and he's talking and everyting. Here. You know, theother day he told me he liked me better than his other grandpa. Now in all fairness hisother grandpa's a drunk but still. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: No no. Henry's almost two and he's talking and everyting. Here. You know, theother day he told me he liked me better than his other grandpa. Now in all fairness hisother grandpa's a drunk but still. . .",
        "response":"Oh, you're a grandpa.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know, maybe. I mean I'm dating a man who's pool I once peed in.",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: I didn't need to know that. I guess 21 years is a lot. I mean, hell, I'm awhole person who can drink older than you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I've not seen her since high school graduation. Oh my God, that night she got sodru. . . motional.",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: Ya know, she's having another baby.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: I didn't need to know that. I guess 21 years is a lot. I mean, hell, I'm awhole person who can drink older than you.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: Yep.",
        "response":"I've not seen her since high school graduation. Oh my God, that night she got sodru. . . motional.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: Yeah. Are we nuts here?",
        "response":"I don't know, maybe. I mean I'm dating a man who's pool I once peed in.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: Ya know, she's having another baby.",
        "response":"I thought she just had one.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, you're a grandpa.",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: Yeah. Are we nuts here?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: Yeah, it sure does. [they hug and it turns into a passionate kiss]",
        "response":"Well, we don't really have to decide anything right now, do we?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow, this really sucks.",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: Yeah, it sure does. [they hug and it turns into a passionate kiss]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So maybe we should just. . .",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: Yeah, yeah, maybe.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: Yeah, yeah, maybe.",
        "response":"Wow, this really sucks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DR. BURKE: So.",
        "response":"So maybe we should just. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"DR. BURKE: So.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh.",
        "response":"I'm done.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh.",
        "response":"I'm done.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rach.",
        "response":"Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wha, OK, I'm sorry, let's uh, why don't we find someplace else.",
        "response":"No, you know what, it's late, everything's gonna be closed. Why don't we just doit another night?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wha, OK, I'm sorry, let's uh, why don't we find someplace else.",
        "response":"No, you know what, it's late, everything's gonna be closed. Why don't we just doit another night?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah well, you know what, so is uh, Sorentino's.",
        "response":"Wha, OK, I'm sorry, let's uh, why don't we find someplace else.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah well, you know what, so is uh, Sorentino's.",
        "response":"Wha, OK, I'm sorry, let's uh, why don't we find someplace else.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, you know what, it's late, everything's gonna be closed. Why don't we just doit another night?",
        "response":"No, no, we won't.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, you know what, it's late, everything's gonna be closed. Why don't we just doit another night?",
        "response":"No, no, we won't.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm done.",
        "response":"Yeah well, you know what, so is uh, Sorentino's.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm done.",
        "response":"Yeah well, you know what, so is uh, Sorentino's.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, we won't.",
        "response":"We won't?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, that's dead right?",
        "response":"[Scene: The museum planetarium. Ross and Rachel enter on stage.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Scene: The museum planetarium. Ross and Rachel enter on stage.]",
        "response":"What is this? What are we doing?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What is this? What are we doing?",
        "response":"Shh. Do you want cran-apple or cran-grape?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[grabs a fur pelt] C'mon.",
        "response":"OK, that's dead right?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Shh. Do you want cran-apple or cran-grape?",
        "response":"Grape.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Shh. Do you want cran-apple or cran-grape?",
        "response":"Grape.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We won't?",
        "response":"[grabs a fur pelt] C'mon.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We won't?",
        "response":"[grabs a fur pelt] C'mon.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, we won't.",
        "response":"We won't?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"</p><p align=\"left\">ROSS: I've no idea, could be. Listen, I'm sorry I had to work tonight.",
        "response":"Oh it's OK. You were worth the wait, and I don't just mean tonight. [they kiss]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ah, so what are we looking at?",
        "response":"Well uh, you see that, that little cluster of stars next to the big one? That isUrsa Major.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ah, so what are we looking at?",
        "response":"Well uh, you see that, that little cluster of stars next to the big one? That isUrsa Major.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"</p><p align=\"left\">ROSS: I've no idea, could be. Listen, I'm sorry I had to work tonight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well uh, you see that, that little cluster of stars next to the big one? That isUrsa Major.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[spreads the pelt on the floor] OK, now, sit. OK. [he starts the music system]",
        "response":"Oh, God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Grape.",
        "response":"[spreads the pelt on the floor] OK, now, sit. OK. [he starts the music system]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Grape.",
        "response":"[spreads the pelt on the floor] OK, now, sit. OK. [he starts the music system]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sorry.",
        "response":"Ah, so what are we looking at?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[They kiss and start undressing. As Rachel tries to pull off Ross's tie she catches it inhis mouth. Then they roll across the fur rug.]",
        "response":"Ah, oh God. Oh, honey, oh that's OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This time it's not so funny.",
        "response":"[They kiss and start undressing. As Rachel tries to pull off Ross's tie she catches it inhis mouth. Then they roll across the fur rug.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh it's OK. You were worth the wait, and I don't just mean tonight. [they kiss]",
        "response":"You're not laughing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi you. I can't believe I'm waking up next to you.",
        "response":"I know it is pretty unbelievaaaaah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi you. I can't believe I'm waking up next to you.",
        "response":"I know it is pretty unbelievaaaaah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ah, oh God. Oh, honey, oh that's OK.",
        "response":"What. Oh no, you just rolled over the juice box.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What. Oh no, you just rolled over the juice box.",
        "response":"Oh, thank God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Hi you. I can't believe I'm waking up next to you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're not laughing.",
        "response":"This time it's not so funny.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. [feels the floor] Oh it's not warm yet, we still have time.",
        "response":"Cool. </font></p><p align=\"center\"><strong><font size=\"3\">END</font></strong></p><hr><p align=\"center\"><!--webbot bot=\"ImageMap\" startspanrectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/216jmo.htm\"rectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2.htm\"rectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/214towpv.htm\"src=\"contrl08.gif\" width=\"194\" height=\"60\"alt=\"contrl08.gif \" --><MAP NAME=\"FrontPageMap0\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"139, 3, 197, 84\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/216jmo.htm\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"70, 2, 131, 84\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2.htm\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"0, 0, 59, 80\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/214towpv.htm\"></MAP><img src=\"contrl08.gif\" width=\"194\" height=\"60\" alt=\"contrl08.gif \" usemap=\"#FrontPageMap0\"><!--webbot bot=\"ImageMap\" i-checksum=\"4039\" endspan--></p><hr><center><img src=\"/cgi-bin/counter/215\"></center><hr></body></html>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's what's weird? Joey, the man's been captain of a <b>cereal</b> for thelast 40 years.",
        "response":"[Joey finishes his cereal, licks his spoon, and puts it back in the silverware drawer.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Joey finishes his cereal, licks his spoon, and puts it back in the silverware drawer.]",
        "response":"Waaa-aaah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Is that the fire alarm?",
        "response":"Yeah. [feels the floor] Oh it's not warm yet, we still have time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"We're not alone. [A church youth group is outside the display watching them]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know it is pretty unbelievaaaaah.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know it is pretty unbelievaaaaah.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"The spoon. You licked and-and you put. You licked and you put.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Waaa-aaah.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well don't you see how gross that is? I mean that's like you using mytoothbrush. [Joey gets a sheepish look] You used my toothbrush?",
        "response":"Well, that was only 'cause I used the red one to unclog the drain.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well don't you see how gross that is? I mean that's like you using mytoothbrush. [Joey gets a sheepish look] You used my toothbrush?",
        "response":"Well, that was only 'cause I used the red one to unclog the drain.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, so.",
        "response":"Well don't you see how gross that is? I mean that's like you using mytoothbrush. [Joey gets a sheepish look] You used my toothbrush?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, so.",
        "response":"Well don't you see how gross that is? I mean that's like you using mytoothbrush. [Joey gets a sheepish look] You used my toothbrush?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, that was only 'cause I used the red one to unclog the drain.",
        "response":"Mine is the red one! Oh God. Can open, worms everywhere.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, that was only 'cause I used the red one to unclog the drain.",
        "response":"Mine is the red one! Oh God. Can open, worms everywhere.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The spoon. You licked and-and you put. You licked and you put.",
        "response":"Yeah, so.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The spoon. You licked and-and you put. You licked and you put.",
        "response":"Yeah, so.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"The spoon. You licked and-and you put. You licked and you put.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Because soap is soap. It's self-cleaning.",
        "response":"Alright, well next time you take a shower, think about the last thing I wash and thefirst thing you wash.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh, look at you fancy lads. What's the occasion?",
        "response":"Well, you know that guy that's on my show that's in a coma? He's havin' a brunch.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh, look at you fancy lads. What's the occasion?",
        "response":"Well, you know that guy that's on my show that's in a coma? He's havin' a brunch.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mine is the red one! Oh God. Can open, worms everywhere.",
        "response":"Hey, why can't we use the same toothbrush, but we can use the same soap?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mine is the red one! Oh God. Can open, worms everywhere.",
        "response":"Hey, why can't we use the same toothbrush, but we can use the same soap?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, why can't we use the same toothbrush, but we can use the same soap?",
        "response":"Because soap is soap. It's self-cleaning.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, why can't we use the same toothbrush, but we can use the same soap?",
        "response":"Because soap is soap. It's self-cleaning.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you know that guy that's on my show that's in a coma? He's havin' a brunch.",
        "response":"Ahh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Ooh, look at you fancy lads. What's the occasion?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi. Well hey, you don't - you don't think they're kind of cool?",
        "response":"No, sorry I don't. Tell me why would anyone pay someone to scar their body for life?What if it doesn't come out right Phoebe? Then it's like, I don't know, havin' a bad haircut all the time. Why's everyone staring at me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ross, come sign this birthday card for dad. Rich is gonna be here any minute.",
        "response":"Oooh, Rich is goin' to the party too, huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"A tattoo? Why, why would you want to do that? [to Rachel] Hi.",
        "response":"Hi. Well hey, you don't - you don't think they're kind of cool?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, a chip. A tattoo, I'm getting a tattoo.",
        "response":"A tattoo? Why, why would you want to do that? [to Rachel] Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I think on my shoulder. [Ross enters]",
        "response":"What? What's on your shoulder?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[enters from her room] OK, ready when you are.",
        "response":"Okey-doke.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? What's on your shoulder?",
        "response":"Um, a chip. A tattoo, I'm getting a tattoo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? What's on your shoulder?",
        "response":"Um, a chip. A tattoo, I'm getting a tattoo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahh.",
        "response":"[enters from her room] OK, ready when you are.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, wait, wait, wait, wait. You know what? Ross, let's - let's switch places. Youget in the middle. No un-, ya know, unless this looks like we're trying to cover somethingup.",
        "response":"Monica, Monica, you could come in straddling him, they still wouldn't believe it.[opens door] We're here.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know, I don't think mom and dad would mind. Remember when you were 9 andRichard was 30, how dad used to say, 'God I hope they get together.'",
        "response":"<b>[Scene: The Gellers' house. Monica, Ross, and Richard are arriving to Mr. Gellersbirthday party.]</b>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, shall we?",
        "response":"OK, wait, wait, wait, wait. You know what? Ross, let's - let's switch places. Youget in the middle. No un-, ya know, unless this looks like we're trying to cover somethingup.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, is today the day you're gonna tell them about you two?",
        "response":"Yeah. It's my dad's birthday, I decided to give him a stroke.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I think you should tell them.",
        "response":"No, I don't even know how serious he is about me. Until I do, I'm not telling themanything.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<b>[Scene: The Gellers' house. Monica, Ross, and Richard are arriving to Mr. Gellersbirthday party.]</b>",
        "response":"Alright, shall we?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, he's my parents' best friend, he has to be there.",
        "response":"Oh, is today the day you're gonna tell them about you two?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. It's my dad's birthday, I decided to give him a stroke.",
        "response":"No, I think you should tell them.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oooh, Rich is goin' to the party too, huh?",
        "response":"Well, he's my parents' best friend, he has to be there.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GELLER: No, Richard Burke gave them a ride.",
        "response":"Oh. Speaking of whom, I hear he's got some 20-year-old twinkie in the city.[Monica sprays whipped cream all over the place]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ah, I was just in the bathroom, and there's mirrors on both sides of you. So whenyou're in there it's like you're peein' with the Rockettes.",
        "response":"Wow, there's my fantasy come true. No, seriously.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, this is a great apartment.",
        "response":"Ah, I was just in the bathroom, and there's mirrors on both sides of you. So whenyou're in there it's like you're peein' with the Rockettes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, this is a great apartment.",
        "response":"Ah, I was just in the bathroom, and there's mirrors on both sides of you. So whenyou're in there it's like you're peein' with the Rockettes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Finger cramp. Oh God, sorry. Here, let me get that mom.",
        "response":"MRS. GELLER: Sooo, Richard's shopping in the junior section.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey! We were just sayin', great apartment man.",
        "response":"JOEY'S CO-STAR: Thanks. You want it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you kids take the train in?",
        "response":"MRS. GELLER: No, Richard Burke gave them a ride.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GELLER: Sooo, Richard's shopping in the junior section.",
        "response":"Are we still on that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Can you believe this place?",
        "response":"I know, this is a great apartment.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I like this lily. It's more open, ya know, and that's like my mom. She had a moreopen, giving spirit. Ooh, Foghorn Leghorn, ooh.",
        "response":"TATTOO ARTIST: Alright, blonde girl, you're in room two, not so blonde girl, you're withme.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. GELLER: Look, I know what you're going through. When I turned 50 I got the Porsche.You... you got your own little speedster.",
        "response":"Guys. Seriously, it is <b>not</b> like that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Jack, would you let it go?",
        "response":"MR. GELLER: Look, I know what you're going through. When I turned 50 I got the Porsche.You... you got your own little speedster.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well I. . .",
        "response":"I like this lily. It's more open, ya know, and that's like my mom. She had a moreopen, giving spirit. Ooh, Foghorn Leghorn, ooh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"JOEY'S CO-STAR: Yeah, I'm movin' to a bigger place. You should definitely take this one.",
        "response":"Yeah, can you see me in a place like this?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh?",
        "response":"JOEY'S CO-STAR: Yeah, I'm movin' to a bigger place. You should definitely take this one.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"TATTOO ARTIST: Alright, blonde girl, you're in room two, not so blonde girl, you're withme.",
        "response":"Here we go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK Rach, which, which lily? This lily or that lily?",
        "response":"Well I. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"JOEY'S CO-STAR: Thanks. You want it?",
        "response":"Huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? Is it - is this 'cause of what Ross said?",
        "response":"No. Well, yeah, maybe.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? Is it - is this 'cause of what Ross said?",
        "response":"No. Well, yeah, maybe.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh.",
        "response":"What? Is it - is this 'cause of what Ross said?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh.",
        "response":"What? Is it - is this 'cause of what Ross said?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Here we go.",
        "response":"[reluctantly] Uh-huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[reluctantly] Uh-huh.",
        "response":"You're not going?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[reluctantly] Uh-huh.",
        "response":"You're not going?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're not going?",
        "response":"Uh-huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're not going?",
        "response":"Uh-huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Just, you know, long time ago. Well, when men used to tell women what to do - alot. And then there was suffrage, which is a good thing but is sounds horrible. Do youwant to get this tattoo?",
        "response":"Yes I do, it's just that Ross is. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Just, you know, long time ago. Well, when men used to tell women what to do - alot. And then there was suffrage, which is a good thing but is sounds horrible. Do youwant to get this tattoo?",
        "response":"Yes I do, it's just that Ross is. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's 1922?",
        "response":"Just, you know, long time ago. Well, when men used to tell women what to do - alot. And then there was suffrage, which is a good thing but is sounds horrible. Do youwant to get this tattoo?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's 1922?",
        "response":"Just, you know, long time ago. Well, when men used to tell women what to do - alot. And then there was suffrage, which is a good thing but is sounds horrible. Do youwant to get this tattoo?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. Well, yeah, maybe.",
        "response":"I don't believe this. Is this how this relationship's gonna work? Ross equalsboss. I mean, c'mon what is this, 1922?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. Well, yeah, maybe.",
        "response":"I don't believe this. Is this how this relationship's gonna work? Ross equalsboss. I mean, c'mon what is this, 1922?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't believe this. Is this how this relationship's gonna work? Ross equalsboss. I mean, c'mon what is this, 1922?",
        "response":"What's 1922?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't believe this. Is this how this relationship's gonna work? Ross equalsboss. I mean, c'mon what is this, 1922?",
        "response":"What's 1922?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes I do, it's just that Ross is. . .",
        "response":"OK, hey, HEY. Is your boyfriend the boss of you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You?",
        "response":"No. You are the boss of you. Now you march your heinie in there and get that hearttattooed on your hip. <b>GO</b>!!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes I do, it's just that Ross is. . .",
        "response":"OK, hey, HEY. Is your boyfriend the boss of you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How ya doin'?",
        "response":"I'm a twinkie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, who is the boss of you?!!",
        "response":"You?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, who is the boss of you?!!",
        "response":"You?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, hey, HEY. Is your boyfriend the boss of you?",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, hey, HEY. Is your boyfriend the boss of you?",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"OK, who is the boss of you?!!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"OK, who is the boss of you?!!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I know. I hate it too. Look, maybe we should just tell them.",
        "response":"Maybe we should just tell your parents first.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I know. I hate it too. Look, maybe we should just tell them.",
        "response":"Maybe we should just tell your parents first.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, this is so hard.",
        "response":"Yeah, I know. I hate it too. Look, maybe we should just tell them.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, this is so hard.",
        "response":"Yeah, I know. I hate it too. Look, maybe we should just tell them.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe we should just tell your parents first.",
        "response":"My parents are dead.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really? I'm a hero.",
        "response":"Oh, this is so hard.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really? I'm a hero.",
        "response":"Oh, this is so hard.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm a twinkie.",
        "response":"Really? I'm a hero.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm a twinkie.",
        "response":"Really? I'm a hero.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Can we drop this? I am not interested in the guy's apartment.",
        "response":"Oh please, I saw the way you were checking out his mouldings. You want it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"God, you are so lucky. I mean, I mean. . . you know what I mean.",
        "response":"I know, I know. Just hang in there, OK. OK, I'll go out first, alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"God, you are so lucky. I mean, I mean. . . you know what I mean.",
        "response":"I know, I know. Just hang in there, OK. OK, I'll go out first, alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright.",
        "response":"[walks out of the bathroom and runs into Mrs. Geller who is going to thebathroom] Judy, <b>going to the bathroom</b>, good for you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, I know. Just hang in there, OK. OK, I'll go out first, alright.",
        "response":"Alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, I know. Just hang in there, OK. OK, I'll go out first, alright.",
        "response":"Alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"My parents are dead.",
        "response":"God, you are so lucky. I mean, I mean. . . you know what I mean.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"My parents are dead.",
        "response":"God, you are so lucky. I mean, I mean. . . you know what I mean.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe we should just tell your parents first.",
        "response":"My parents are dead.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh please, I saw the way you were checking out his mouldings. You want it.",
        "response":"Why would I want another apartment, huh? I've already got an apartment that I love.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh please, I saw the way you were checking out his mouldings. You want it.",
        "response":"Why would I want another apartment, huh? I've already got an apartment that I love.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I'm sorry. I'm 28 years old, I've never lived alone, and I'm finally at a placewhere I've got enough money that I don't need a roommate anymore.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why would I want another apartment, huh? I've already got an apartment that I love.",
        "response":"Well it wouldn't kill you to say it once in a while.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why would I want another apartment, huh? I've already got an apartment that I love.",
        "response":"Well it wouldn't kill you to say it once in a while.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well it wouldn't kill you to say it once in a while.",
        "response":"Alright, you want the truth? I'm thinkin' about it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well it wouldn't kill you to say it once in a while.",
        "response":"Alright, you want the truth? I'm thinkin' about it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, you want the truth? I'm thinkin' about it.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, you want the truth? I'm thinkin' about it.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry. I'm 28 years old, I've never lived alone, and I'm finally at a placewhere I've got enough money that I don't need a roommate anymore.",
        "response":"Woah, woah, woah. I don't need a roommate either, OK? I can afford to live hereby myself. Ya know, I may have to bring in somebody once a week to lick the silverware.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry. I'm 28 years old, I've never lived alone, and I'm finally at a placewhere I've got enough money that I don't need a roommate anymore.",
        "response":"Woah, woah, woah. I don't need a roommate either, OK? I can afford to live hereby myself. Ya know, I may have to bring in somebody once a week to lick the silverware.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Woah, woah, woah. I don't need a roommate either, OK? I can afford to live hereby myself. Ya know, I may have to bring in somebody once a week to lick the silverware.",
        "response":"What're you gettin' so bent out of shape for, huh? It's not like we agreed to livetogether forever. We're not Bert and Ernie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Woah, woah, woah. I don't need a roommate either, OK? I can afford to live hereby myself. Ya know, I may have to bring in somebody once a week to lick the silverware.",
        "response":"What're you gettin' so bent out of shape for, huh? It's not like we agreed to livetogether forever. We're not Bert and Ernie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What're you gettin' so bent out of shape for, huh? It's not like we agreed to livetogether forever. We're not Bert and Ernie.",
        "response":"Look, you know what? If this is the way you feel, then maybe you should take it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What're you gettin' so bent out of shape for, huh? It's not like we agreed to livetogether forever. We're not Bert and Ernie.",
        "response":"Look, you know what? If this is the way you feel, then maybe you should take it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I'm sorry. I'm 28 years old, I've never lived alone, and I'm finally at a placewhere I've got enough money that I don't need a roommate anymore.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, you know what? If this is the way you feel, then maybe you should take it.",
        "response":"Well that's how I feel.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, you know what? If this is the way you feel, then maybe you should take it.",
        "response":"Well that's how I feel.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Fine with me.",
        "response":"Great. Then you'll be able to spend more quality time with your real friends, thespoons.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mon, Mon, are you OK?",
        "response":"You remember that video I found of mom and dad?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well that's how I feel.",
        "response":"Well then maybe you should take it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well that's how I feel.",
        "response":"Well then maybe you should take it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You remember that video I found of mom and dad?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well then maybe you should take it.",
        "response":"Well then maybe I will.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well then maybe you should take it.",
        "response":"Well then maybe I will.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well then maybe I will.",
        "response":"Fine with me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well then maybe I will.",
        "response":"Fine with me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uhh, not that I know of.",
        "response":"MRS. GELLER: Well, I was thinking, why doesn't he give Monica a call?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nothing, I just heard something nice about you.",
        "response":"Humm, really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Nothing, I just heard something nice about you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Nothing, I just heard something nice about you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You remember that video I found of mom and dad?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Well, I just caught the live show.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Well, I just caught the live show.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I just caught the live show.",
        "response":"Eww.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey there.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GELLER: She never tells us anything. Ross, did you know Monica's seeing someone?",
        "response":"Mom, there are so many people in my life. Some of them are seeing people and some ofthem aren't. Is that crystal?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, a doctor of meat. Of course he's a real doctor. And he's handsome, and he'ssweet, and know you'd like him. [she puts her arm around Richard]",
        "response":"MRS. GELLER: Well that's wonderful. . . I",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GELLER: A real doctor?",
        "response":"No, a doctor of meat. Of course he's a real doctor. And he's handsome, and he'ssweet, and know you'd like him. [she puts her arm around Richard]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Al-alright, l-look you guys, this is the best relationship I've been in. . .",
        "response":"MRS. GELLER: Oh please, a relationship.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GELLER: Oh please, a relationship.",
        "response":"Yes, a relationship. For your information I am crazy about this man.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohh.",
        "response":"MRS. GELLER: She never tells us anything. Ross, did you know Monica's seeing someone?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GELLER: Well, I was thinking, why doesn't he give Monica a call?",
        "response":"That - that's an idea.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GELLER: Well that's wonderful. . . I",
        "response":"Mom, it's OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, uh, he's a doctor.",
        "response":"MRS. GELLER: A real doctor?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. GELLER: Am I supposed to stand here and listen to this on my birthday?",
        "response":"Dad, dad this is a good thing for me. Ya know, and you even said yourself, you'venever seen Richard happier.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Dad, dad this is a good thing for me. Ya know, and you even said yourself, you'venever seen Richard happier.",
        "response":"MR. GELLER: When did I say that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh that looks so good, oh I love it.",
        "response":"I know, so do I. Oh Phoebe, I'm so glad you made me do this. OK, lemme se yours.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, so do I. Oh Phoebe, I'm so glad you made me do this. OK, lemme se yours.",
        "response":"Ahh. OK, let's see yours again.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, so do I. Oh Phoebe, I'm so glad you made me do this. OK, lemme se yours.",
        "response":"Ahh. OK, let's see yours again.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. GELLER: When did I say that?",
        "response":"Upstairs in the bathroom right before you felt up mom.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes, a relationship. For your information I am crazy about this man.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes.",
        "response":"MR. GELLER: Am I supposed to stand here and listen to this on my birthday?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Yes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebe we just saw mine, let me see yours.",
        "response":"Oh OK. [pulls over her shirt and shows a bare shoulder] Oh no, oh it's gone,that's so weird, I don't know how-where it went.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebe we just saw mine, let me see yours.",
        "response":"Oh OK. [pulls over her shirt and shows a bare shoulder] Oh no, oh it's gone,that's so weird, I don't know how-where it went.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh OK. [pulls over her shirt and shows a bare shoulder] Oh no, oh it's gone,that's so weird, I don't know how-where it went.",
        "response":"You didn't get it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh OK. [pulls over her shirt and shows a bare shoulder] Oh no, oh it's gone,that's so weird, I don't know how-where it went.",
        "response":"You didn't get it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahh. OK, let's see yours again.",
        "response":"Phoebe we just saw mine, let me see yours.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahh. OK, let's see yours again.",
        "response":"Phoebe we just saw mine, let me see yours.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Why didn't you get it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You didn't get it?",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You didn't get it?",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, I know, and I was gonna get it but then he came in with this needle anduh, di-, did you know they do this with needles?",
        "response":"Really? You don't say, because mine was licked on by kittens.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebe, how would you do this to me? This was all your idea.",
        "response":"I know, I know, and I was gonna get it but then he came in with this needle anduh, di-, did you know they do this with needles?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebe, how would you do this to me? This was all your idea.",
        "response":"I know, I know, and I was gonna get it but then he came in with this needle anduh, di-, did you know they do this with needles?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry, I'm sorry.",
        "response":"Phoebe, how would you do this to me? This was all your idea.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry, I'm sorry.",
        "response":"Phoebe, how would you do this to me? This was all your idea.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why didn't you get it?",
        "response":"I'm sorry, I'm sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why didn't you get it?",
        "response":"I'm sorry, I'm sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Why didn't you get it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey listen, I'm sorry about what happened. . .",
        "response":"Yeah me too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey listen, I'm sorry about what happened. . .",
        "response":"Yeah me too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. So do we need to hug here or. . .",
        "response":"No, we're alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know. Yeah.",
        "response":"Yeah. So do we need to hug here or. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know. Yeah.",
        "response":"Yeah. So do we need to hug here or. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey listen, I'm sorry about what happened. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey listen, I'm sorry about what happened. . .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah me too.",
        "response":"I know. Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah me too.",
        "response":"I know. Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Lick away my man.",
        "response":"These'll go great in my new place. You know, 'till I get real ones.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Lick away my man.",
        "response":"These'll go great in my new place. You know, 'till I get real ones.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So I got ya something. [tosses Joey a bag of plastic spoons]",
        "response":"Plastic spoons. Great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So I got ya something. [tosses Joey a bag of plastic spoons]",
        "response":"Plastic spoons. Great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, we're alright.",
        "response":"So I got ya something. [tosses Joey a bag of plastic spoons]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, we're alright.",
        "response":"So I got ya something. [tosses Joey a bag of plastic spoons]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. So do we need to hug here or. . .",
        "response":"No, we're alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Plastic spoons. Great.",
        "response":"Lick away my man.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Plastic spoons. Great.",
        "response":"Lick away my man.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm movin' out like we talked about.",
        "response":"Well I didn't think that was serious. [grabs the spoons back] Ya know I thoughtthat was just a fight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I can't use these forever. I mean, let's face it, they're no friend to theenvironment.",
        "response":"No-no, I mean what, what's this about your new place?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I can't use these forever. I mean, let's face it, they're no friend to theenvironment.",
        "response":"No-no, I mean what, what's this about your new place?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Well, I can't use these forever. I mean, let's face it, they're no friend to theenvironment.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Well, I can't use these forever. I mean, let's face it, they're no friend to theenvironment.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No-no, I mean what, what's this about your new place?",
        "response":"I'm movin' out like we talked about.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No-no, I mean what, what's this about your new place?",
        "response":"I'm movin' out like we talked about.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"These'll go great in my new place. You know, 'till I get real ones.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"These'll go great in my new place. You know, 'till I get real ones.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well I didn't think that was serious. [grabs the spoons back] Ya know I thoughtthat was just a fight.",
        "response":"Well, it was a fight. . . based on serious stuff, remember. About how I never livedalone or anything. I just think it would be good for me, ya know, help me to grow or. . .whatever.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well I didn't think that was serious. [grabs the spoons back] Ya know I thoughtthat was just a fight.",
        "response":"Well, it was a fight. . . based on serious stuff, remember. About how I never livedalone or anything. I just think it would be good for me, ya know, help me to grow or. . .whatever.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, are you cool with this. I mean, I don't want to leave you high and dry.",
        "response":"Hey, no, I've never been lower or wetter. I'll be fine. I'll just turn your, uh,bedroom into a game room or somethin', you know, put the foosball table in there.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, are you cool with this. I mean, I don't want to leave you high and dry.",
        "response":"Hey, no, I've never been lower or wetter. I'll be fine. I'll just turn your, uh,bedroom into a game room or somethin', you know, put the foosball table in there.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, it was a fight. . . based on serious stuff, remember. About how I never livedalone or anything. I just think it would be good for me, ya know, help me to grow or. . .whatever.",
        "response":"Well, there you go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, it was a fight. . . based on serious stuff, remember. About how I never livedalone or anything. I just think it would be good for me, ya know, help me to grow or. . .whatever.",
        "response":"Well, there you go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm movin' out like we talked about.",
        "response":"Well I didn't think that was serious. [grabs the spoons back] Ya know I thoughtthat was just a fight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, there you go.",
        "response":"Hey, are you cool with this. I mean, I don't want to leave you high and dry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, there you go.",
        "response":"Hey, are you cool with this. I mean, I don't want to leave you high and dry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, no, I've never been lower or wetter. I'll be fine. I'll just turn your, uh,bedroom into a game room or somethin', you know, put the foosball table in there.",
        "response":"Woah. Why do you get to keep the table?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, no, I've never been lower or wetter. I'll be fine. I'll just turn your, uh,bedroom into a game room or somethin', you know, put the foosball table in there.",
        "response":"Woah. Why do you get to keep the table?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright I'll tell you what, I'll play you for it.",
        "response":"Alright, you're on. I can take two minutes out of my day to kick your ass.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. And uh, I paid for the other half.",
        "response":"Alright I'll tell you what, I'll play you for it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. And uh, I paid for the other half.",
        "response":"Alright I'll tell you what, I'll play you for it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Woah. Why do you get to keep the table?",
        "response":"I did pay for half of it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Woah. Why do you get to keep the table?",
        "response":"I did pay for half of it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I did pay for half of it.",
        "response":"Yeah. And uh, I paid for the other half.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I did pay for half of it.",
        "response":"Yeah. And uh, I paid for the other half.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, you're on. I can take two minutes out of my day to kick your ass.",
        "response":"Your little men are gonna get scored on more times than your sister.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, you're on. I can take two minutes out of my day to kick your ass.",
        "response":"Your little men are gonna get scored on more times than your sister.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright I'll tell you what, I'll play you for it.",
        "response":"Alright, you're on. I can take two minutes out of my day to kick your ass.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Your little men are gonna get scored on more times than your sister.",
        "response":"Woah, woah, woah, woah. Which sister?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh. Well did you get it? Let me see.",
        "response":"Is Ross here?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh. Well did you get it? Let me see.",
        "response":"Is Ross here?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh.",
        "response":"Oh. Well did you get it? Let me see.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Is Ross here?",
        "response":"No he went out to get pizza.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Is Ross here?",
        "response":"No he went out to get pizza.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, hi. For your information this is exactly what I wanted. This is a tattoo ofthe earth as seen from a great distance. It's the way my mother sees me from heaven.",
        "response":"Oh, what a load of crap. That is a dot. Your mother is up in heaven going, 'Wherethe hell is my lily, you wuss?' OK, Phoebe, that is not a tattoo, this is a tattoo. [shebends over and bears her tattoo right when Ross returns]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That is not a tattoo, that is a nothing. I finally got her back in the chair,bairly touched her with a needle, she jumped up screaming, and that was it.",
        "response":"OK, hi. For your information this is exactly what I wanted. This is a tattoo ofthe earth as seen from a great distance. It's the way my mother sees me from heaven.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That is not a tattoo, that is a nothing. I finally got her back in the chair,bairly touched her with a needle, she jumped up screaming, and that was it.",
        "response":"OK, hi. For your information this is exactly what I wanted. This is a tattoo ofthe earth as seen from a great distance. It's the way my mother sees me from heaven.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, that's my tattoo.",
        "response":"That is not a tattoo, that is a nothing. I finally got her back in the chair,bairly touched her with a needle, she jumped up screaming, and that was it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, well then what is this? [shows her bare shoulder]",
        "response":"What're we looking at? That blue freckle?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No he went out to get pizza.",
        "response":"Oh really, OK. [shows Monica her tattoo]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No he went out to get pizza.",
        "response":"Oh really, OK. [shows Monica her tattoo]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What're we looking at? That blue freckle?",
        "response":"OK, that's my tattoo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh really, OK. [shows Monica her tattoo]",
        "response":"That's great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, what a load of crap. That is a dot. Your mother is up in heaven going, 'Wherethe hell is my lily, you wuss?' OK, Phoebe, that is not a tattoo, this is a tattoo. [shebends over and bears her tattoo right when Ross returns]",
        "response":"You got a tattoo?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well?",
        "response":"Well it's really. . . sexy. I wouldn't have thought it would be but. . . wow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well?",
        "response":"Well it's really. . . sexy. I wouldn't have thought it would be but. . . wow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You got a tattoo?",
        "response":"Maybe. But just a little one. Phoebe got the whole world.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You got a tattoo?",
        "response":"Maybe. But just a little one. Phoebe got the whole world.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe. But just a little one. Phoebe got the whole world.",
        "response":"Lemme see. [looks]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe. But just a little one. Phoebe got the whole world.",
        "response":"Lemme see. [looks]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Lemme see. [looks]",
        "response":"Well?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Lemme see. [looks]",
        "response":"Well?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well it's really. . . sexy. I wouldn't have thought it would be but. . . wow.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well it's really. . . sexy. I wouldn't have thought it would be but. . . wow.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Get out of the corner. Pass it, pass it.",
        "response":"Stop talkin' to your men. [Joey scores]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I guess.",
        "response":"Hey, save us some pizza. [they go off to Rachel's room]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Stop talkin' to your men. [Joey scores]",
        "response":"Yes! And the table is mine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, so uh, is it sore or can you do stuff?",
        "response":"I guess.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, so uh, is it sore or can you do stuff?",
        "response":"I guess.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Yeah, so uh, is it sore or can you do stuff?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Yeah, so uh, is it sore or can you do stuff?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Listen, uh, I don't know when I'm gonna see you again.",
        "response":"Well, I'm guessing uh, tonight at the coffee house.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, uhh, em, you want me to uh, give you a hand with the foosball table?",
        "response":"Naa, you keep it, you need the practice.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Stop talkin' to your men. [Joey scores]",
        "response":"Yes! And the table is mine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes! And the table is mine.",
        "response":"Congratulations. [Chandler leaves]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, I guess this is it.",
        "response":"Yeah, right, yeah, I guess so.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Naa, you keep it, you need the practice.",
        "response":"Thanks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Naa, you keep it, you need the practice.",
        "response":"Thanks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thanks.",
        "response":"So, I guess this is it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thanks.",
        "response":"So, I guess this is it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[looking at a water sculpture that looks like a window with rain running down it]Hey, excellent, excellent water-table thing.",
        "response":"Thanks, yeah. I love this but ya know what, it makes me wanna pee.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thanks, yeah. I love this but ya know what, it makes me wanna pee.",
        "response":"Yeah, well me too, yeah. I think that's the challenge.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thanks, yeah. I love this but ya know what, it makes me wanna pee.",
        "response":"Yeah, well me too, yeah. I think that's the challenge.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, well me too, yeah. I think that's the challenge.",
        "response":"Hey, how come, uhh, Chandler didn't come?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I'm guessing uh, tonight at the coffee house.",
        "response":"Right, yeah. OK. Um, take care.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I'm guessing uh, tonight at the coffee house.",
        "response":"Right, yeah. OK. Um, take care.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[looking at some kind of glass sculpture thing] Wow Joey, this is, uhh...",
        "response":"Art.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right, yeah. OK. Um, take care.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Art.",
        "response":"Art it is.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So why don't ya show us the rest of your casa?",
        "response":"Yeah. Uh, oh, OH, the best part, c'mon. [leads them to the bathroom, gesturestowards toilet, everyone stares, uncomprehending] Heh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. Uh, oh, OH, the best part, c'mon. [leads them to the bathroom, gesturestowards toilet, everyone stares, uncomprehending] Heh?",
        "response":"Hey, nice toilet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, how come, uhh, Chandler didn't come?",
        "response":"Well uh, it's cause he had a thing with, wi-, with the thing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right, I go-, I got it.",
        "response":"So why don't ya show us the rest of your casa?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well uh, it's cause he had a thing with, wi-, with the thing.",
        "response":"Right, I go-, I got it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's right, I have a phone <i>in here</i>.",
        "response":"Joey, promise me something.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wha-, you have a phone in here?",
        "response":"That's right, I have a phone <i>in here</i>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No no no, behind it.",
        "response":"Wha-, you have a phone in here?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, nice toilet.",
        "response":"No no no, behind it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK. I just met this producer of this like, teeny record company, who said that Ihave a very fresh, offbeat sound and she wants to do a demo of <i>Smelly Cat</i>.",
        "response":"[congradulating her and celebrating]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Now wait a minute, I claimed you in the name of France four years ago.",
        "response":"Anyway, OK, now promise you won't like, freak out and say how great this is untilI'm done, OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK.",
        "response":"OK. I just met this producer of this like, teeny record company, who said that Ihave a very fresh, offbeat sound and she wants to do a demo of <i>Smelly Cat</i>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK.",
        "response":"OK. I just met this producer of this like, teeny record company, who said that Ihave a very fresh, offbeat sound and she wants to do a demo of <i>Smelly Cat</i>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God. You are not gonna believe this. I havejust been discovered.",
        "response":"Now wait a minute, I claimed you in the name of France four years ago.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Anyway, OK, now promise you won't like, freak out and say how great this is untilI'm done, OK.",
        "response":"OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Never call me from that phone.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey, promise me something.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey, promise me something.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK. I just met this producer of this like, teeny record company, who said that Ihave a very fresh, offbeat sound and she wants to do a demo of <i>Smelly Cat</i>.",
        "response":"[congradulating her and celebrating]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm not done yet, OK. God. OK, if that goes well, they may even want to make analbum.",
        "response":"[everyone is quiet, unsure if she's done or not]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God. Ross, OK, if you care about me at all, you will get the pie out of theman's hood.",
        "response":"Get the what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[celebrating more]",
        "response":"I'm not done yet, OK. God. OK, if that goes well, they may even want to make analbum.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[congradulating her and celebrating]",
        "response":"I told you not to do that yet. And, she wants to do a video.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[congradulating her and celebrating]",
        "response":"I told you not to do that yet. And, she wants to do a video.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I told you not to do that yet. And, she wants to do a video.",
        "response":"[celebrating more]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I told you not to do that yet. And, she wants to do a video.",
        "response":"[celebrating more]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[everyone is quiet, unsure if she's done or not]",
        "response":"I'm done now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Your boyfriend has been in there for over an hour. I can't believe it, it's likeI'm living with him again. He's here when I go to sleep, he's here when I wake up, he'shere when I want to use the shower, ughh. It's like I'm sixteen all over again .",
        "response":"Well, you're not sixteen, you're both adults now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Your boyfriend has been in there for over an hour. I can't believe it, it's likeI'm living with him again. He's here when I go to sleep, he's here when I wake up, he'shere when I want to use the shower, ughh. It's like I'm sixteen all over again .",
        "response":"Well, you're not sixteen, you're both adults now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's goin' on?",
        "response":"Your boyfriend has been in there for over an hour. I can't believe it, it's likeI'm living with him again. He's here when I go to sleep, he's here when I wake up, he'shere when I want to use the shower, ughh. It's like I'm sixteen all over again .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's goin' on?",
        "response":"Your boyfriend has been in there for over an hour. I can't believe it, it's likeI'm living with him again. He's here when I go to sleep, he's here when I wake up, he'shere when I want to use the shower, ughh. It's like I'm sixteen all over again .",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you're not sixteen, you're both adults now.",
        "response":"GET OUT YOU DUFUS!!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, you're not sixteen, you're both adults now.",
        "response":"GET OUT YOU DUFUS!!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"GET OUT YOU DUFUS!!",
        "response":"Or ya know, he's rubber and you're glue.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Blow drying what, you have no hair.",
        "response":"What's goin' on?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Get the what?",
        "response":"Pie in the hood, pie in the hood. Go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I hope you cleaned your hair out of the drain.",
        "response":"[in a childish voice] I hope you cleaned your hair out of the drain.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I hope you cleaned your hair out of the drain.",
        "response":"[in a childish voice] I hope you cleaned your hair out of the drain.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[in a childish voice] I hope you cleaned your hair out of the drain.",
        "response":"Shut up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[in a childish voice] I hope you cleaned your hair out of the drain.",
        "response":"Shut up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[comes out] All yours.",
        "response":"I hope you cleaned your hair out of the drain.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[childish voice] Shut up.",
        "response":"Cut it out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[childish voice] Shut up.",
        "response":"Cut it out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Shut up.",
        "response":"[childish voice] Shut up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Shut up.",
        "response":"[childish voice] Shut up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Listen, I'm, I'm sorry I didn't make it over there today.",
        "response":"Oh, that's OK. You uh, you had a thing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Listen, I'm, I'm sorry I didn't make it over there today.",
        "response":"Oh, that's OK. You uh, you had a thing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that's OK. You uh, you had a thing.",
        "response":"Yeah well, I hear the place looks great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey!",
        "response":"Listen, I'm, I'm sorry I didn't make it over there today.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey!",
        "response":"Listen, I'm, I'm sorry I didn't make it over there today.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Cut it out.",
        "response":"[childish voice] Mi-mi-mii.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello.",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahh, forget about it, I'm havin' a ball. How's the apartment doin'",
        "response":"Oh hey, it's, it's terriffic. I mean it's a regular space... fest.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahh, forget about it, I'm havin' a ball. How's the apartment doin'",
        "response":"Oh hey, it's, it's terriffic. I mean it's a regular space... fest.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah well, I hear the place looks great.",
        "response":"Ahh, forget about it, I'm havin' a ball. How's the apartment doin'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah well, I hear the place looks great.",
        "response":"Ahh, forget about it, I'm havin' a ball. How's the apartment doin'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that's OK. You uh, you had a thing.",
        "response":"Yeah well, I hear the place looks great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh hey, it's, it's terriffic. I mean it's a regular space... fest.",
        "response":"Oh, well great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh hey, it's, it's terriffic. I mean it's a regular space... fest.",
        "response":"Oh, well great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, well great.",
        "response":"Yeah I just... wanted to call and say hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, well great.",
        "response":"Yeah I just... wanted to call and say hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I still can't believe they promoted her to lieutenant.",
        "response":"Naa, you're just sayin' that 'cause you're in love with Yasmine Blepe.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I still can't believe they promoted her to lieutenant.",
        "response":"Naa, you're just sayin' that 'cause you're in love with Yasmine Blepe.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Naa, you're just sayin' that 'cause you're in love with Yasmine Blepe.",
        "response":"Well, how could anyone not be in love with Yasmine Blepe?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Naa, you're just sayin' that 'cause you're in love with Yasmine Blepe.",
        "response":"Well, how could anyone not be in love with Yasmine Blepe?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah I just... wanted to call and say hey.",
        "response":"Well OK then. [oven timer goes off behind Chandler] Was that the oven timer?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah I just... wanted to call and say hey.",
        "response":"Well OK then. [oven timer goes off behind Chandler] Was that the oven timer?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, can you believe they gave Stephanie skin cancer?",
        "response":"I still can't believe they promoted her to lieutenant.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well OK then. [oven timer goes off behind Chandler] Was that the oven timer?",
        "response":"That's right my friend. It's time for...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, how could anyone not be in love with Yasmine Blepe?",
        "response":"Hey, hey, they're runnin'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But we had one of the greatest talks we ever had last night. I mean it was, itwas like when we first started living together.",
        "response":"Look, I know you don't want to hear this right now but, we've seen him in his newplace, alright. And he's happy, he's, he's decorated.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I did. I thought it'd be great. I figured I'd have like, time alone with my thoughtsbut, ya know, it turns out I don't have as many thoughts as you'd think.",
        "response":"Joey, why don't you talk to Chandler about moving back?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK. [singing] <i>Smelly cat, smell-ly cat, what are they feeding you? Smelly cat</i>[back up singers start singing <i>smelly, smelly, smelly, smelly</i> behind her] Oh woah,oh my God. I mean like, who was that?",
        "response":"They're your backup singers... beind you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK. [singing] <i>Smelly cat, smell-ly cat, what are they feeding you? Smelly cat</i>[back up singers start singing <i>smelly, smelly, smelly, smelly</i> behind her] Oh woah,oh my God. I mean like, who was that?",
        "response":"They're your backup singers... beind you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK Phoebe, you ready to try one?",
        "response":"OK. [singing] <i>Smelly cat, smell-ly cat, what are they feeding you? Smelly cat</i>[back up singers start singing <i>smelly, smelly, smelly, smelly</i> behind her] Oh woah,oh my God. I mean like, who was that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey, why don't you talk to Chandler about moving back?",
        "response":"You really think he'd take me? I mean, we had a pretty good talk last night but,when I moved out, I hurt him bad.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm telling you, there's no way he's moving back.",
        "response":"But we had one of the greatest talks we ever had last night. I mean it was, itwas like when we first started living together.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, hey, they're runnin'",
        "response":"See, this is the brilliance of the show. I say always keep them running. All thetime, running. Run. Run Yasmine, run like the wind.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, how could anyone not be in love with Yasmine Blepe?",
        "response":"Hey, hey, they're runnin'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK. [singing] <i>Smelly cat, smell-ly cat, what are they feeding you? Smelly cat</i>[back up singers - <i>smelly, smelly, smelly, really bad smelly cat, it's not your fault</i>]OK, sorry. I'm just, I'm just not getting that everyone um, gets how smelly this catacually is. I just think that maybe if we could talk about this, 'cause I need to feelthat you really care about the cat.",
        "response":"Honey, uh we, we can talk about this. It's just that it's costing about ahundred dollars a minute to be in here.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK. [singing] <i>Smelly cat, smell-ly cat, what are they feeding you? Smelly cat</i>[back up singers - <i>smelly, smelly, smelly, really bad smelly cat, it's not your fault</i>]OK, sorry. I'm just, I'm just not getting that everyone um, gets how smelly this catacually is. I just think that maybe if we could talk about this, 'cause I need to feelthat you really care about the cat.",
        "response":"Honey, uh we, we can talk about this. It's just that it's costing about ahundred dollars a minute to be in here.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alrighty. From the top.",
        "response":"OK. [singing] <i>Smelly cat, smell-ly cat, what are they feeding you? Smelly cat</i>[back up singers - <i>smelly, smelly, smelly, really bad smelly cat, it's not your fault</i>]OK, sorry. I'm just, I'm just not getting that everyone um, gets how smelly this catacually is. I just think that maybe if we could talk about this, 'cause I need to feelthat you really care about the cat.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alrighty. From the top.",
        "response":"OK. [singing] <i>Smelly cat, smell-ly cat, what are they feeding you? Smelly cat</i>[back up singers - <i>smelly, smelly, smelly, really bad smelly cat, it's not your fault</i>]OK, sorry. I'm just, I'm just not getting that everyone um, gets how smelly this catacually is. I just think that maybe if we could talk about this, 'cause I need to feelthat you really care about the cat.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Honey, uh we, we can talk about this. It's just that it's costing about ahundred dollars a minute to be in here.",
        "response":"Oh OK. So, um, the cat stinks but you love it, let's go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"They're your backup singers... beind you.",
        "response":"OH!! Oh I thought they were just watching me. You know, like at, like at anaquarium, ya know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"They're your backup singers... beind you.",
        "response":"OH!! Oh I thought they were just watching me. You know, like at, like at anaquarium, ya know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OH!! Oh I thought they were just watching me. You know, like at, like at anaquarium, ya know.",
        "response":"Alrighty. From the top.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OH!! Oh I thought they were just watching me. You know, like at, like at anaquarium, ya know.",
        "response":"Alrighty. From the top.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh I-, Oh wait, Tony can you hang on? That's the other line. [gets the other line]Hello. Oh yeah she's here but uh, can she call you back? OK thanks. [hangs up the otherline] Call Joanna. [back on with Tony] Hi.",
        "response":"Did she leave a number?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh I-, Oh wait, Tony can you hang on? That's the other line. [gets the other line]Hello. Oh yeah she's here but uh, can she call you back? OK thanks. [hangs up the otherline] Call Joanna. [back on with Tony] Hi.",
        "response":"Did she leave a number?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, there is no way he was a velociraptor. No Tony, look at the cranial ridge, OK.If Dino was a velociraptor, he would have eaten the Flintstones. Yeah, yeah. [Monica comesout of her room] Oh, were you takin' a nap?",
        "response":"I <i>was</i>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I <i>was</i>.",
        "response":"Oh I-, Oh wait, Tony can you hang on? That's the other line. [gets the other line]Hello. Oh yeah she's here but uh, can she call you back? OK thanks. [hangs up the otherline] Call Joanna. [back on with Tony] Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I <i>was</i>.",
        "response":"Oh I-, Oh wait, Tony can you hang on? That's the other line. [gets the other line]Hello. Oh yeah she's here but uh, can she call you back? OK thanks. [hangs up the otherline] Call Joanna. [back on with Tony] Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did you see me write one down?",
        "response":"I don't have her number, butt-munch.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did you see me write one down?",
        "response":"I don't have her number, butt-munch.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did she leave a number?",
        "response":"Did you see me write one down?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did she leave a number?",
        "response":"Did you see me write one down?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You wanna get out of my face?",
        "response":"Wait hold on Tony, hold on. [answers second line] Hello. Hi, yeah no, she's righthere. Um hold on. [gets first line] Hi Tony, can I call you back? That's uh, that's mysister's boyfriend.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't have her number, butt-munch.",
        "response":"Well, she'll call back, don't be such a baby.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't have her number, butt-munch.",
        "response":"Well, she'll call back, don't be such a baby.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, you wanna get off my back?",
        "response":"You wanna get out of my face?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, you wanna get off my back?",
        "response":"You wanna get out of my face?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, she'll call back, don't be such a baby.",
        "response":"I'm not a baby, you're the baby.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, she'll call back, don't be such a baby.",
        "response":"I'm not a baby, you're the baby.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm not a baby, you're the baby.",
        "response":"Look, you wanna get off my back?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm not a baby, you're the baby.",
        "response":"Look, you wanna get off my back?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You wanna get out of my face?",
        "response":"Wait hold on Tony, hold on. [answers second line] Hello. Hi, yeah no, she's righthere. Um hold on. [gets first line] Hi Tony, can I call you back? That's uh, that's mysister's boyfriend.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wait hold on Tony, hold on. [answers second line] Hello. Hi, yeah no, she's righthere. Um hold on. [gets first line] Hi Tony, can I call you back? That's uh, that's mysister's boyfriend.",
        "response":"Give me that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wait hold on Tony, hold on. [answers second line] Hello. Hi, yeah no, she's righthere. Um hold on. [gets first line] Hi Tony, can I call you back? That's uh, that's mysister's boyfriend.",
        "response":"Give me that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK.",
        "response":"Hi sweetie, look before I forget, did I leave my diaphram at your place? Hi mom.[she starts throwing oranges at Ross who's looking pleased with himself]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So uhh, how's the palace?",
        "response":"You know it's funny you should mention that 'cause I was thinkin'... what's with theboxes?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So uhh, how's the palace?",
        "response":"You know it's funny you should mention that 'cause I was thinkin'... what's with theboxes?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"So uhh, how's the palace?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Give me that.",
        "response":"OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Give me that.",
        "response":"OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Likewise. Uh, I'll take that. [grabs moose hat] It's what I came for. So, this isnew. Where'd you two meet?",
        "response":"At the uh, supermarket, in the uh, ethnic food section. I helped him pick out achorizo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Likewise. Uh, I'll take that. [grabs moose hat] It's what I came for. So, this isnew. Where'd you two meet?",
        "response":"At the uh, supermarket, in the uh, ethnic food section. I helped him pick out achorizo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Chan, is that Joey guy gonna come by and pick up his moose hat or should I justtoss it out?",
        "response":"Well, uh, why don't you ask him yourself. Joey, this is my new roommate Eddie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Chan, is that Joey guy gonna come by and pick up his moose hat or should I justtoss it out?",
        "response":"Well, uh, why don't you ask him yourself. Joey, this is my new roommate Eddie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, uhh, actually I uh, have some news.",
        "response":"Hey Chan, is that Joey guy gonna come by and pick up his moose hat or should I justtoss it out?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know it's funny you should mention that 'cause I was thinkin'... what's with theboxes?",
        "response":"Oh, uhh, actually I uh, have some news.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nice to meet ya.",
        "response":"Likewise. Uh, I'll take that. [grabs moose hat] It's what I came for. So, this isnew. Where'd you two meet?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, uh, why don't you ask him yourself. Joey, this is my new roommate Eddie.",
        "response":"Nice to meet ya.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"At the uh, supermarket, in the uh, ethnic food section. I helped him pick out achorizo.",
        "response":"Wow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well I uh, got what I came for. [puts on moose hat] I'll uh, I'll see you guys.",
        "response":"Hey Jo. When'd you start usin' mousse in your hair?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well yeah, in that it's not being used and I... have it to spare.",
        "response":"Well I uh, got what I came for. [puts on moose hat] I'll uh, I'll see you guys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well yeah, in that it's not being used and I... have it to spare.",
        "response":"Well I uh, got what I came for. [puts on moose hat] I'll uh, I'll see you guys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well you know, we got to talking and uh, he said he needed a place and I had aspare room.",
        "response":"Oh, now it's a spare room?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well you know, we got to talking and uh, he said he needed a place and I had aspare room.",
        "response":"Oh, now it's a spare room?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow.",
        "response":"Well you know, we got to talking and uh, he said he needed a place and I had aspare room.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, now it's a spare room?",
        "response":"Well yeah, in that it's not being used and I... have it to spare.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, now it's a spare room?",
        "response":"Well yeah, in that it's not being used and I... have it to spare.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Now OK, I haven't seen it yet so, if you don't like it, well, so what, none of youever made a video. [puts the tape in] OK.",
        "response":"[The video is a very dramatic episode with an obviously dubbed voice for Phoebe. Everyonewatches in disbeliefe]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know.",
        "response":"I sound amazing. I, I, I've never heard myself sing before. I mean, except in myown head. Oh, this is so cool, now I can hear what you hear.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[cheer]",
        "response":"Now OK, I haven't seen it yet so, if you don't like it, well, so what, none of youever made a video. [puts the tape in] OK.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[The video is a very dramatic episode with an obviously dubbed voice for Phoebe. Everyonewatches in disbeliefe]",
        "response":"Oh my God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, check it out, oh check it out. It's <i>Smelly Cat</i> the video.",
        "response":"[cheer]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, check it out, oh check it out. It's <i>Smelly Cat</i> the video.",
        "response":"[cheer]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Oh, check it out, oh check it out. It's <i>Smelly Cat</i> the video.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Oh, check it out, oh check it out. It's <i>Smelly Cat</i> the video.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God.",
        "response":"I know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I sound amazing. I, I, I've never heard myself sing before. I mean, except in myown head. Oh, this is so cool, now I can hear what you hear.",
        "response":"Pretty uhm, different huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Morning. I just uh, came by to pick up my mail. [looks for the mail on the table bythe door, it's not there] Where's the mail?",
        "response":"Oh it's uh, over there on the table.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Morning. I just uh, came by to pick up my mail. [looks for the mail on the table bythe door, it's not there] Where's the mail?",
        "response":"Oh it's uh, over there on the table.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Morning.",
        "response":"Morning. I just uh, came by to pick up my mail. [looks for the mail on the table bythe door, it's not there] Where's the mail?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Morning.",
        "response":"Morning. I just uh, came by to pick up my mail. [looks for the mail on the table bythe door, it's not there] Where's the mail?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh it's uh, over there on the table.",
        "response":"You don't keep it over here on this table any more?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh it's uh, over there on the table.",
        "response":"You don't keep it over here on this table any more?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Pretty uhm, different huh?",
        "response":"Oh, I am sorry but I am incredibly talented.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Eddie.",
        "response":"Morning.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No I just uh, thought you liked your eggs with the bread with the hole in themiddle, a-la me.",
        "response":"Well I do, but uh, Eddie makes them this way and, well they're pretty darn good.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"No I just uh, thought you liked your eggs with the bread with the hole in themiddle, a-la me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"No I just uh, thought you liked your eggs with the bread with the hole in themiddle, a-la me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, Eddie likes to keep it over there.",
        "response":"Alright, here you go my friend. Eggs a-la Eddie, huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You don't keep it over here on this table any more?",
        "response":"No, Eddie likes to keep it over there.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, here you go my friend. Eggs a-la Eddie, huh?",
        "response":"Oh, ooh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, ooh.",
        "response":"Huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Great, well, I'm happy for ya. [picks up the orange juice carton and it's empty]Alright that's it. He just comes in here, Mr. Jonny Neweggs, with his, his, his movin' themail and his, his 'see ya pals'. And now there's no juice. There's no juice f or thepeople who need the juice and want the juice. I need the juice.",
        "response":"There's another carton right over there.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Great, well, I'm happy for ya. [picks up the orange juice carton and it's empty]Alright that's it. He just comes in here, Mr. Jonny Neweggs, with his, his, his movin' themail and his, his 'see ya pals'. And now there's no juice. There's no juice f or thepeople who need the juice and want the juice. I need the juice.",
        "response":"There's another carton right over there.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I couldn't be happier.",
        "response":"Great, well, I'm happy for ya. [picks up the orange juice carton and it's empty]Alright that's it. He just comes in here, Mr. Jonny Neweggs, with his, his, his movin' themail and his, his 'see ya pals'. And now there's no juice. There's no juice f or thepeople who need the juice and want the juice. I need the juice.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I couldn't be happier.",
        "response":"Great, well, I'm happy for ya. [picks up the orange juice carton and it's empty]Alright that's it. He just comes in here, Mr. Jonny Neweggs, with his, his, his movin' themail and his, his 'see ya pals'. And now there's no juice. There's no juice f or thepeople who need the juice and want the juice. I need the juice.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well I do, but uh, Eddie makes them this way and, well they're pretty darn good.",
        "response":"Well you guys, I'm outta here. See ya pals.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well you guys, I'm outta here. See ya pals.",
        "response":"See ya. [Eddie leaves]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So how you two gettin' along?",
        "response":"Oh, I couldn't be happier.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So how you two gettin' along?",
        "response":"Oh, I couldn't be happier.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"See ya. [Eddie leaves]",
        "response":"So how you two gettin' along?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well I like both eggs equally.",
        "response":"Oh come on. Nobody likes two different kinds of eggs equally. You like one betterthan the other and I wanna know which.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Eggs. Who's eggs do you like better, his or mine, huh?",
        "response":"Well I like both eggs equally.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Eggs. Who's eggs do you like better, his or mine, huh?",
        "response":"Well I like both eggs equally.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"There's another carton right over there.",
        "response":"Hey, this isn't about juice anymore, alright man.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"There's another carton right over there.",
        "response":"Hey, this isn't about juice anymore, alright man.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, so what's it about?",
        "response":"Eggs. Who's eggs do you like better, his or mine, huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, so what's it about?",
        "response":"Eggs. Who's eggs do you like better, his or mine, huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, this isn't about juice anymore, alright man.",
        "response":"Alright, so what's it about?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, this isn't about juice anymore, alright man.",
        "response":"Alright, so what's it about?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh that's great, why don't you tell mommy on me.",
        "response":"Now I'm mommy in this little play? Alright look, I refuse to get sucked into thislike, weird little Geller dimension thing OK. So I'm gonna go and take a nice long hotbubble bath because you kids are driving me crazy. [goes in the bathroom]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Now I'm mommy in this little play? Alright look, I refuse to get sucked into thislike, weird little Geller dimension thing OK. So I'm gonna go and take a nice long hotbubble bath because you kids are driving me crazy. [goes in the bathroom]",
        "response":"OK, what're we gonna do about this?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh come on. Nobody likes two different kinds of eggs equally. You like one betterthan the other and I wanna know which.",
        "response":"Well what's the difference? Your eggs aren't here anymore, are they? You tookyour eggs and you left. You really expect me to never find new eggs?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well I like both eggs equally.",
        "response":"Oh come on. Nobody likes two different kinds of eggs equally. You like one betterthan the other and I wanna know which.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I guess we could tape <i>Entertainment Tonight</i>.",
        "response":"Not that, this, US. Oh my God, Ross, you-re, you're, it's jus-, you-, ever sin-you been here.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I guess we could tape <i>Entertainment Tonight</i>.",
        "response":"Not that, this, US. Oh my God, Ross, you-re, you're, it's jus-, you-, ever sin-you been here.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, what're we gonna do about this?",
        "response":"Well, I guess we could tape <i>Entertainment Tonight</i>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's my TV.",
        "response":"Wha-, oh, quit it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wha-, oh, quit it.",
        "response":"Bite me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Not that, this, US. Oh my God, Ross, you-re, you're, it's jus-, you-, ever sin-you been here.",
        "response":"Ow, ow, OK. Alright, alright, Mon, Mon, you've gone ultrasonic again, alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Not that, this, US. Oh my God, Ross, you-re, you're, it's jus-, you-, ever sin-you been here.",
        "response":"Ow, ow, OK. Alright, alright, Mon, Mon, you've gone ultrasonic again, alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I just can't stand you being here all the time.",
        "response":"Why, why, why can't you stand me being here? I don't, I, we're just, ya know, we'rejust havin' fun.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I just can't stand you being here all the time.",
        "response":"Why, why, why can't you stand me being here? I don't, I, we're just, ya know, we'rejust havin' fun.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Fun? Fun, you think this is fun?",
        "response":"Yeah, c'mon I mean I though, you know, I thought we're just foolin' around. Likewhen, uh, when we were kids.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why, why, why can't you stand me being here? I don't, I, we're just, ya know, we'rejust havin' fun.",
        "response":"Fun? Fun, you think this is fun?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why, why, why can't you stand me being here? I don't, I, we're just, ya know, we'rejust havin' fun.",
        "response":"Fun? Fun, you think this is fun?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ow, ow, OK. Alright, alright, Mon, Mon, you've gone ultrasonic again, alright.",
        "response":"I just can't stand you being here all the time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ow, ow, OK. Alright, alright, Mon, Mon, you've gone ultrasonic again, alright.",
        "response":"I just can't stand you being here all the time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, c'mon I mean I though, you know, I thought we're just foolin' around. Likewhen, uh, when we were kids.",
        "response":"Ross, I hated you when we were kids.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, c'mon I mean I though, you know, I thought we're just foolin' around. Likewhen, uh, when we were kids.",
        "response":"Ross, I hated you when we were kids.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You hated me when we were kids?",
        "response":"Yes. I hated you. I mean I, I, loved you in a 'you're my brother so I have to'kind of way, but basically, yeah, I hated your guts.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You hated me when we were kids?",
        "response":"Yes. I hated you. I mean I, I, loved you in a 'you're my brother so I have to'kind of way, but basically, yeah, I hated your guts.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Fun? Fun, you think this is fun?",
        "response":"Yeah, c'mon I mean I though, you know, I thought we're just foolin' around. Likewhen, uh, when we were kids.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes. I hated you. I mean I, I, loved you in a 'you're my brother so I have to'kind of way, but basically, yeah, I hated your guts.",
        "response":"Why did you hate me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes. I hated you. I mean I, I, loved you in a 'you're my brother so I have to'kind of way, but basically, yeah, I hated your guts.",
        "response":"Why did you hate me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ross, I hated you when we were kids.",
        "response":"You hated me when we were kids?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ross, I hated you when we were kids.",
        "response":"You hated me when we were kids?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why did you hate me?",
        "response":"Because, you were mean to me and you, you teased me and you always, always gotyour way.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why did you hate me?",
        "response":"Because, you were mean to me and you, you teased me and you always, always gotyour way.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Because, you were mean to me and you, you teased me and you always, always gotyour way.",
        "response":"And that wasn't fun for you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Because, you were mean to me and you, you teased me and you always, always gotyour way.",
        "response":"And that wasn't fun for you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't believe you hated me.",
        "response":"Now I love you. And not just 'cause I have to.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Duh-huh!",
        "response":"I can't believe you hated me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Duh-huh!",
        "response":"I can't believe you hated me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And that wasn't fun for you?",
        "response":"Duh-huh!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And that wasn't fun for you?",
        "response":"Duh-huh!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't believe you hated me.",
        "response":"Now I love you. And not just 'cause I have to.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. You're just gonna have to stop pissing me off.",
        "response":"I can do that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. You're just gonna have to stop pissing me off.",
        "response":"I can do that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Yeah. You're just gonna have to stop pissing me off.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Yeah. You're just gonna have to stop pissing me off.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Now I love you. And not just 'cause I have to.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Now I love you. And not just 'cause I have to.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can do that.",
        "response":"Then I won't have to kill you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can do that.",
        "response":"Then I won't have to kill you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So you wanna watch uh, <i>Entertainment Tonight</i>?",
        "response":"Yeah, thanks. You know what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So you wanna watch uh, <i>Entertainment Tonight</i>?",
        "response":"Yeah, thanks. You know what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Then I won't have to kill you.",
        "response":"So you wanna watch uh, <i>Entertainment Tonight</i>?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Then I won't have to kill you.",
        "response":"So you wanna watch uh, <i>Entertainment Tonight</i>?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"If you really want to watch that Serengetti thing, you can.",
        "response":"Ohh... OK. [changes the channel]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"If you really want to watch that Serengetti thing, you can.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"If you really want to watch that Serengetti thing, you can.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, thanks. You know what?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, thanks. You know what?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, how did you find out?",
        "response":"Well, OK, the record company sent over this piece of paper for me to sign, sayingthat it's OK for someone else to sing for me. That was my first clue.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, OK, the record company sent over this piece of paper for me to sign, sayingthat it's OK for someone else to sing for me. That was my first clue.",
        "response":"So what're you gonna do?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Listen. You are not going to believe this but, that is not me singing on thevideo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Listen. You are not going to believe this but, that is not me singing on thevideo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes.",
        "response":"Well, how did you find out?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Listen. You are not going to believe this but, that is not me singing on thevideo.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Listen. You are not going to believe this but, that is not me singing on thevideo.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Yes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"OK, Phoebs. But what about you?",
        "response":"Well I have a video, you have to pay attention. No this, this voice woman, she'sso talented but, according to the producer people, they said she doesn't have like theright look or something, ya know. I mean, it's like, she's like one of those an imals atthe pound who like nobody wants 'cause they're not pretty enough or you know. Like, likesome old dog who's just kind of like stinky and. Huuuuh, oh my God, she's smelly cat. Oh,oh that song has so many levels.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The voice woman. Ya know, I mean, she has a great voice but she doesn't have avideo.",
        "response":"OK, Phoebs. But what about you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What woman?",
        "response":"The voice woman. Ya know, I mean, she has a great voice but she doesn't have avideo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So what're you gonna do?",
        "response":"Well, I can't work with people who would do this.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So what're you gonna do?",
        "response":"Well, I can't work with people who would do this.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I can't work with people who would do this.",
        "response":"Sure.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I can't work with people who would do this.",
        "response":"Sure.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I mean this poor woman.",
        "response":"What woman?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sure.",
        "response":"I mean this poor woman.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No thanks man, I'm not uh, I'm not really into sports.",
        "response":"[stares in disbeliefe] Yeah o-, OK, alright. [oven timer goes off] Doesn'tmatter, time for <i>Baywatch</i>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No thanks man, I'm not uh, I'm not really into sports.",
        "response":"[stares in disbeliefe] Yeah o-, OK, alright. [oven timer goes off] Doesn'tmatter, time for <i>Baywatch</i>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[stares in disbeliefe] Yeah o-, OK, alright. [oven timer goes off] Doesn'tmatter, time for <i>Baywatch</i>.",
        "response":"Y-, y-, you like that show?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[stares in disbeliefe] Yeah o-, OK, alright. [oven timer goes off] Doesn'tmatter, time for <i>Baywatch</i>.",
        "response":"Y-, y-, you like that show?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You don't like that show?",
        "response":"Wha-, n-, no. I mean it's just a bunch of pretty people runnin' around on thebeach, ya know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You don't like that show?",
        "response":"Wha-, n-, no. I mean it's just a bunch of pretty people runnin' around on thebeach, ya know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Eddie, you uh, wanna play some foosball?",
        "response":"No thanks man, I'm not uh, I'm not really into sports.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Y-, y-, you like that show?",
        "response":"You don't like that show?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Y-, y-, you like that show?",
        "response":"You don't like that show?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wha-, n-, no. I mean it's just a bunch of pretty people runnin' around on thebeach, ya know.",
        "response":"Well that's the brilliance of it. The pretty people... and the running.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wha-, n-, no. I mean it's just a bunch of pretty people runnin' around on thebeach, ya know.",
        "response":"Well that's the brilliance of it. The pretty people... and the running.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well that's the brilliance of it. The pretty people... and the running.",
        "response":"I tell ya, I-, I'm gonna go read in my room for a little while.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well that's the brilliance of it. The pretty people... and the running.",
        "response":"I tell ya, I-, I'm gonna go read in my room for a little while.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[singing] <i>Smelly cat, smell-ly cat, what are they feeding you?</i> Everybody.",
        "response":"<i>Smelly cat, smell-ly cat, it's not your fault.</i>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I tell ya, I-, I'm gonna go read in my room for a little while.",
        "response":"Oh o-, OK man.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<i>Smelly cat, smell-ly cat, it's not your fault.</i>",
        "response":"Monica.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[sings] <i>They won't take you to the vet.</i>",
        "response":"Chandler.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Monica.",
        "response":"[sings] <i>They won't take you to the vet.</i>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[sings] <i>And you're no friend to those with noses.</i>",
        "response":"Uh, Ross, those are the only lines we have, sorry. OK, you guys, once more.</font></p><p align=\"center\"><strong><font size=\"3\">END</font></strong></p><hr><p align=\"center\"><!--webbot bot=\"ImageMap\" startspanrectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/218drd.htm\"rectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2.htm\"rectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/216jmo.htm\"src=\"contrl08.gif\" width=\"194\" height=\"60\"alt=\"contrl08.gif \" --><MAP NAME=\"FrontPageMap0\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"138, 2, 197, 84\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/218drd.htm\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"70, 3, 129, 84\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2.htm\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"0, 1, 57, 80\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/216jmo.htm\"></MAP><img src=\"contrl08.gif\" width=\"194\" height=\"60\" alt=\"contrl08.gif \" usemap=\"#FrontPageMap0\"><!--webbot bot=\"ImageMap\" i-checksum=\"48752\" endspan--></p><hr><center><img src=\"/cgi-bin/counter/217\"></center><hr></body></html>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. This game is grotesque. Twenty armless guys joined at the waist by a steelbar, forced to play soccer forever. Ahh, hello, human-rights violation.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line03\"></a> CHANDLER: Ya know Phoebs, don't feel so bad for 'em. After they'redone playing, I break out the little plastic women and everybody has a pretty good time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line03\"></a> CHANDLER: Ya know Phoebs, don't feel so bad for 'em. After they'redone playing, I break out the little plastic women and everybody has a pretty good time.",
        "response":"Why don't you play with your roommate?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh oh, ooh, are we not getting along with the new boy?",
        "response":"No he's, he's alright, just uh, he spends most of his time in his room.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh oh, ooh, are we not getting along with the new boy?",
        "response":"No he's, he's alright, just uh, he spends most of his time in his room.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ah he's a, he's not a big fan of foosball.",
        "response":"Uh oh, ooh, are we not getting along with the new boy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ah he's a, he's not a big fan of foosball.",
        "response":"Uh oh, ooh, are we not getting along with the new boy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why don't you play with your roommate?",
        "response":"Ah he's a, he's not a big fan of foosball.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rachel.",
        "response":"[sings] <i>And you're no friend to those with noses.</i>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh good, ok. Oh nooo, I have to go because I'm late for my um, Green Eggs and Hamdiscussion group. Um tonight it's why he would not eat them on a train. Have fun bye.",
        "response":"That was so lame.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No he's, he's alright, just uh, he spends most of his time in his room.",
        "response":"Maybe that's because you haven't taken the time to get to know him. Let's remedythat, shall we?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No he's, he's alright, just uh, he spends most of his time in his room.",
        "response":"Maybe that's because you haven't taken the time to get to know him. Let's remedythat, shall we?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line04\"></a> PHOEBE: Hi, um, I just thought that it would be fun if the three ofus had some beers and got to know each other.",
        "response":"Yeah alright, that sounds alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What was that?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line04\"></a> PHOEBE: Hi, um, I just thought that it would be fun if the three ofus had some beers and got to know each other.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe that's because you haven't taken the time to get to know him. Let's remedythat, shall we?",
        "response":"We don't need to remedy that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe that's because you haven't taken the time to get to know him. Let's remedythat, shall we?",
        "response":"We don't need to remedy that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We don't need to remedy that.",
        "response":"Oh yeah, it'll be fun. [throws a tennis ball at Eddie's bedroom door]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That was so lame.",
        "response":"I know, yeah. Ok, talk to him. [leaves]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line05\"></a> CHANDLER: What're you kidding? I broke up with her. She actuallythought that Sean Penn was the capital of Cambodia.",
        "response":"That's good man, when everybody knows that the uh, the capital of Cambodia is uh...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um, we should go too, I got patients at 8 in the moring.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line09\"></a> MONICA: Ya know, I was thinking. Ya know how we always stay at yourapartment? Well, I thought maybe tonight we'd stay at my place.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, this is so nice. Alright I have to make a speech. I just wanna say that of allthe guys that Monica has been with, and that is a lot, I like you the best.",
        "response":"Oh, thank you Phoebs. That's very sweet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line09\"></a> MONICA: Ya know, I was thinking. Ya know how we always stay at yourapartment? Well, I thought maybe tonight we'd stay at my place.",
        "response":"I don't know, I don't have my jammies.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's good, that's good. So, so, so who broke up with who?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line05\"></a> CHANDLER: What're you kidding? I broke up with her. She actuallythought that Sean Penn was the capital of Cambodia.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know, yeah. Ok, talk to him. [leaves]",
        "response":"So, you uh, you think that Speed Racer guy gets a lot of tickets er?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, maybe you don't need them.",
        "response":"My baby sister, ladies and gentlemen.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"My baby sister, ladies and gentlemen.",
        "response":"Shut up, I'm happy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That was so lame.",
        "response":"I know, yeah. Ok, talk to him. [leaves]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line11\"></a> TILLY: I'm looking for Eddie Minowick.",
        "response":"Oh, uh, he's not here right now, uh, I'm Chandler, can I take a message, or, ora fishtank?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I gather by that oh that he told you about me.",
        "response":"Oh yeah, your uh, name came up in a uh, conversation that terrified me to myvery soul.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, uh, he's not here right now, uh, I'm Chandler, can I take a message, or, ora fishtank?",
        "response":"Thanks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line11\"></a> TILLY: I'm looking for Eddie Minowick.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh.",
        "response":"I gather by that oh that he told you about me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, thank you Phoebs. That's very sweet.",
        "response":"Ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, oh, c'mon in.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line12\"></a> TILLY: I'm Tilly.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line12\"></a> TILLY: I'm Tilly.",
        "response":"Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thanks.",
        "response":"Oh, oh, c'mon in.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah, your uh, name came up in a uh, conversation that terrified me to myvery soul.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line13\"></a> TILLY: He's kind of intense huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line13\"></a> TILLY: He's kind of intense huh?",
        "response":"Yes. Hey, can I ask you, is Eddie a little...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Eddie, I just came by to drop off your tank.",
        "response":"That's very thoughtful of you. It's very thougtful.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Eddie, I just came by to drop off your tank.",
        "response":"That's very thoughtful of you. It's very thougtful.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes. Hey, can I ask you, is Eddie a little...",
        "response":"[walks around corner] A little what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[walks around corner] A little what?",
        "response":"Bit country? C'mon in here you roomie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[walks around corner] A little what?",
        "response":"Bit country? C'mon in here you roomie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello Tilly.",
        "response":"Eddie, I just came by to drop off your tank.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Bit country? C'mon in here you roomie.",
        "response":"Hello Tilly.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Page 42, page 42, page 42.",
        "response":"Ok, ok, ok. Ooh, hey 'new doc on the block, Days of Our Lives' Joey Tribbiani.'Ooh, cool picture.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebs, check it out, check it out, check it out, check it out.",
        "response":"Oh, ooh, Soap Opera Digest, oh that's one of my favorite digests.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, ooh, Soap Opera Digest, oh that's one of my favorite digests.",
        "response":"Page 42, page 42, page 42.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, ooh, Soap Opera Digest, oh that's one of my favorite digests.",
        "response":"Page 42, page 42, page 42.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's very thoughtful of you. It's very thougtful.",
        "response":"Well, ok then. I'm gonna go. Bye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's very thoughtful of you. It's very thougtful.",
        "response":"Well, ok then. I'm gonna go. Bye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, ok then. I'm gonna go. Bye.",
        "response":"Bye-bye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Tilly leaves]",
        "response":"So, we gettin' a fish?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Bye.",
        "response":"[Tilly leaves]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, well, kinda yeah. Like, remember last week when Alex was in the accident? Wellthe line in the script was, 'If we don't get this woman to a hospital, she's going todie.' But I made it, ' If this woman doesn't get to a hospital, she's not gonna live.'",
        "response":"Ohh, ok, I see what you did there. Aren't you afraid though, that the writers aregonna be kinda mad when they read this?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohh, ok, I see what you did there. Aren't you afraid though, that the writers aregonna be kinda mad when they read this?",
        "response":"Huh? Never really thought about the writers. The scripts just kinda come to myhouse. But you know what? This makes me look good, which makes the show look good, whichmakes the writers look good so how could they be mad about that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line14\"></a> PHOEBE: Hey is this true, that you write a lot of your own lines?",
        "response":"Uh, well, kinda yeah. Like, remember last week when Alex was in the accident? Wellthe line in the script was, 'If we don't get this woman to a hospital, she's going todie.' But I made it, ' If this woman doesn't get to a hospital, she's not gonna live.'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I fall down an elevator shaft? What the hell does this mean, I fall down an elevatorshaft?",
        "response":"DELIVERY GUY: Uhh, I don't know, I just bring the scripts.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DELIVERY GUY: Uhh, I don't know, I just bring the scripts.",
        "response":"They can't kill me, I'm Francesca's long lost son.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, ok, ok. Ooh, hey 'new doc on the block, Days of Our Lives' Joey Tribbiani.'Ooh, cool picture.",
        "response":"Ooh, I look good.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"They can't kill me, I'm Francesca's long lost son.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line15\"></a> DELIVERY GUY: Right. Could you sign this?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Page 42, page 42, page 42.",
        "response":"Ok, ok, ok. Ooh, hey 'new doc on the block, Days of Our Lives' Joey Tribbiani.'Ooh, cool picture.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh, I look good.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line14\"></a> PHOEBE: Hey is this true, that you write a lot of your own lines?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I mean what can I say? I, I was married to Barbara for 30 years. She was myhigh school sweetheart, now you, that's two.",
        "response":"Two it is. Ok, time for bed, I'm gonna go brush my teeth. [goes in the bathroom]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Two? TWO? How is that possible? I mean, have you seen you?",
        "response":"Well, I mean what can I say? I, I was married to Barbara for 30 years. She was myhigh school sweetheart, now you, that's two.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Two? TWO? How is that possible? I mean, have you seen you?",
        "response":"Well, I mean what can I say? I, I was married to Barbara for 30 years. She was myhigh school sweetheart, now you, that's two.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Night Richard. Good luck Mon.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line17\"></a> MONICA: Alright, before I tell you, uh, why don't you tell me howmany women you've been with.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line17\"></a> MONICA: Alright, before I tell you, uh, why don't you tell me howmany women you've been with.",
        "response":"Two.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"DELIVERY GUY: I don't think that's gonna affect the plot of the show.",
        "response":"How can they do this to me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. No way, I'm not signing that.",
        "response":"DELIVERY GUY: I don't think that's gonna affect the plot of the show.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line15\"></a> DELIVERY GUY: Right. Could you sign this?",
        "response":"No. No way, I'm not signing that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Two.",
        "response":"Two? TWO? How is that possible? I mean, have you seen you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Two it is. Ok, time for bed, I'm gonna go brush my teeth. [goes in the bathroom]",
        "response":"<a name=\"line18\"></a> RICHARD: Woah, woah, no wait a minute now. C'mon it's your turn. Ohc'mon. Ya know, I don't need the actual number, just a ballpark.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line18\"></a> RICHARD: Woah, woah, no wait a minute now. C'mon it's your turn. Ohc'mon. Ya know, I don't need the actual number, just a ballpark.",
        "response":"Ok, it is definitely less than a ballpark.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yes, the weenie from Torrini.",
        "response":"Oh honey, are you jealous of Paolo? Oh, c'mon, I'm so much happier with you than Iever was with him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yes, the weenie from Torrini.",
        "response":"Oh honey, are you jealous of Paolo? Oh, c'mon, I'm so much happier with you than Iever was with him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow, I am so glad I'm not Monica right now.",
        "response":"Tell me about it. So what, what's your magic number?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, uh, Billy Dreskin, Pete Carney, Barry, and uh, oh, Paolo.",
        "response":"Oh yes, the weenie from Torrini.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, uh, Billy Dreskin, Pete Carney, Barry, and uh, oh, Paolo.",
        "response":"Oh yes, the weenie from Torrini.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Better not be doin' these in order.",
        "response":"Ok, uh, Billy Dreskin, Pete Carney, Barry, and uh, oh, Paolo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Tell me about it. So what, what's your magic number?",
        "response":"Uhhhooo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's very interesting, ya know, 'cause that's exactly what someone who slept withher would say.",
        "response":"This is nuts. This is crazy. She came over for like two minutes, dropped off afish tank, and left, end of story.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's very interesting, ya know, 'cause that's exactly what someone who slept withher would say.",
        "response":"This is nuts. This is crazy. She came over for like two minutes, dropped off afish tank, and left, end of story.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Eddie, I didn't sleep with your ex-girlfriend.",
        "response":"That's very interesting, ya know, 'cause that's exactly what someone who slept withher would say.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This is nuts. This is crazy. She came over for like two minutes, dropped off afish tank, and left, end of story.",
        "response":"Where's Buddy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This is nuts. This is crazy. She came over for like two minutes, dropped off afish tank, and left, end of story.",
        "response":"Where's Buddy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh honey, are you jealous of Paolo? Oh, c'mon, I'm so much happier with you than Iever was with him.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Buddy?",
        "response":"My fish, Buddy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Where's Buddy?",
        "response":"Buddy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Where's Buddy?",
        "response":"Buddy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"There was no fish when she dropped it off.",
        "response":"Oh, this is, this is unbelievable. I mean, first you sleep with my ex-girlfriendthen you insult my inteligenct by lying about it and then you kill my fish, my Buddy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, that's not bad at all. I mean, you had me thinkin it was like a fleet.",
        "response":"You really ok with it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, that's not bad at all. I mean, you had me thinkin it was like a fleet.",
        "response":"You really ok with it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well yeah.",
        "response":"Well, that's not bad at all. I mean, you had me thinkin it was like a fleet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well yeah.",
        "response":"Well, that's not bad at all. I mean, you had me thinkin it was like a fleet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's it? That's the giant number you were afraid to tell me?",
        "response":"Well yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"My fish, Buddy.",
        "response":"There was no fish when she dropped it off.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"My fish, Buddy.",
        "response":"There was no fish when she dropped it off.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Buddy?",
        "response":"My fish, Buddy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? Alright, what about my two?",
        "response":"Well, it just seems like a really small number.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What? Alright, what about my two?",
        "response":"Well, it just seems like a really small number.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yay. Ok about that two.",
        "response":"What? Alright, what about my two?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yay. Ok about that two.",
        "response":"What? Alright, what about my two?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, it just seems like a really small number.",
        "response":"Right, and...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh honey, I'm fine.",
        "response":"Oh, yay. Ok about that two.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh honey, I'm fine.",
        "response":"Oh, yay. Ok about that two.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You really ok with it?",
        "response":"Oh honey, I'm fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You really ok with it?",
        "response":"Oh honey, I'm fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And, well, don't you have a lot of wild oats to sew? Or is that what you're doingwith me? Oh my God, am I an oat?",
        "response":"Honey, you are not an oat. I, I mean I don't know, I, I guess I'm just not an oatguy. I've only slept with women I've been in love with.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And, well, don't you have a lot of wild oats to sew? Or is that what you're doingwith me? Oh my God, am I an oat?",
        "response":"Honey, you are not an oat. I, I mean I don't know, I, I guess I'm just not an oatguy. I've only slept with women I've been in love with.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Honey, you are not an oat. I, I mean I don't know, I, I guess I'm just not an oatguy. I've only slept with women I've been in love with.",
        "response":"But you've only slept with two people.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Honey, you are not an oat. I, I mean I don't know, I, I guess I'm just not an oatguy. I've only slept with women I've been in love with.",
        "response":"But you've only slept with two people.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right, and...",
        "response":"And, well, don't you have a lot of wild oats to sew? Or is that what you're doingwith me? Oh my God, am I an oat?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right, and...",
        "response":"And, well, don't you have a lot of wild oats to sew? Or is that what you're doingwith me? Oh my God, am I an oat?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, it just seems like a really small number.",
        "response":"Right, and...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But you've only slept with two people.",
        "response":"Right.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But you've only slept with two people.",
        "response":"Right.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line24\"></a> ROSS: Animal sex, animal sex? So what're you saying, I mean, you'resaying that like, there's nothing between us animal at all. I mean there's not even like,uhm, a little animal, not even, not even like, like chipmunk sex?",
        "response":"Ok, Ross, try to hear me. Ok, I, hey, I'm not gonna lie to you. Ok, it was goodwith Paolo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"God, Ross, look, what you and I have is special, all Paolo and I ever had was...",
        "response":"<a name=\"line24\"></a> ROSS: Animal sex, animal sex? So what're you saying, I mean, you'resaying that like, there's nothing between us animal at all. I mean there's not even like,uhm, a little animal, not even, not even like, like chipmunk sex?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But, what you and I have is so much better. Ok, we have tenderness, we haveintimacy, we connect. Ya know, I swear, this is the best I have ever had.",
        "response":"Until now. [jumps on Rachel on the bed]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Knock-knock.",
        "response":"But, what you and I have is so much better. Ok, we have tenderness, we haveintimacy, we connect. Ya know, I swear, this is the best I have ever had.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Knock-knock.",
        "response":"But, what you and I have is so much better. Ok, we have tenderness, we haveintimacy, we connect. Ya know, I swear, this is the best I have ever had.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, Ross, try to hear me. Ok, I, hey, I'm not gonna lie to you. Ok, it was goodwith Paolo.",
        "response":"Knock-knock.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow. Oh wow. You know I love you too, right.",
        "response":"Now I do. [they kiss and fall to the bed]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right.",
        "response":"Wow. Oh wow. You know I love you too, right.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right.",
        "response":"Wow. Oh wow. You know I love you too, right.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi. Richard just told me he loves me.",
        "response":"Oh my God, honey that's great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi. Richard just told me he loves me.",
        "response":"Oh my God, honey that's great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know. I just can't find...",
        "response":"Oh they're in the top drawer. Hurry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know. I just can't find...",
        "response":"Oh they're in the top drawer. Hurry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God, honey that's great.",
        "response":"I know. I just can't find...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God, honey that's great.",
        "response":"I know. I just can't find...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh they're in the top drawer. Hurry.",
        "response":"You need one too?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh they're in the top drawer. Hurry.",
        "response":"You need one too?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, hi.",
        "response":"Hi. Richard just told me he loves me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[comes out of the bedroom] Rachel. [growls then sees Richard standing there] Hey.",
        "response":"Hey. They're just trying to decide somehting.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey. They're just trying to decide somehting.",
        "response":"Good, good, good. So, is uh, was your moustache, did, used to be different?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey. They're just trying to decide somehting.",
        "response":"Good, good, good. So, is uh, was your moustache, did, used to be different?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Monica.",
        "response":"Hi. Uh, we'll be right there, we're just trying to decide something. [shuts thebathroom door]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You need one too?",
        "response":"Ooooh yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"There's only one.",
        "response":"Monica.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Good, good, good. So, is uh, was your moustache, did, used to be different?",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Good, good, good. So, is uh, was your moustache, did, used to be different?",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Oh. How do you uh, ya know, keep it so neat?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, ok, ok, I will, I will, I, hey, I will clean the apartment for two months.",
        "response":"Alright, I tell you what, I'll give this to you now if you can tell me where wekeep the dustpan.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, ok, ok, I will, I will, I, hey, I will clean the apartment for two months.",
        "response":"Alright, I tell you what, I'll give this to you now if you can tell me where wekeep the dustpan.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh. How do you uh, ya know, keep it so neat?",
        "response":"I have a little comb.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh. How do you uh, ya know, keep it so neat?",
        "response":"I have a little comb.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I have a little comb.",
        "response":"Oh. And what do you call that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I have a little comb.",
        "response":"Oh. And what do you call that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh. And what do you call that?",
        "response":"A moustache comb.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Oh. How do you uh, ya know, keep it so neat?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Ok, ok, ok, I will, I will, I, hey, I will clean the apartment for two months.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line26\"></a> MONICA: It's not gonna happen. They're doing it tonight, we can doit tomorrow.",
        "response":"Uh, in the future, if I could see the schedule beforehand...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Shall we?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line26\"></a> MONICA: It's not gonna happen. They're doing it tonight, we can doit tomorrow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, I tell you what, I'll give this to you now if you can tell me where wekeep the dustpan.",
        "response":"Agghhh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no way. You've got it totally the other way around my friend. John Voit was...",
        "response":"Honey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, when I woke up this morning, he'd stolen all the insoles out of my shoes.",
        "response":"Why?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why?",
        "response":"Because he thinks I slept with his ex-girlfriend and killed his fish.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Honey.",
        "response":"What, what oh....[Ross and Rachel go into her room]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So were you in Nam?",
        "response":"Rock-paper-scissors?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Agghhh.",
        "response":"So were you in Nam?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's gonna be ok. You know that?",
        "response":"No, I don't. It's like, ya know, you work your whole life for somethin' and youthink that when you get it it's never gonna be as good as you thought it would be. Butthis so was. Ya know, it changed everything. Like the other day, I got this credit cardapplication, and I was pre- approved. Huh? I've never been pre-approved for anything in mylife.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line27\"></a> PHOEBE: Why would you kill his fish?",
        "response":"Because sometimes, Phoebe after you sleep with someone, you have to kill thefish.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Because he thinks I slept with his ex-girlfriend and killed his fish.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line27\"></a> PHOEBE: Why would you kill his fish?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. [sound of Dr. Remore's body hitting the bottom of the shaft] Now maybe.",
        "response":"<b>[Scene: Joey's apartment. Everyone is outside knocking.]</b>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<b>[Scene: Joey's apartment. Everyone is outside knocking.]</b>",
        "response":"C'mon.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And some of us really have to pee.",
        "response":"[Joey opens the door]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Joey opens the door]",
        "response":"Sorry Joey [runs to the bathroom]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey.",
        "response":"Open up. We want to talk to you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon.",
        "response":"Joey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I don't. It's like, ya know, you work your whole life for somethin' and youthink that when you get it it's never gonna be as good as you thought it would be. Butthis so was. Ya know, it changed everything. Like the other day, I got this credit cardapplication, and I was pre- approved. Huh? I've never been pre-approved for anything in mylife.",
        "response":"I'm sorry man.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[throws it across the room while Eddie's not looking] Listen Eddie, um, I'vebeen thinking about our current living situation and uh, why are you smiling?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line33\"></a> EDDIE: I got a little surprise, look. There's a new fishie. I namedhim uh, Chandler, you know, after, after you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line33\"></a> EDDIE: I got a little surprise, look. There's a new fishie. I namedhim uh, Chandler, you know, after, after you.",
        "response":"[looks in the fish bowl to see a fish cracker] Well that's not an, even a realfish. No, that's a goldfish cracker.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, sure, why not.",
        "response":"[throws it across the room while Eddie's not looking] Listen Eddie, um, I'vebeen thinking about our current living situation and uh, why are you smiling?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[looks in the fish bowl to see a fish cracker] Well that's not an, even a realfish. No, that's a goldfish cracker.",
        "response":"What's you point man?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's you point man?",
        "response":"Ok, good night. [walks towards his room] You big freak of nature.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line32\"></a> EDDIE: Pecan sandy, just made em.",
        "response":"Yeah alright. What're these, raisins?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uhhhaahh.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line32\"></a> EDDIE: Pecan sandy, just made em.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah alright. What're these, raisins?",
        "response":"Uh, sure, why not.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohh, brisk tonight.",
        "response":"Oh man.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohh, brisk tonight.",
        "response":"Oh man.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh man.",
        "response":"Let's never speak of this.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh man.",
        "response":"Let's never speak of this.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Ohh, brisk tonight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Ohh, brisk tonight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Let's never speak of this.",
        "response":"You got it. </font></p><p align=\"center\"><strong><font size=\"3\">END</font></strong></p><hr><p align=\"center\"><!--webbot bot=\"ImageMap\" startspanrectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/219ewg.htm\"rectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2.htm\"rectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/217emi.htm\"src=\"contrl08.gif\" width=\"194\" height=\"60\"alt=\"contrl08.gif \" --><MAP NAME=\"FrontPageMap0\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"138, 1, 197, 84\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/219ewg.htm\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"71, 2, 131, 84\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2.htm\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"0, 0, 58, 80\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/217emi.htm\"></MAP><img src=\"contrl08.gif\" width=\"194\" height=\"60\" alt=\"contrl08.gif \" usemap=\"#FrontPageMap0\"><!--webbot bot=\"ImageMap\" i-checksum=\"48434\" endspan--></p><hr><center><img src=\"/cgi-bin/counter/218\"></center><hr></body></html>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Eddie. Daahh!! What're you doin' here?",
        "response":"Nothin' roomie, just watchin' you sleep.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Makes me feel um, peaceful, heh-heh, please.",
        "response":"I can't sleep now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Makes me feel um, peaceful, heh-heh, please.",
        "response":"I can't sleep now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why?",
        "response":"Makes me feel um, peaceful, heh-heh, please.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why?",
        "response":"Makes me feel um, peaceful, heh-heh, please.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nothin' roomie, just watchin' you sleep.",
        "response":"Why?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nothin' roomie, just watchin' you sleep.",
        "response":"Why?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't sleep now.",
        "response":"You want me to sing?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hannibal Lecter...better roommate than you.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line02\"></a> EDDIE: No. See now I don't think you're being fair. I mean one nightyou see me and you get scared, I mean, what about all the other nights when you don't seeme, huh? What about last night when you went and got a drink of water and I was niceenough to hide behind the door, what's that about, huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line02\"></a> EDDIE: No. See now I don't think you're being fair. I mean one nightyou see me and you get scared, I mean, what about all the other nights when you don't seeme, huh? What about last night when you went and got a drink of water and I was niceenough to hide behind the door, what's that about, huh?",
        "response":"I didn't realize that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, look, that's it, it's over, I want you out, I want you out of the apartmentnow.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line01\"></a> EDDIE: Woah, woah, woah, what're, what're you talkin' about man.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line01\"></a> EDDIE: Woah, woah, woah, what're, what're you talkin' about man.",
        "response":"Hannibal Lecter...better roommate than you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You want me to sing?",
        "response":"No, look, that's it, it's over, I want you out, I want you out of the apartmentnow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't sleep now.",
        "response":"You want me to sing?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I didn't realize that.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"GET OUT NOW!!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"GET OUT NOW!!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Where did you hear it from before?",
        "response":"Oh, right, all right, you know what pallie I understand, consider me gone, you knowwhat, I'll be out by the time you get home from work tomorrow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line03\"></a> EDDIE: Ok, then I want to hear you say it, I, I want to hear you sayyou want me out.",
        "response":"I want you out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes please.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line03\"></a> EDDIE: Ok, then I want to hear you say it, I, I want to hear you sayyou want me out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No no no, I wanna hear it from your lips.",
        "response":"Where did you hear it from before?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No no no, I wanna hear it from your lips.",
        "response":"Where did you hear it from before?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I want you out.",
        "response":"No no no, I wanna hear it from your lips.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"GET OUT NOW!!",
        "response":"Ok, you really want me out?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"GET OUT NOW!!",
        "response":"Ok, you really want me out?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, you really want me out?",
        "response":"Yes please.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow, for a guy who's recently lost his job, you're in an awfully good mood.",
        "response":"Hey, I'll be alright. I mean it's not like I'm starting from sqare one. I was Dr.Drake Remoray on <i>Days of Our Lives</i>. Heh? I mean that's gotta have some kind ofcache.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, right, all right, you know what pallie I understand, consider me gone, you knowwhat, I'll be out by the time you get home from work tomorrow.",
        "response":"[Eddie leaves the room and Chandler mouths &quot;Thank you&quot; to himself]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, I'll be alright. I mean it's not like I'm starting from sqare one. I was Dr.Drake Remoray on <i>Days of Our Lives</i>. Heh? I mean that's gotta have some kind ofcache.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line06\"></a> MONICA: Cache? Jaunty?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line06\"></a> MONICA: Cache? Jaunty?",
        "response":"Chandler gave me word of the day toilet paper. I'm gonna get some coffee.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Fine, make fun. I think it's jaunty.",
        "response":"Wow, for a guy who's recently lost his job, you're in an awfully good mood.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Fine, make fun. I think it's jaunty.",
        "response":"Wow, for a guy who's recently lost his job, you're in an awfully good mood.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Eddie leaves the room and Chandler mouths &quot;Thank you&quot; to himself]",
        "response":"I heard that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oooh, so so so, did you read the book?",
        "response":"Oh my God, it was incredible.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"A mirror?",
        "response":"Fine, make fun. I think it's jaunty.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah and oh, and but there's, there's wind and the wind can make us Goddesses. Butyou know who takes out wind? Men, they just take it.",
        "response":"Men just take out wind?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Men just take out wind?",
        "response":"Ya-huh, all the time, cause they are the lightning bearers.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Men just take out wind?",
        "response":"Ya-huh, all the time, cause they are the lightning bearers.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God, it was incredible.",
        "response":"Didn't it like totally speak to you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Well that sounds kinda cool, kinda like <i>The Hobbit</i>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ya-huh, all the time, cause they are the lightning bearers.",
        "response":"Wow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ya-huh, all the time, cause they are the lightning bearers.",
        "response":"Wow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It is nothing like the Hobbit. It's like reading about every relationship I'veever had, except for Richard.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line07\"></a> PHOEBE: Oh yes, no, Richard would never steal your wind.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes. But all the other ones.",
        "response":"Oh yes. Oh and, the part about how they're always like drinking from out pool ofinner power, but God forbid we should take a sip.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, you're not mad at me for getting fired and everything?",
        "response":"Joey, look at me, look at me. Do I have lipstick on my teeth?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, you're not mad at me for getting fired and everything?",
        "response":"Joey, look at me, look at me. Do I have lipstick on my teeth?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Don't worry about it already. Things happen.",
        "response":"So, you're not mad at me for getting fired and everything?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, 'cause he's yummy.",
        "response":"Yes. But all the other ones.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, 'cause he's yummy.",
        "response":"Yes. But all the other ones.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line07\"></a> PHOEBE: Oh yes, no, Richard would never steal your wind.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"No, 'cause he's yummy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look honey, people get fired left and right in this business. I already got youan audition for <i>Another World</i>.",
        "response":"Alright. Cab driver number two?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look honey, people get fired left and right in this business. I already got youan audition for <i>Another World</i>.",
        "response":"Alright. Cab driver number two?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, can we get back to me?",
        "response":"Look honey, people get fired left and right in this business. I already got youan audition for <i>Another World</i>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, can we get back to me?",
        "response":"Look honey, people get fired left and right in this business. I already got youan audition for <i>Another World</i>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're welcome.",
        "response":"But I was Dr. Drake Remoray. How can I go from bein' a neurosurgeon to drivin' acab?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey, look at me, look at me. Do I have lipstick on my teeth?",
        "response":"No, can we get back to me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey, look at me, look at me. Do I have lipstick on my teeth?",
        "response":"No, can we get back to me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright. Cab driver number two?",
        "response":"You're welcome.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright. Cab driver number two?",
        "response":"You're welcome.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But this is a two line part, it's like takin' a step backwards. I'm not gonna dothis.",
        "response":"Joey, I'm gonna tell you the same thing I told Al Minser and his pyramid of dogs.Take any job you can get and don't make on the floor.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But this is a two line part, it's like takin' a step backwards. I'm not gonna dothis.",
        "response":"Joey, I'm gonna tell you the same thing I told Al Minser and his pyramid of dogs.Take any job you can get and don't make on the floor.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey, I'm gonna tell you the same thing I told Al Minser and his pyramid of dogs.Take any job you can get and don't make on the floor.",
        "response":"I'm sorry. See ya.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But I was Dr. Drake Remoray. How can I go from bein' a neurosurgeon to drivin' acab?",
        "response":"Things change, roll with em.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But I was Dr. Drake Remoray. How can I go from bein' a neurosurgeon to drivin' acab?",
        "response":"Things change, roll with em.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Things change, roll with em.",
        "response":"But this is a two line part, it's like takin' a step backwards. I'm not gonna dothis.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Things change, roll with em.",
        "response":"But this is a two line part, it's like takin' a step backwards. I'm not gonna dothis.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're welcome.",
        "response":"But I was Dr. Drake Remoray. How can I go from bein' a neurosurgeon to drivin' acab?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey you guys.",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line10\"></a> RACHEL: No, why do we always have to do everything according to yourtime table?",
        "response":"Actually it's the movie theatre that has the time schedule. So you don't miss thebeginning.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line12\"></a> RACHEL: Yes, my wind. How do you expect me to grow if you won't letme blow?",
        "response":"You, you know I, I don't, have a- have a problem with that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Excuse me, your, your, your wind?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line12\"></a> RACHEL: Yes, my wind. How do you expect me to grow if you won't letme blow?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, I just, I just really need to be with myself right now. I'm sorry.",
        "response":"Um-um, um-um.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um-um, um-um.",
        "response":"You're right, I don't have to apologize. Sorry. Damnit!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line10\"></a> RACHEL: No, why do we always have to do everything according to yourtime table?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Uh, sweetie we've gotta go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, sweetie we've gotta go.",
        "response":"NO!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"NO!",
        "response":"No?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line13\"></a> ROSS: I, I don't know, it's got all this stuff about wind and treesand there's some kind of sacred pool in it. I mean, I don't really get it but she's, she'spretty upset about it.",
        "response":"See, this is why I don't date women who read. Uh-oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What is it?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line13\"></a> ROSS: I, I don't know, it's got all this stuff about wind and treesand there's some kind of sacred pool in it. I mean, I don't really get it but she's, she'spretty upset about it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line14\"></a> ROSS: What, what's that?",
        "response":"It's my VISA bill. Envelope one of two. That can't be good.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"See, this is why I don't date women who read. Uh-oh.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line14\"></a> ROSS: What, what's that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's my VISA bill. Envelope one of two. That can't be good.",
        "response":"Open it, open in.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Open it, open in.",
        "response":"Oh my God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Open it, open in.",
        "response":"Oh my God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God.",
        "response":"Woah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God.",
        "response":"Woah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"My animals. Hey the guy said they suited me, he spoke with an accent, I was allconfused. I don't know what I'm gonna do.",
        "response":"Well I guess you can start by drivin a cab on <i>Another World</i>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line15\"></a> ROSS: What, woah, woah, $3500 at porcelain safari?",
        "response":"My animals. Hey the guy said they suited me, he spoke with an accent, I was allconfused. I don't know what I'm gonna do.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look at this, how did I spend so much money?",
        "response":"Uh Joey, that's just the minumum amount due, that's your total due.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look at this, how did I spend so much money?",
        "response":"Uh Joey, that's just the minumum amount due, that's your total due.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well I guess you can start by drivin a cab on <i>Another World</i>.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahh.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line15\"></a> ROSS: What, woah, woah, $3500 at porcelain safari?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh Joey, that's just the minumum amount due, that's your total due.",
        "response":"Ahh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Woah.",
        "response":"Look at this, how did I spend so much money?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Woah.",
        "response":"Look at this, how did I spend so much money?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So suck it up man, it's a job, it's money.",
        "response":"Hey, look, I don't need you getting all judgemental and condescending and pedantic.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So suck it up man, it's a job, it's money.",
        "response":"Hey, look, I don't need you getting all judgemental and condescending and pedantic.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That's a two line part.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line16\"></a> ROSS: Joey, you owe $1100 at I Love Lucite.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well I guess you can start by drivin a cab on <i>Another World</i>.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line16\"></a> ROSS: Joey, you owe $1100 at I Love Lucite.",
        "response":"So what.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So what.",
        "response":"So suck it up man, it's a job, it's money.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That audition.",
        "response":"That's a two line part.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"That audition.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"That audition.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, I'm not being any of those things, ok, I'm just being realistic.",
        "response":"Well knock it off, you're supposed to be my friend.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, I'm not being any of those things, ok, I'm just being realistic.",
        "response":"Well knock it off, you're supposed to be my friend.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, look, I don't need you getting all judgemental and condescending and pedantic.",
        "response":"Toilet paper?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, look, I don't need you getting all judgemental and condescending and pedantic.",
        "response":"Toilet paper?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well knock it off, you're supposed to be my friend.",
        "response":"I am your friend.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Look, I'm not being any of those things, ok, I'm just being realistic.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Look, I'm not being any of those things, ok, I'm just being realistic.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Toilet paper?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Toilet paper?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line17\"></a> JOEY: Well then tell me things like, 'Joey you'll be fine,' and,'Hang in there,' and, and, 'Somethin' big's fonna come along, I know it.'",
        "response":"But I don't know it. What I do know is that you owe $2300 at Isn't it Chromantic.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, well then get some sense. I mean it took you what, 10 years to get that job, whoknows how long it's gonna be till you get another.",
        "response":"Look, I don't wanna hear this right now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, well then get some sense. I mean it took you what, 10 years to get that job, whoknows how long it's gonna be till you get another.",
        "response":"Look, I don't wanna hear this right now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Ross, I'm aware of what I owe.",
        "response":"Ok, well then get some sense. I mean it took you what, 10 years to get that job, whoknows how long it's gonna be till you get another.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Ross, I'm aware of what I owe.",
        "response":"Ok, well then get some sense. I mean it took you what, 10 years to get that job, whoknows how long it's gonna be till you get another.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I am your friend.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line17\"></a> JOEY: Well then tell me things like, 'Joey you'll be fine,' and,'Hang in there,' and, and, 'Somethin' big's fonna come along, I know it.'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But I don't know it. What I do know is that you owe $2300 at Isn't it Chromantic.",
        "response":"Hey Ross, I'm aware of what I owe.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, I don't wanna hear this right now.",
        "response":"Huh, I'm just saying...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, I don't wanna hear this right now.",
        "response":"Huh, I'm just saying...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok. I'll see ya later. Just think about it, ok.",
        "response":"I don't need to think about it. I was Dr. Drake Remoray. That was huge. Big thingsare gonna happen, you'll see. Ross, you still there?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well don't just say.",
        "response":"Ya know, maybe, maybe I should just go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well don't just say.",
        "response":"Ya know, maybe, maybe I should just go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok.",
        "response":"Ok. I'll see ya later. Just think about it, ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok.",
        "response":"Ok. I'll see ya later. Just think about it, ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh, I'm just saying...",
        "response":"Well don't just say.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh, I'm just saying...",
        "response":"Well don't just say.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ya know, maybe, maybe I should just go.",
        "response":"Ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ya know, maybe, maybe I should just go.",
        "response":"Ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line18\"></a> EDDIE: Oh yeah, that's right, look I got us a new goldfish. He's alot fiestier that the last one.",
        "response":"Maybe 'cause the last one was made by Pepperidge Farm. Look Eddie, isn't theresomething else you're supposed to be doing right now?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Maybe 'cause the last one was made by Pepperidge Farm. Look Eddie, isn't theresomething else you're supposed to be doing right now?",
        "response":"Well, not unless it's got something to do with dehydrating my man because right nowI'm a dehydrating maniac!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, not unless it's got something to do with dehydrating my man because right nowI'm a dehydrating maniac!",
        "response":"Look you have to help me out here. I thought we had a deal. I thought by thetime...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look Eddie, aren't you forgetting anything?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line18\"></a> EDDIE: Oh yeah, that's right, look I got us a new goldfish. He's alot fiestier that the last one.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahhhh-gaaaahhh. Eddie what're you still doin' here?",
        "response":"Ah, just some basic dehydrating of a few fruits and vegetables. MAN ALIVE thisthing's fantastic!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahhhh-gaaaahhh. Eddie what're you still doin' here?",
        "response":"Ah, just some basic dehydrating of a few fruits and vegetables. MAN ALIVE thisthing's fantastic!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look you have to help me out here. I thought we had a deal. I thought by thetime...",
        "response":"<a name=\"line19\"></a> EDDIE: Ah-ah-ah, you know what that is?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ah, just some basic dehydrating of a few fruits and vegetables. MAN ALIVE thisthing's fantastic!",
        "response":"Look Eddie, aren't you forgetting anything?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey pal.",
        "response":"Ahhhh-gaaaahhh. Eddie what're you still doin' here?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ah, it's career stuff. I don't know if you heard but they killed off my character onthe show.",
        "response":"Oh, that's too bad. How'd they do it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ah, it's career stuff. I don't know if you heard but they killed off my character onthe show.",
        "response":"Oh, that's too bad. How'd they do it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Lemonade? You ok man?",
        "response":"Ah, it's career stuff. I don't know if you heard but they killed off my character onthe show.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Lemonade? You ok man?",
        "response":"Ah, it's career stuff. I don't know if you heard but they killed off my character onthe show.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line19\"></a> EDDIE: Ah-ah-ah, you know what that is?",
        "response":"Your last roommate's kidney?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that's too bad. How'd they do it?",
        "response":"I fell down an elevator shaft.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that's too bad. How'd they do it?",
        "response":"I fell down an elevator shaft.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Gunther, let me get a lemonade to go.",
        "response":"Lemonade? You ok man?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I fell down an elevator shaft.",
        "response":"That sucks. I was buried in an avalanche.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line22\"></a> CHANDLER: You, move out. Take your fruit, your stupid small fruitand GET OUT!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Aaahhhhhhh! Aaahhhh!",
        "response":"Why must everybody watch me sleep? There'll be no more watching me sleep, nomore watching.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why must everybody watch me sleep? There'll be no more watching me sleep, nomore watching.",
        "response":"I wa-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why must everybody watch me sleep? There'll be no more watching me sleep, nomore watching.",
        "response":"I wa-",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I fell down an elevator shaft.",
        "response":"That sucks. I was buried in an avalanche.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I used to be Bryce on <i>All My Children</i>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That sucks. I was buried in an avalanche.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That sucks. I was buried in an avalanche.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I wa-",
        "response":"Uuuh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This is not out of the blue, this is smack dab in the middle of the blue.",
        "response":"Ohhhh. Relax, take it easy buddy. Tell me twice, you want me to go? Alright,alright, guess I'll be back for my stuff. [walks out the door and after a pause comes backin] But if you think for one second I'm leaving you alone with my fish, you're insaneJack!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This is not out of the blue, this is smack dab in the middle of the blue.",
        "response":"Ohhhh. Relax, take it easy buddy. Tell me twice, you want me to go? Alright,alright, guess I'll be back for my stuff. [walks out the door and after a pause comes backin] But if you think for one second I'm leaving you alone with my fish, you're insaneJack!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohhhh. Relax, take it easy buddy. Tell me twice, you want me to go? Alright,alright, guess I'll be back for my stuff. [walks out the door and after a pause comes backin] But if you think for one second I'm leaving you alone with my fish, you're insaneJack!",
        "response":"You want some help.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I uh, I gotta tell you man, I mean, that's uh, it's kinda out of the blue, I meandon't you think?",
        "response":"This is not out of the blue, this is smack dab in the middle of the blue.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I uh, I gotta tell you man, I mean, that's uh, it's kinda out of the blue, I meandon't you think?",
        "response":"This is not out of the blue, this is smack dab in the middle of the blue.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line22\"></a> CHANDLER: You, move out. Take your fruit, your stupid small fruitand GET OUT!",
        "response":"You, you want, you want me to move out?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh.",
        "response":"I uh, I gotta tell you man, I mean, that's uh, it's kinda out of the blue, I meandon't you think?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh.",
        "response":"I uh, I gotta tell you man, I mean, that's uh, it's kinda out of the blue, I meandon't you think?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You, you want, you want me to move out?",
        "response":"Uh-huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohhhh. Relax, take it easy buddy. Tell me twice, you want me to go? Alright,alright, guess I'll be back for my stuff. [walks out the door and after a pause comes backin] But if you think for one second I'm leaving you alone with my fish, you're insaneJack!",
        "response":"You want some help.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"CASTING GUY: Five oh dollars.",
        "response":"Ohh, you know what it is? It's smudgy 'cause they're fax pages. Now when I was on <i>Daysof Our Lives</i> as Dr. Drake Remoray, they'd send over the whole script on real paper andeverything.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<i>All the way to the airport huh? You know that's over 30 miles, that's gonna costyou about so bucks.</i>",
        "response":"CASTING GUY: Excuse me, that's 50 bucks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Do you not remember the puppet guy?",
        "response":"Yeah you like totally let him wash his feet in the pool of your inner power.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You want some help.",
        "response":"No help required Chico. [reaches into the tank and grabs the fish and puts it inhis pocket]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"CASTING GUY: Excuse me, that's 50 bucks.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And I would have to say pah-huh.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Do you not remember the puppet guy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"CASTING GUY: Five oh dollars.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line27\"></a> RACHEL: Ok, ok, ok, moving on, moving on, next question. Ok number29, have you ever betrayed another goddess for a lightning bearer? Ok, number 30.",
        "response":"Woah, woah, woah, let's go back to 29.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line27\"></a> RACHEL: Ok, ok, ok, moving on, moving on, next question. Ok number29, have you ever betrayed another goddess for a lightning bearer? Ok, number 30.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And his puppet too.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line26\"></a> PHOEBE: Yeah ok, well at least I didn't let some guy into the forestof my righteous truth on the first date.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line26\"></a> PHOEBE: Yeah ok, well at least I didn't let some guy into the forestof my righteous truth on the first date.",
        "response":"Who?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Not uh, not to my recollection.",
        "response":"Huuh, alright, Danny Arshak, ninth grade. Oh, c'mon Rach, you know the bottle wastotally pointing at me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah you like totally let him wash his feet in the pool of your inner power.",
        "response":"And his puppet too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Woah, woah, woah, let's go back to 29.",
        "response":"Not uh, not to my recollection.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Who?",
        "response":"Paul.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Paul.",
        "response":"Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"They're takin all my stuff back. I guess you were right.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line29\"></a> ROSS: No look I wasn''t right, that's what I came here to tell you.I was totally hung up on, on my own stuff. Listen, I'm someone who needs the wholesecurity thing, ya know. To know exactly where my next paycheck is coming from buy you,you don't need that and that's amazing to me. I could never do what you do Joey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line29\"></a> ROSS: No look I wasn''t right, that's what I came here to tell you.I was totally hung up on, on my own stuff. Listen, I'm someone who needs the wholesecurity thing, ya know. To know exactly where my next paycheck is coming from buy you,you don't need that and that's amazing to me. I could never do what you do Joey.",
        "response":"Thanks Ross.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line28\"></a> PHOEBE: Listen to you two. It's so sad. Looks like I'm gonna begoing to the goddess meetings alone.",
        "response":"Well not when they find out you slept with Jason Hurley an hour after he broke upwith Monica.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Only 'cause you took up half the circle.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line28\"></a> PHOEBE: Listen to you two. It's so sad. Looks like I'm gonna begoing to the goddess meetings alone.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thanks Ross.",
        "response":"Yeah. And you should hold out for something bigger. I can't tell you how muchrespect I have for you not going to that stupid cab driver audition.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huuh, alright, Danny Arshak, ninth grade. Oh, c'mon Rach, you know the bottle wastotally pointing at me.",
        "response":"Only 'cause you took up half the circle.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Not uh, not to my recollection.",
        "response":"Huuh, alright, Danny Arshak, ninth grade. Oh, c'mon Rach, you know the bottle wastotally pointing at me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[enters] Oh my God, what's goin' on?",
        "response":"They're takin all my stuff back. I guess you were right.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh hey uh, be careful with that 3-D last supper, Judas is a little loose.",
        "response":"[enters] Oh my God, what's goin' on?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. And you should hold out for something bigger. I can't tell you how muchrespect I have for you not going to that stupid cab driver audition.",
        "response":"I went.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. And you should hold out for something bigger. I can't tell you how muchrespect I have for you not going to that stupid cab driver audition.",
        "response":"I went.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Great, how did it go?",
        "response":"I didn't get it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Great, how did it go?",
        "response":"I didn't get it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I went.",
        "response":"Great, how did it go?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I went.",
        "response":"Great, how did it go?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I didn't get it.",
        "response":"Good for you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I didn't get it.",
        "response":"Good for you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Good for you.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right then.",
        "response":"[movers removing a glass parrot] Oh, not my parrot.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right then.",
        "response":"[movers removing a glass parrot] Oh, not my parrot.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"You're livin' the dream.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"You're livin' the dream.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're livin' the dream.",
        "response":"Huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're livin' the dream.",
        "response":"Huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Good for you.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh?",
        "response":"All right then.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh?",
        "response":"All right then.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Go ahead, go ahead with the bird. Ok, do you have anything for around 200?",
        "response":"Uh, the dog. [points to a big poecelain greyhound]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't watch this.",
        "response":"[approaching the mover holding the parrot] Hey hold on, hold on. How much for theuh, how much to save the bird?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, the dog. [points to a big poecelain greyhound]",
        "response":"Huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, the dog. [points to a big poecelain greyhound]",
        "response":"Huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[movers removing a glass parrot] Oh, not my parrot.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[movers removing a glass parrot] Oh, not my parrot.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I can't watch this.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"I can't watch this.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We didn't order cake.",
        "response":"No, I know, they're from me. Look you guys this is not good. I mean we have enoughtrouble with guys stealing our wind without taking it from each other.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We didn't order cake.",
        "response":"No, I know, they're from me. Look you guys this is not good. I mean we have enoughtrouble with guys stealing our wind without taking it from each other.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I know, they're from me. Look you guys this is not good. I mean we have enoughtrouble with guys stealing our wind without taking it from each other.",
        "response":"You're right.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I know, they're from me. Look you guys this is not good. I mean we have enoughtrouble with guys stealing our wind without taking it from each other.",
        "response":"You're right.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know.",
        "response":"I love you goddesses. I don't ever want to suck your wind again.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Here are your cakes.",
        "response":"We didn't order cake.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"I'll take it. My gift to you man.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're right.",
        "response":"You know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So I got it in the junior miss department, big diff. Anyway check it out man, it'sgonna make a hell of a conversation piece at out next cocktail party, huh pal?",
        "response":"Our next cocktail party?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I love you goddesses. I don't ever want to suck your wind again.",
        "response":"Thank you. So are we good?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, you know, put chips in it, we'll make like a chip chick.",
        "response":"Eddie, do you remember yesterday?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, you know, put chips in it, we'll make like a chip chick.",
        "response":"Eddie, do you remember yesterday?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Our next cocktail party?",
        "response":"Yeah, you know, put chips in it, we'll make like a chip chick.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Our next cocktail party?",
        "response":"Yeah, you know, put chips in it, we'll make like a chip chick.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Eddie, do you remember yesterday?",
        "response":"Uh yes, I think I vaguely recall it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thank you. So are we good?",
        "response":"We're good.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We're good.",
        "response":"We're good?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So on this road trip, did you guys win any money?",
        "response":"Naah, I crapped out, but Mr. 21 over here he cleans up, 300 bucks, check it out hebuys me these new shoes, sweet huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Naah, I crapped out, but Mr. 21 over here he cleans up, 300 bucks, check it out hebuys me these new shoes, sweet huh?",
        "response":"Nice.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Naah, I crapped out, but Mr. 21 over here he cleans up, 300 bucks, check it out hebuys me these new shoes, sweet huh?",
        "response":"Nice.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line34\"></a> CHANDLER: So what happened?",
        "response":"We took a road trip to Las Vegas man.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh yes, I think I vaguely recall it.",
        "response":"Do you remember talking to me yesterday?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh yes, I think I vaguely recall it.",
        "response":"Do you remember talking to me yesterday?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Eddie, do you remember yesterday?",
        "response":"Uh yes, I think I vaguely recall it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, yes.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line34\"></a> CHANDLER: So what happened?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Do you remember talking to me yesterday?",
        "response":"Uh, yes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's Eddie you freak, your roommate.",
        "response":"I, I'm sorry, I uh [unchains the door and opens it all the way] I already have aroommate. [Joey turns around in the leather recliner]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why doesn't my key work and what's all my stuff doin' downstairs?",
        "response":"Well, I'm, I'm sorry...[Eddie forces his head in the door] Ahhh. Have we met?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why doesn't my key work and what's all my stuff doin' downstairs?",
        "response":"Well, I'm, I'm sorry...[Eddie forces his head in the door] Ahhh. Have we met?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I, I'm sorry, I uh [unchains the door and opens it all the way] I already have aroommate. [Joey turns around in the leather recliner]",
        "response":"Hello.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I'm, I'm sorry...[Eddie forces his head in the door] Ahhh. Have we met?",
        "response":"It's Eddie you freak, your roommate.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I'm, I'm sorry...[Eddie forces his head in the door] Ahhh. Have we met?",
        "response":"It's Eddie you freak, your roommate.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hello.",
        "response":"Yeah, he's lived here for years, I don't, I don't know what you're talking aboutman.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"May I help you?",
        "response":"Why doesn't my key work and what's all my stuff doin' downstairs?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nice.",
        "response":"Yeah. Well see ya upstairs. See ya pals.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line38\"></a> CHANDLER: See ya. [shuts the door] Goodbuy you fruit dryingpsychopath. So you want me to help you unpack your stuff?",
        "response":"Na, na I'm ok. Oh and uh, just so you know, I'm not movin' back in 'cause I have to.Well, I mean, I do have to. It's just that that place wasn't really, I mean, this is...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Na, na I'm ok. Oh and uh, just so you know, I'm not movin' back in 'cause I have to.Well, I mean, I do have to. It's just that that place wasn't really, I mean, this is...",
        "response":"Welcome home man. [they hug and jump around]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey no problem.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line38\"></a> CHANDLER: See ya. [shuts the door] Goodbuy you fruit dryingpsychopath. So you want me to help you unpack your stuff?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know I would.",
        "response":"Well that's uh, that's a good point. Um ok, well, uh, I guess I got the wrongapartment then. I, I'm, look, I'm, ya know, I'm sorry, I'm terriably sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well that's uh, that's a good point. Um ok, well, uh, I guess I got the wrongapartment then. I, I'm, look, I'm, ya know, I'm sorry, I'm terriably sorry.",
        "response":"Hey no problem.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, he's lived here for years, I don't, I don't know what you're talking aboutman.",
        "response":"No he, he moved out and I moved in.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No he, he moved out and I moved in.",
        "response":"Well I, I think we'd remember something like that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Welcome home man. [they hug and jump around]",
        "response":"A little foos?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Welcome home man. [they hug and jump around]",
        "response":"A little foos?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line36\"></a> CHANDLER: I'm gonna hold him a different way. Look I don'tunderstand, if you hated it so much, why did you buy it in the first place?",
        "response":"Well, I had a whole ceramic zoo thing goin' over there but now, without the otherones, it just looks tacky.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He paid a lot of money for it.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line36\"></a> CHANDLER: I'm gonna hold him a different way. Look I don'tunderstand, if you hated it so much, why did you buy it in the first place?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line02\"></a> PHOEBE: C'mon, happy family gets a dog, frontier fun.",
        "response":"Yeah but Phoebs, what about the end?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What're you talkin' about?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line02\"></a> PHOEBE: C'mon, happy family gets a dog, frontier fun.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What happened to the foosball?",
        "response":"Ah that's a cantelope.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Absolutely.",
        "response":"What happened to the foosball?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Absolutely.",
        "response":"What happened to the foosball?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"A little foos?",
        "response":"Absolutely.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"A little foos?",
        "response":"Absolutely.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line10\"></a> CHANDLER: I don't know, Richard's really nice and everything, uh,it's just that we don't know him really well, ya know, and plus he's, ya know, old [Monicagives him a glare] -er than some people, but, uh, younger than some buildings.",
        "response":"So what, he's a little older, big deal, I mean he's important to me. Ya know ifyou ask him, he might take you on his Jag. [walks off]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon. Keeps his fingers to himself and he's always minty fresh.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line10\"></a> CHANDLER: I don't know, Richard's really nice and everything, uh,it's just that we don't know him really well, ya know, and plus he's, ya know, old [Monicagives him a glare] -er than some people, but, uh, younger than some buildings.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yu-huh. That's when my mother would shut off the TV and say 'The end'.",
        "response":"What about the part where he has rabies?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, this could be tough.",
        "response":"[Monica walks back in the kitchen] Ok ok ok ok. Monica, we'll bring him, but only ifhe takes the Jaguar.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What when Yeller saves saves the family from the wolf and everyone's happy?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line03\"></a> RACHEL: That's not the end.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What about the part where he has rabies?",
        "response":"He doesn't have rabies, he has babies. That's what my mom said.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line03\"></a> RACHEL: That's not the end.",
        "response":"Yu-huh. That's when my mother would shut off the TV and say 'The end'.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know.",
        "response":"C'mon. Keeps his fingers to himself and he's always minty fresh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I meant, why don't you take Richard to the game? What?",
        "response":"I don't know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh shout, that would have been fun.",
        "response":"Oh look, did, did you just see that? Did you see? He just waved, he just waved, he'snever waved before, you've never waved before. Yes he has. Very good.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Monica walks back in the kitchen] Ok ok ok ok. Monica, we'll bring him, but only ifhe takes the Jaguar.",
        "response":"Ooh, you almost had it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Phoebs, whatcha got there?",
        "response":"Ok, <i>Love Story</i>, <i>Brian's Song</i>, and <i>Terms of Endearment</i>.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really? I mean, I, I had a whole speach prepared.",
        "response":"Oh shout, that would have been fun.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[smells Ben's butt] No no, you're fine, you're fine.",
        "response":"[enters with Susan] Hello",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi honey.",
        "response":"Oh you guys are not gonna believe what happened.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh you guys are not gonna believe what happened.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey Phoebs, whatcha got there?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[enters with Susan] Hello",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, ya know, they're a little behind the times in Colonial Williamsburg.",
        "response":"Think I better go before mommy starts weeping.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"He-he-eyy. [Shakes his had and passes the dollar]",
        "response":"Hey, you're gettin' better. I'm gonna keep this by the way.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're welcome. Hey Joey, thanks for parking the car [passes the dollar back].",
        "response":"No problem. Hey Chandler",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, you're gettin' better. I'm gonna keep this by the way.",
        "response":"Ok. He kept my dollar.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So'd you guys have fun?",
        "response":"Your boyfriend is so cool.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No problem. Hey Chandler",
        "response":"I think they get it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No problem. Hey Chandler",
        "response":"I think they get it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Your boyfriend is so cool.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I think they get it.",
        "response":"Ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Naa. A while ago I got a sah out of him, which I thought, ya know, might turn intosah-condary caregiver but... Hey, would you uh, would you hold him for a sec, 'cause I, Igotta take this off.",
        "response":"Oh, yeah sure, Ok. [she takes Ben and holds him at arms length]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No luck huh?",
        "response":"Naa. A while ago I got a sah out of him, which I thought, ya know, might turn intosah-condary caregiver but... Hey, would you uh, would you hold him for a sec, 'cause I, Igotta take this off.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, didn't he tell ya?",
        "response":"Well, he told me he was going out with the guys, I just didn't know that you werethe guys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, he told me he was going out with the guys, I just didn't know that you werethe guys.",
        "response":"You hear that? We're the guys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"CAROL and SUSAN: We love you. Buy.",
        "response":"Have a good time. Ok, Ben.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Think I better go before mommy starts weeping.",
        "response":"Buy mommy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Buy mommy.",
        "response":"CAROL and SUSAN: We love you. Buy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Have a good time. Ok, Ben.",
        "response":"Ross.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ross.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, here, here. There we go.",
        "response":"Ok, I'm sorry, I'm just not very good with babies. I mean I haven't been aroundthem, I mean, you know, since I was one.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, here, here. There we go.",
        "response":"Ok, I'm sorry, I'm just not very good with babies. I mean I haven't been aroundthem, I mean, you know, since I was one.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah sure, Ok. [she takes Ben and holds him at arms length]",
        "response":"<a name=\"line24\"></a> ROSS: What're you doing?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line25\"></a> ROSS: Well just hold him like you'd hold a football.",
        "response":"This is how I would hold a football.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line25\"></a> ROSS: Well just hold him like you'd hold a football.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line24\"></a> ROSS: What're you doing?",
        "response":"Uh, I'm holding Ben.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This is how I would hold a football.",
        "response":"Ok, here, here. There we go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, I'm holding Ben.",
        "response":"Yeah, well, he's a baby not a bomb.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, well, he's a baby not a bomb.",
        "response":"Ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, I'm sorry, I'm just not very good with babies. I mean I haven't been aroundthem, I mean, you know, since I was one.",
        "response":"It's alright, it's no big deal.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, I'm sorry, I'm just not very good with babies. I mean I haven't been aroundthem, I mean, you know, since I was one.",
        "response":"It's alright, it's no big deal.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Yeah, definitely, I'm sure you'll feel totally different when it's our baby.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Yeah, definitely, I'm sure you'll feel totally different when it's our baby.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, definitely, I'm sure you'll feel totally different when it's our baby.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, definitely, I'm sure you'll feel totally different when it's our baby.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's alright, it's no big deal.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's alright, it's no big deal.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Two, two babies?",
        "response":"Yeah. Ya know, a boy and a girl. Hopefully the girl will come first so Ben herewon't feel too competitive.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Two, two babies?",
        "response":"Yeah. Ya know, a boy and a girl. Hopefully the girl will come first so Ben herewon't feel too competitive.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You think about stuff like that?",
        "response":"Uhh, yeah. I mean, actually I kinda think that we'll have, we'll have two babies.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You think about stuff like that?",
        "response":"Uhh, yeah. I mean, actually I kinda think that we'll have, we'll have two babies.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uhh, yeah. I mean, actually I kinda think that we'll have, we'll have two babies.",
        "response":"Two, two babies?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uhh, yeah. I mean, actually I kinda think that we'll have, we'll have two babies.",
        "response":"Two, two babies?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"You think about stuff like that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"You think about stuff like that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, that way I figure, ya know, we'll be far enough away from our parents that wedon't have to see them all the time but close enough that they can come over and babysitwhenever we want. And yes, I know, the taxes are a little higher than, let's say, Nassaucounty but the school system's supposedly great.",
        "response":"Wow. Wow, that's great. Great. Ok, wow, you know what.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh.",
        "response":"Yeah, that way I figure, ya know, we'll be far enough away from our parents that wedon't have to see them all the time but close enough that they can come over and babysitwhenever we want. And yes, I know, the taxes are a little higher than, let's say, Nassaucounty but the school system's supposedly great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh.",
        "response":"Yeah, that way I figure, ya know, we'll be far enough away from our parents that wedon't have to see them all the time but close enough that they can come over and babysitwhenever we want. And yes, I know, the taxes are a little higher than, let's say, Nassaucounty but the school system's supposedly great.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. Ya know, a boy and a girl. Hopefully the girl will come first so Ben herewon't feel too competitive.",
        "response":"Then what's gonna happen?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. Ya know, a boy and a girl. Hopefully the girl will come first so Ben herewon't feel too competitive.",
        "response":"Then what's gonna happen?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Then what's gonna happen?",
        "response":"Well, we won't wanna raise kids in the city so we'll probably move to uh, Scarsdale.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Then what's gonna happen?",
        "response":"Well, we won't wanna raise kids in the city so we'll probably move to uh, Scarsdale.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, we won't wanna raise kids in the city so we'll probably move to uh, Scarsdale.",
        "response":"Uh-huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, we won't wanna raise kids in the city so we'll probably move to uh, Scarsdale.",
        "response":"Uh-huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, that way I figure, ya know, we'll be far enough away from our parents that wedon't have to see them all the time but close enough that they can come over and babysitwhenever we want. And yes, I know, the taxes are a little higher than, let's say, Nassaucounty but the school system's supposedly great.",
        "response":"Wow. Wow, that's great. Great. Ok, wow, you know what.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Huh?",
        "response":"I'm off my break now so uh, um here you take this [hands back Ben] and um, I amgonna go pour these very nice people some coffee. Ok. Oh look at that, I don't have a pot.I don't have a pot. Well, hey, maybe I've got one at home, or in Scarsdale. Hey is that adoor? [leaves]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So you watched the movies huh?",
        "response":"Uh huh, what is happening to the world? I mean, no no no, 'cause ET leaves, andand Rocky loses, Charlotte dies.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh huh, what is happening to the world? I mean, no no no, 'cause ET leaves, andand Rocky loses, Charlotte dies.",
        "response":"Charlotte who?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, ok, murder, cancer, soccer teams eating each other in the Andes.",
        "response":"So you watched the movies huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Phoebs, what's happening?",
        "response":"Oh, ok, murder, cancer, soccer teams eating each other in the Andes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow. Wow, that's great. Great. Ok, wow, you know what.",
        "response":"Huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow. Wow, that's great. Great. Ok, wow, you know what.",
        "response":"Huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey Phoebs, what's happening?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Please, I almost fell for that with, uh, <i>Pride of the Yankees</i>, I thought Iwas gonna see a film about Yankee pride and then, boom, the guy gets Lou Gehrig's disease.",
        "response":"Uh, the guy was Lou Gehrig. Didn't you kinda see it coming?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"With the web, the spider she dies, she does. She has babies and dies. It's like yaknow, hey welcome home from the hospital, thud.",
        "response":"Alright, you wanna feel better?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line26\"></a> PHOEBE: <i>It's a Wonderful Life</i>. Yes I've heard of this.",
        "response":"So you can't lose, it's there in the title. Wonderfullness is baked right in.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, the guy was Lou Gehrig. Didn't you kinda see it coming?",
        "response":"Phoebe, just watch that, I promise it will resotre all your faith in humanity.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Charlotte who?",
        "response":"With the web, the spider she dies, she does. She has babies and dies. It's like yaknow, hey welcome home from the hospital, thud.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, here, watch this.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line26\"></a> PHOEBE: <i>It's a Wonderful Life</i>. Yes I've heard of this.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, you wanna feel better?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, you wanna feel better?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Ok, here, watch this.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok. [leaves]",
        "response":"Oh, why does this bother me so much? I mean I don't wanna be one of those peoplewho tells their boyfriend they wanna spend 24 hours a day with them.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sure.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line30\"></a> MONICA: It's just that he doesn't have that much free time, ya know,and I don't know, what do I do?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, it's the college playoffs.",
        "response":"Oh, then go Vassar.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, then go Vassar.",
        "response":"Uh, they're not in it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, then go Vassar.",
        "response":"Uh, they're not in it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, they're not in it.",
        "response":"Ok, then just go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, they're not in it.",
        "response":"Ok, then just go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, then just go.",
        "response":"Ok. [leaves]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, then just go.",
        "response":"Ok. [leaves]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line33\"></a> RACHEL: Yes, but I, I think about who's apartment we're gonna sleepat tomorrow night and, and where we're gonna have dinner next Saturday night. I do notthink about what our childrens' names are gonna be. You know what our childrens names aregonna be.",
        "response":"No, no, I mean, ya know, I, I read a book and there was a girl named Emily and Ithought, I thought that might be good.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know, you tell me. One minute I'm holding Ben like a football, the nextthing I know, I've got two kids, I'm living in Scarsdale complaining about the taxes.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line32\"></a> ROSS: Well I'm sorry, I think about stuff. Ya know, I mean, you'reat work, you're assembling bones, your mind wanders.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"C'mon, what, you never think about our future?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line33\"></a> RACHEL: Yes, but I, I think about who's apartment we're gonna sleepat tomorrow night and, and where we're gonna have dinner next Saturday night. I do notthink about what our childrens' names are gonna be. You know what our childrens names aregonna be.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line32\"></a> ROSS: Well I'm sorry, I think about stuff. Ya know, I mean, you'reat work, you're assembling bones, your mind wanders.",
        "response":"Ross, you have planned out the next 20 years of our lives, we've been dating forsix weeks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line30\"></a> MONICA: It's just that he doesn't have that much free time, ya know,and I don't know, what do I do?",
        "response":"Does it matter? You're ultimately just gonna die or get divorced or have to blowyour pets head off.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Does it matter? You're ultimately just gonna die or get divorced or have to blowyour pets head off.",
        "response":"[enters] Aghh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, no, I mean, ya know, I, I read a book and there was a girl named Emily and Ithought, I thought that might be good.",
        "response":"What was the book?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What was the book?",
        "response":"The big book of childrens' names.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[enters] Aghh.",
        "response":"Me too. [leaves]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But I do not want to have everything decided for me. I spent my whole life likethat. It's what I had with Barry, that was one of the reasons I left. I, I like notknowing right now and I'm sorry if that scares you but if you want to be with me you aregonna have to deal with that.",
        "response":"Ok fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But I do not want to have everything decided for me. I spent my whole life likethat. It's what I had with Barry, that was one of the reasons I left. I, I like notknowing right now and I'm sorry if that scares you but if you want to be with me you aregonna have to deal with that.",
        "response":"Ok fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"But I do not want to have everything decided for me. I spent my whole life likethat. It's what I had with Barry, that was one of the reasons I left. I, I like notknowing right now and I'm sorry if that scares you but if you want to be with me you aregonna have to deal with that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"But I do not want to have everything decided for me. I spent my whole life likethat. It's what I had with Barry, that was one of the reasons I left. I, I like notknowing right now and I'm sorry if that scares you but if you want to be with me you aregonna have to deal with that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The big book of childrens' names.",
        "response":"Ok, Ross, Ross, ok listen, what we have is amazing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"The big book of childrens' names.",
        "response":"Ok, Ross, Ross, ok listen, what we have is amazing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, Ross, Ross, ok listen, what we have is amazing.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, Ross, Ross, ok listen, what we have is amazing.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What was the book?",
        "response":"The big book of childrens' names.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I didn't know that.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line34\"></a> ROSS: Ok, then you're gonna have to understand that you're with aguy who's not gonna stop planning his future with you because he knows that we're gonnaend up together and if that scares you, tough, 'cause you're gonna have to deal with that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line34\"></a> ROSS: Ok, then you're gonna have to understand that you're with aguy who's not gonna stop planning his future with you because he knows that we're gonnaend up together and if that scares you, tough, 'cause you're gonna have to deal with that.",
        "response":"Fine, I will.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Fine, I will.",
        "response":"Good, 'cause I love you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Good, 'cause I love you.",
        "response":"Oh yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We're not done.",
        "response":"I didn't know that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thank you.",
        "response":"We're not done.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thank you.",
        "response":"We're not done.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok fine.",
        "response":"Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok fine.",
        "response":"Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well I love you too.",
        "response":"Well that's the first time we've said that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well I love you too.",
        "response":"Well that's the first time we've said that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well that's the first time we've said that.",
        "response":"Yes it is.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well that's the first time we've said that.",
        "response":"Yes it is.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Good, 'cause I love you.",
        "response":"Oh yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Well I love you too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Well I love you too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah. You know, I don't know if I was happier when um George Bailey destroyedthe family business or um, Donna Reid cried, or when the mean pharmacist made his earbleed.",
        "response":"Alright, I'll give you the ear thing but don't you think the ending was prettywonderful?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did you like it?",
        "response":"Oh yeah. You know, I don't know if I was happier when um George Bailey destroyedthe family business or um, Donna Reid cried, or when the mean pharmacist made his earbleed.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[enters] Honey. Uh, not to sound too Florence Henderson but, dinner's on thetable.",
        "response":"Ok, just one more point.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, just one more point.",
        "response":"[grabs the other two bars on Richard's side and scores] Score! Now can we go?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I'm gonna kiss you.",
        "response":"Well you better.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes it is.",
        "response":"Well, I'm gonna kiss you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes it is.",
        "response":"Well, I'm gonna kiss you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Is everything all right?",
        "response":"Um-hmm.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um-hmm.",
        "response":"Uh-oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line40\"></a> JOEY: No no, seriously, Chandler and I were just talkin about this.He is so much cooler than our dads. [Chandler starts kicking him below the table] I mean,you know, our dad's are ok, ya know, but Richard is just- ow, ow. What are you kickin mefor? Huh? I'm tryin to talk here.",
        "response":"Uh, you guys see me as a dad?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line40\"></a> JOEY: No no, seriously, Chandler and I were just talkin about this.He is so much cooler than our dads. [Chandler starts kicking him below the table] I mean,you know, our dad's are ok, ya know, but Richard is just- ow, ow. What are you kickin mefor? Huh? I'm tryin to talk here.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No no, seriously, Joey's my dad, Monica's my dad. I've even got some dads downat work.",
        "response":"That's fine. Well, your other dad and I are gonna go have a romantic evening andI guess I'll just see you kids around.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[her and Richard return to her place] So are you ok?",
        "response":"Yeah, just, I feel like I'm about a hundred. I thought I was just one of theguys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Not a dad.",
        "response":"I can't believe you got us into trouble. [slaps Joey on the arm. Joey takesexception and slaps him back]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh, yeah.",
        "response":"No no, seriously, Joey's my dad, Monica's my dad. I've even got some dads downat work.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're not a dad. You're not a dad.",
        "response":"Not a dad.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Nooooo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, just, I feel like I'm about a hundred. I thought I was just one of theguys.",
        "response":"Come here. I'll make you feel like one of the guys. You know for a really coolguy, you suck at foosball.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, just, I feel like I'm about a hundred. I thought I was just one of theguys.",
        "response":"Come here. I'll make you feel like one of the guys. You know for a really coolguy, you suck at foosball.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Come here. I'll make you feel like one of the guys. You know for a really coolguy, you suck at foosball.",
        "response":"What're you talkin' about, I was killin' 'em.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Come here. I'll make you feel like one of the guys. You know for a really coolguy, you suck at foosball.",
        "response":"What're you talkin' about, I was killin' 'em.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, we can do this now, can't we Ben? Yes we can, yes we can. [finishes thediaper] There. I did it. I did it. Look at that, oh, stays on and everything. Hi.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"I'm sorry, what did you just say? Did you just say hi? Oh my God, Ross, Ross, Benjust said 'Hi'.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's us.",
        "response":"Come on up. I'm gonna get the rest of his stuff together. [walks in his room]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What're you talkin' about, I was killin' 'em.",
        "response":"Yeah, well they suck too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[doorbell buzzes] Hello.",
        "response":"It's us.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry, what did you just say? Did you just say hi? Oh my God, Ross, Ross, Benjust said 'Hi'.",
        "response":"Wha, what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Great, great, and I miss that too, I miss everything.",
        "response":"Oh, I'm sorry, I guess I just bring it out in him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I'm sorry, I guess I just bring it out in him.",
        "response":"CAROL and SUSAN: Hello.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"CAROL and SUSAN: Hello.",
        "response":"Guess what. Ben just said his first word.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ben just said hi.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line43\"></a> ROSS: What, the word hi?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line43\"></a> ROSS: What, the word hi?",
        "response":"Ye-, no, my Uncle Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ye-, no, my Uncle Hi.",
        "response":"Great, great, and I miss that too, I miss everything.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know, actually it's more like, hi.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wha, what?",
        "response":"Ben just said hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We've got a cab waiting downstairs.",
        "response":"Well, this was fun. Uh, we should really do it again sometime, wha'dya say? Ok.Alright so I've got him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, this was fun. Uh, we should really do it again sometime, wha'dya say? Ok.Alright so I've got him.",
        "response":"Tuesday.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, this was fun. Uh, we should really do it again sometime, wha'dya say? Ok.Alright so I've got him.",
        "response":"Tuesday.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, this could go on for a while.",
        "response":"We've got a cab waiting downstairs.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Tuesday right. Ok, bye you guys.",
        "response":"Take care.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Tuesday.",
        "response":"Tuesday right. Ok, bye you guys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Ok, this could go on for a while.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, alright, ok. Bye.",
        "response":"Bye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Take care.",
        "response":"Bye Ben.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Bye.",
        "response":"Bye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Bye.",
        "response":"Bye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Bye.",
        "response":"Bye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Bye.",
        "response":"Bye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Bye.",
        "response":"Bye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Bye.",
        "response":"Bye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Bye.",
        "response":"Bye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And they were serving franks which is his first name minus the s at the end. Andthere was a rotisserie with spinning chicken.",
        "response":"His indian name?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"His indian name?",
        "response":"No because I chickened out the last time when I tried to meet him. So I meancoincidences? I don't think so.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah.",
        "response":"Hey, you just wanna forget about raquetball and hang out here?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why?",
        "response":"Hamburger. McDonald's. Old MacDonald had a farm, my dad is a pharmacist.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, alright, that's it, now I have to go see him.",
        "response":"Why?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Freaky.",
        "response":"Weird, weird.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow.",
        "response":"Freaky.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Bye.",
        "response":"Bye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Bye.",
        "response":"Bye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"BIG BULLY: Why should we?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line09\"></a>Because it's a special hat. [Chandler looks at Ross funny] Seehe bought it 'cause he was feeling really down one day so he got the hat to cheer himselfup, ya know. Now Chandler...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, ok, you know what? I think you're very funny. Kudos on that hat joke. But, comeon guy just, just give him back the hat.",
        "response":"BIG BULLY: Why should we?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"LITTLE BULLY: I just took your hat. See, I can be funny too. My, my joke is that I, I tookyour hat.",
        "response":"That, that is funny. Can I have it back?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What just happened?",
        "response":"LITTLE BULLY: I just took your hat. See, I can be funny too. My, my joke is that I, I tookyour hat.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, there is one more way to say it, who knows it?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line07\"></a> LITTLE BULLY: Is that supposed to be funny?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line07\"></a> LITTLE BULLY: Is that supposed to be funny?",
        "response":"No actually, I was just going for colorful.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, you just wanna forget about raquetball and hang out here?",
        "response":"Yeah alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That, that is funny. Can I have it back?",
        "response":"LITTLE BULLY: No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"LITTLE BULLY: No.",
        "response":"No?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, how'd the interview go?",
        "response":"It bit. It was a 50's theme restraunt. I have to cook in a costume and dance onthe counter. <a name=\"line10\"></a>I mean I was a chef at Cafe des Artistes. I mean howcould I take a job where I have to make something called Laverne and Curly Fries?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It bit. It was a 50's theme restraunt. I have to cook in a costume and dance onthe counter. <a name=\"line10\"></a>I mean I was a chef at Cafe des Artistes. I mean howcould I take a job where I have to make something called Laverne and Curly Fries?",
        "response":"So don't do it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It bit. It was a 50's theme restraunt. I have to cook in a costume and dance onthe counter. <a name=\"line10\"></a>I mean I was a chef at Cafe des Artistes. I mean howcould I take a job where I have to make something called Laverne and Curly Fries?",
        "response":"So don't do it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Stop talking, stop talking now. Let me just get this straight. You're actuallystealing my hat?",
        "response":"BIG BULLY: You got a problem with that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How can I not do it? I have $127 in the bank.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line11\"></a> JOEY: Monica, relax, go get a beer.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's the matter with you?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line12\"></a> CHANDLER: The mean guys at the coffee house took my hat.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"BIG BULLY: You got a problem with that?",
        "response":"No, just wanna make sure we're on the same page.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line11\"></a> JOEY: Monica, relax, go get a beer.",
        "response":"I don't want a beer.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So don't do it.",
        "response":"How can I not do it? I have $127 in the bank.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"My stock, MEG, it went up 2 points. Hey guys, do you realize that if I hadinvested my $127 in myself yesterday that I'd like have...a lot more than that today. Yaknow what, I'm gonna do it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It was ridiculous. Ya know, these guys, they were bullies, actual bullies, ya know. <aname=\"line13\"></a> We're grown ups, this kinda stuff isn't supposed to happen anymore.",
        "response":"Oohhh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohhh [turns as if to hug someone] Oh no, wait a minute, I have no one.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line42\"></a> JOEY: Hey, woah, let's go down there and get your hat back.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line42\"></a> JOEY: Hey, woah, let's go down there and get your hat back.",
        "response":"Na, forget it, it's probably stripped and sold for parts by now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line12\"></a> CHANDLER: The mean guys at the coffee house took my hat.",
        "response":"Noo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Hi. [Ross turns to Rachel and they hug]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[seeing TV] Hey, I went up.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oohhh.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oohhh.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"My stock, MEG, it went up 2 points. Hey guys, do you realize that if I hadinvested my $127 in myself yesterday that I'd like have...a lot more than that today. Yaknow what, I'm gonna do it.",
        "response":"Do what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, hey, hey no.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line17\"></a> RACHEL: Ok, doggie get the- aahhh. Ok go get the sandwich, get thesandwich doggie. [dog ignores the sandwich] Good doggie get the sandwich, get the...ok,Joey, the dog will lick himself but he will not touch your sandwich, what does that say?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well why don't you just reach out and take his trampoline.",
        "response":"Ok, here, I know what we can do. [grabs Joey's sadwich and throws it out thewindow]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, here, I know what we can do. [grabs Joey's sadwich and throws it out thewindow]",
        "response":"Hey, hey, hey no.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No no, 'cause mayo, that would make it gross.",
        "response":"[a little dog starts attacking her leg] Hey, hey, no, oh oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Olive loaf and ham spread, no mayo.",
        "response":"No no, 'cause mayo, that would make it gross.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[a little dog starts attacking her leg] Hey, hey, no, oh oh.",
        "response":"Run Phoebe run.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohh, what is in that?",
        "response":"Olive loaf and ham spread, no mayo.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Do what?",
        "response":"Put all my money in me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line17\"></a> RACHEL: Ok, doggie get the- aahhh. Ok go get the sandwich, get thesandwich doggie. [dog ignores the sandwich] Good doggie get the sandwich, get the...ok,Joey, the dog will lick himself but he will not touch your sandwich, what does that say?",
        "response":"Well if he's not gonna eat it, I will.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line18\"></a> CHANDLER: Do you have to be a Century 21 real-estate agent to get towear those really cool jackets?",
        "response":"Do you say this stuff to girls?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line18\"></a> CHANDLER: Do you have to be a Century 21 real-estate agent to get towear those really cool jackets?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well pal, you didn't give me much of a choice. [flicks the ends of the big bully'stie]",
        "response":"Don't play with his things.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you crazy?",
        "response":"Phoebs, he's just a little dog. [turns back to the car window and the dog is halfwaythrough it.] Ahhh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line21\"></a> BIG BULLY: Alright, let's take this outside.",
        "response":"Let's, let's take this outside? Who talks like that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line21\"></a> BIG BULLY: Alright, let's take this outside.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well if he's not gonna eat it, I will.",
        "response":"Are you crazy?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Don't play with his things.",
        "response":"I know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I just think that this was a really bad sign, ya know. I mean, like the beast atthe threshold, you know. It's just like, I have no family left, ya know. I mean except formy grandmother, you know, but let's face it, she's not gonna be around forever, despitewhat she says. And I have a sister who I've barely spoken to since we like shared a womb.I don't know, this is my real father and I just, I want things to be like just right.",
        "response":"Yeah Phoebe, I completely understand.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's the matter?",
        "response":"I just think that this was a really bad sign, ya know. I mean, like the beast atthe threshold, you know. It's just like, I have no family left, ya know. I mean except formy grandmother, you know, but let's face it, she's not gonna be around forever, despitewhat she says. And I have a sister who I've barely spoken to since we like shared a womb.I don't know, this is my real father and I just, I want things to be like just right.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's the matter?",
        "response":"I just think that this was a really bad sign, ya know. I mean, like the beast atthe threshold, you know. It's just like, I have no family left, ya know. I mean except formy grandmother, you know, but let's face it, she's not gonna be around forever, despitewhat she says. And I have a sister who I've barely spoken to since we like shared a womb.I don't know, this is my real father and I just, I want things to be like just right.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, you missed, 'Takes money to make money,' and uh, 'Don't make me come downthere and kick your wall street butt.'",
        "response":"<a name=\"line25\"></a> MONICA: Hey, I made $17 before breakfast, what have you done?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line25\"></a> MONICA: Hey, I made $17 before breakfast, what have you done?",
        "response":"Well uh, I had breakfast here so technically I saved $3.50.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, my financially challenged friends, <a name=\"line44\"></a> I split my moneyand I bought some shares of CHP and ZXY.",
        "response":"How come those?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How come those?",
        "response":"Well, CHP because I used to have a crush on Eric Estrada. And ZXY becuase I thinkit sounds zexy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[enters] Hey.",
        "response":"Hey Phoebs. Oh hey, how's the dog?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I don't know.",
        "response":"What's the matter?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line31\"></a> ROSS: No. Man I don't wanna have to have Joey with me every time Iwanna descent cup of coffee. Ya know, and I don't wanna spend the rest of my life drinkingcappucino with a 'K'. I say you and I go back down there and stand up to those guys.",
        "response":"Alright, hang on a second there Custer.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line27\"></a> PHOEBE: Yeah, but he did have to have a bunch of stitches and hesaid that only once in a blue moon does a dog's ear grow back so...still hoping.",
        "response":"Ok, so Phoebe, now are you gonna call your dad and let him know that his dog isok?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I, I don't wanna meet my father over the phone. <a name=\"line45\"></a> What am Igonna say, like 'Hi, I'm Phoebe, the daughter you abandoned. Oh, by the way, I broke yourdog.'",
        "response":"Hey Phoebs, if you want, I'll do it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line31\"></a> ROSS: No. Man I don't wanna have to have Joey with me every time Iwanna descent cup of coffee. Ya know, and I don't wanna spend the rest of my life drinkingcappucino with a 'K'. I say you and I go back down there and stand up to those guys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, thank God.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line27\"></a> PHOEBE: Yeah, but he did have to have a bunch of stitches and hesaid that only once in a blue moon does a dog's ear grow back so...still hoping.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Phoebs. Oh hey, how's the dog?",
        "response":"Ok, I talked to the vet, people are so nice upstate. Anyway, he said that thelittle fella's gonna be ok and I can pick him up tomorrow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Phoebs, if you want, I'll do it.",
        "response":"Ok. Listen, just don't say anything about me, ok. [goes over and grabs the phonethat's sitting by Monica]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"No?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi, welcome home. [pulls Rachel inside] I need to borrow a hundred bucks.",
        "response":"For what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi, welcome home. [pulls Rachel inside] I need to borrow a hundred bucks.",
        "response":"For what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Hi, welcome home. [pulls Rachel inside] I need to borrow a hundred bucks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Hi, welcome home. [pulls Rachel inside] I need to borrow a hundred bucks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah really, Ross, have you ever been beaten up before?",
        "response":"Yeah, sure.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Opens the door] I need to borrow a hundred bucks.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"For what?",
        "response":"I've gotta get back in the game.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"For what?",
        "response":"I've gotta get back in the game.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, sure.",
        "response":"By someone besides Monica?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, I've come to terms with it, you have to too.",
        "response":"Ok. Look uhh, Mon I'm, I'm really sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why, when did you get out of the game?",
        "response":"I don't know, I lost it all ok. I lost it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why, when did you get out of the game?",
        "response":"I don't know, I lost it all ok. I lost it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I've gotta get back in the game.",
        "response":"Why, when did you get out of the game?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I've gotta get back in the game.",
        "response":"Why, when did you get out of the game?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh no.",
        "response":"Hey, I've come to terms with it, you have to too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh no.",
        "response":"Hey, I've come to terms with it, you have to too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know, I lost it all ok. I lost it.",
        "response":"Oh no.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know, I lost it all ok. I lost it.",
        "response":"Oh no.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line33\"></a> MONICA: But I need it. Otherwords I'm gonna have to take thathorrible diner job. You know, with the dancing and the costumes. I don't wanna have towear flame retardant boobs.",
        "response":"Nobody does honey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I, I don't have it.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line33\"></a> MONICA: But I need it. Otherwords I'm gonna have to take thathorrible diner job. You know, with the dancing and the costumes. I don't wanna have towear flame retardant boobs.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line34\"></a> MRS BUFFAY: Schnoodle. Oh my God, what the hell happened to my dog?",
        "response":"It was an accident, and, and the woman who did this would never ever hurt a dog onpurpose. She's a vegetarian.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It was an accident, and, and the woman who did this would never ever hurt a dog onpurpose. She's a vegetarian.",
        "response":"MRS BUFFAY: What are these, stitches?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line34\"></a> MRS BUFFAY: Schnoodle. Oh my God, what the hell happened to my dog?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, I've come to terms with it, you have to too.",
        "response":"Ok. Look uhh, Mon I'm, I'm really sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok. Look uhh, Mon I'm, I'm really sorry.",
        "response":"Yeah, yeah, yeah, where are we on the hundred bucks?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok. Look uhh, Mon I'm, I'm really sorry.",
        "response":"Yeah, yeah, yeah, where are we on the hundred bucks?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, yeah, yeah, where are we on the hundred bucks?",
        "response":"I, I don't have it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, eight of them. That's 56 to him. You know also, if, if it's raining, youcan't let him look up too long 'cause that cone'll fill up really really fast.",
        "response":"MRS BUFFAY: Yeah well, thanks for bringing back what's left of him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS BUFFAY: What are these, stitches?",
        "response":"Yeah, eight of them. That's 56 to him. You know also, if, if it's raining, youcan't let him look up too long 'cause that cone'll fill up really really fast.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS BUFFAY: Well he left four years ago so we're expecting him back any minute now.",
        "response":"Alright, I'm, I'm gonna go. I'm sorry about the dog, everything. I'm sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey lady. Hey wait up. How do you know my dad?",
        "response":"Um well I don't really. Just genetically. He's kinda my dad too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok so will he be back soon?",
        "response":"MRS BUFFAY: Well he left four years ago so we're expecting him back any minute now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS BUFFAY: Yeah well, thanks for bringing back what's left of him.",
        "response":"Sure, oh, is, is Frank home.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS BUFFAY: How do you know Frank?",
        "response":"Just from a, from a long time ago. Is he here?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um well I don't really. Just genetically. He's kinda my dad too.",
        "response":"Heavy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sure, oh, is, is Frank home.",
        "response":"MRS BUFFAY: How do you know Frank?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. So um, did he ever talk about me, Phoebe?",
        "response":"No but he didn't really talk about anything.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. So um, did he ever talk about me, Phoebe?",
        "response":"No but he didn't really talk about anything.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Um well I don't really. Just genetically. He's kinda my dad too.",
        "response":"Heavy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Heavy.",
        "response":"Yeah. So um, did he ever talk about me, Phoebe?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Heavy.",
        "response":"Yeah. So um, did he ever talk about me, Phoebe?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No but he didn't really talk about anything.",
        "response":"Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No but he didn't really talk about anything.",
        "response":"Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh.",
        "response":"Except stilts.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh.",
        "response":"Except stilts.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Stilts?",
        "response":"Yeah, he loved stilts. One time I was upstairs, I was stealing cigarettes out of mymom's purse, and uh, all of a sudden I look over and there's my dad's head bobbing pastthe window. He just had this big smile on his face and he was waving 'cause he was alwayshappiest when he was on his stilts.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Stilts?",
        "response":"Yeah, he loved stilts. One time I was upstairs, I was stealing cigarettes out of mymom's purse, and uh, all of a sudden I look over and there's my dad's head bobbing pastthe window. He just had this big smile on his face and he was waving 'cause he was alwayshappiest when he was on his stilts.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, he loved stilts. One time I was upstairs, I was stealing cigarettes out of mymom's purse, and uh, all of a sudden I look over and there's my dad's head bobbing pastthe window. He just had this big smile on his face and he was waving 'cause he was alwayshappiest when he was on his stilts.",
        "response":"Wow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, he loved stilts. One time I was upstairs, I was stealing cigarettes out of mymom's purse, and uh, all of a sudden I look over and there's my dad's head bobbing pastthe window. He just had this big smile on his face and he was waving 'cause he was alwayshappiest when he was on his stilts.",
        "response":"Wow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"I don't know what to do with that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Except stilts.",
        "response":"Stilts?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Except stilts.",
        "response":"Stilts?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This is huge, you can buy me beer.",
        "response":"I'm not gonna. But you know what's cool though? Ok, if you had a friend namedPete, then I could say, 'Oh yeah, I know Pete, he's friends with my brother.'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This is huge, you can buy me beer.",
        "response":"I'm not gonna. But you know what's cool though? Ok, if you had a friend namedPete, then I could say, 'Oh yeah, I know Pete, he's friends with my brother.'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm not gonna. But you know what's cool though? Ok, if you had a friend namedPete, then I could say, 'Oh yeah, I know Pete, he's friends with my brother.'",
        "response":"I gotta friend named Mark.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm not gonna. But you know what's cool though? Ok, if you had a friend namedPete, then I could say, 'Oh yeah, I know Pete, he's friends with my brother.'",
        "response":"I gotta friend named Mark.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't know what to do with that.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line36\"></a> FRANK: Me neither. So you're like my big sister.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line36\"></a> FRANK: Me neither. So you're like my big sister.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I gotta friend named Mark.",
        "response":"That'll work too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I gotta friend named Mark.",
        "response":"That'll work too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"This is huge, you can buy me beer.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That'll work too.",
        "response":"Cool, alright. So maybe, ya know, I could give you a call sometime, we could talkor somethin'.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That'll work too.",
        "response":"Cool, alright. So maybe, ya know, I could give you a call sometime, we could talkor somethin'.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Cool, alright. So maybe, ya know, I could give you a call sometime, we could talkor somethin'.",
        "response":"Yeah, that'd be ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Cool, alright. So maybe, ya know, I could give you a call sometime, we could talkor somethin'.",
        "response":"Yeah, that'd be ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, that'd be ok.",
        "response":"Alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, that'd be ok.",
        "response":"Alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright.",
        "response":"Ok, I'm in the book.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright.",
        "response":"Ok, I'm in the book.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, I'm in the book.",
        "response":"Ok, yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright. So um, stilts huh?",
        "response":"Yeah hey, you know if you want I can take you around back and show you where he hithis head on the rain gutter.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright. So um, stilts huh?",
        "response":"Yeah hey, you know if you want I can take you around back and show you where he hithis head on the rain gutter.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Would you come on! Come on! [waitress brings their coffee] Thank you.",
        "response":"[They rush to put the cream and sugar in their cups and gulp down a few drinks]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah hey, you know if you want I can take you around back and show you where he hithis head on the rain gutter.",
        "response":"Ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[They rush to put the cream and sugar in their cups and gulp down a few drinks]",
        "response":"Ah, there we go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ah, there we go.",
        "response":"I think we proved our point.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, yeah.",
        "response":"Alright. So um, stilts huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, yeah.",
        "response":"Alright. So um, stilts huh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, I'm in the book.",
        "response":"Ok, yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, it's sharp, it's metal, I think I can do some, you know, serious damagewith it.",
        "response":"BIG BULLY: No, you can't use your watch.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Whad'ya mean?",
        "response":"Well, it's sharp, it's metal, I think I can do some, you know, serious damagewith it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Question. If I don't care about my watch, can I use it as a weapon?",
        "response":"Whad'ya mean?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"BIG BULLY: No, you can't use your watch.",
        "response":"Ok. [reaches in his pocket]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I think we proved our point.",
        "response":"You burn your mouth?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I think we proved our point.",
        "response":"You burn your mouth?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You burn your mouth?",
        "response":"Cannot feel my tounge.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok. [reaches in his pocket]",
        "response":"BIG BULLY: Or your keys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"BIG BULLY: Or your keys.",
        "response":"Ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, I'll get candles and my mom's lace tablecloth, and since it's Rachel'sbirthday, I mean, we want it to be special, I thought I'd poach a salmon.",
        "response":"Ohhh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, hey, woah, you want some of this, huh? You want a piece of this, huh? I'mstandin here, huh.",
        "response":"Hey, hey, those guys are takin our stuff! [some guy runs off with the hat]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"BIG BULLY: Of course we're hitting faces, why wouldn't you hit faces?",
        "response":"Well because I have to work on Monday, I have a big presentation.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Before I forget, are we hitting faces?",
        "response":"BIG BULLY: Of course we're hitting faces, why wouldn't you hit faces?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"LITTLE BULLY: No.",
        "response":"Huh. [reaches over and grabs the hat and bolts for the door but slips and fallsbehind the couch]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, hey, those guys are takin our stuff! [some guy runs off with the hat]",
        "response":"Hey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, listen guys, are we uh, are we ok here?",
        "response":"LITTLE BULLY: We're ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok so, can I have my hat back?",
        "response":"LITTLE BULLY: No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"LITTLE BULLY: We're ok.",
        "response":"Alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. GREENE: What? The father can't drop by to see the daughter on her birthday?",
        "response":"No no, the father can, but um, since I am the roommate I can tell you that she'snot here and I'll pass along the message, ok. So bye-bye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[answers the door] Dr. Greene. Oh my God it's Rachel's dad. What're you doinghere?",
        "response":"MR. GREENE: What? The father can't drop by to see the daughter on her birthday?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line01\"></a> ROSS: Question. Why do we always have to have parties where youpoach things?",
        "response":"You wanna be in charge of the food committee?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Question two. Why do we always have to have parties with committees?",
        "response":"Really. Why can't we just get some pizzas and get some beers and have fun?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line01\"></a> ROSS: Question. Why do we always have to have parties where youpoach things?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really. Why can't we just get some pizzas and get some beers and have fun?",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, how bout just her mom?",
        "response":"Why her mom?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why her mom?",
        "response":"Cause I already invited her.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohhh.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright you guys are off to party number one [ushers 3 guys into Monica'sapartment] and you, you are off to party number two [ushers four women into his apartment.Two guys try to follow and Chandler blocks them and shoos them off to Monica's apartment]Alright fellas, let's keep it movin', let' keep it movin.",
        "response":"Chandler could you at least send some women to my party? [buzzer goes off] Alrightthat's Ross.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, this more than anything else, is the staging area.",
        "response":"[as they're walking out, Dr. Greene questioningly gestures at the Happy Birthdaysign over the door] This is clearly in the wrong apartment. [they all walk across thehall]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chandler could you at least send some women to my party? [buzzer goes off] Alrightthat's Ross.",
        "response":"Ok, they're coming, shhh. [Runs into Monica's apartment and grabs one last girlto take to his apartment]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No no, the father can, but um, since I am the roommate I can tell you that she'snot here and I'll pass along the message, ok. So bye-bye.",
        "response":"MR. GREENE: Ohhh, you're having a parteee.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. GREENE: Ohhh, you're having a parteee.",
        "response":"No, no, not a party. Just a surprise gathering of some people Rachel knows. Um,this is Phoebe and Chandler and Joey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So uh, Joey and Chanlder, I, I think it's time that you take Dr. Greene over toyour place.",
        "response":"Uhh, yes, absdolutely, um. Why again?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thanks for being born.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line14\"></a> RACHEL: Ohh, thank you for my beautiul earrings, they're perfect. Ilove you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uhh, yes, absdolutely, um. Why again?",
        "response":"Because that's where the party is you goon. See this is just the staging area.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right this is staging.",
        "response":"Yeah, this more than anything else, is the staging area.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line14\"></a> RACHEL: Ohh, thank you for my beautiul earrings, they're perfect. Ilove you.",
        "response":"Oh, now you can exchange them if you want, ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my gosh, wow. Monica. Oh my god. Mom. This is so great.",
        "response":"MRS. GREENE: Happy birthday sweetie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right.",
        "response":"Ok, everybody, there's food and drinks on the table. Go across the hall.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, everybody, there's food and drinks on the table. Go across the hall.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GREENE: Happy birthday sweetie.",
        "response":"Wow you, you. I had no idea.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow you, you. I had no idea.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, I knew.",
        "response":"All right.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"No, I knew.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"No, I knew.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't believe this is happening.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line16\"></a> ROSS: You know what, this is ridiculous, ok. This is your birthday,this is your party. I say we just put 'em all together and if they can't deal with it, whocares.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I have to be, I don't really have a choice, I mean, you know, I could lookat the bright side, I get two birthday parties and two birthday cakes.",
        "response":"Well, actually just one birthday flan.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I have to be, I don't really have a choice, I mean, you know, I could lookat the bright side, I get two birthday parties and two birthday cakes.",
        "response":"Well, actually just one birthday flan.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line16\"></a> ROSS: You know what, this is ridiculous, ok. This is your birthday,this is your party. I say we just put 'em all together and if they can't deal with it, whocares.",
        "response":"I do.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look, are you gonna be ok?",
        "response":"Well, I have to be, I don't really have a choice, I mean, you know, I could lookat the bright side, I get two birthday parties and two birthday cakes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Right now, Joey and Chandler's, go now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right now, Joey and Chandler's, go now.",
        "response":"Why.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Right now, Joey and Chandler's, go now.",
        "response":"Why.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why.",
        "response":"Just go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line17\"></a> JOEY: Yeah, we set up a court in your room. Uh, you didn't reallylike that grey lamp, did you?",
        "response":"Joey, a woman just stuck her tounge down my throat, I'm not even listening toyou.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<b>[Time lapse. Chandler runs out of the bathroom.]</b>",
        "response":"Joey, Joey. Hey, some girl just walked up to me and said, 'I want you Dennis,'and stuck her tounge down my throat. I love this party.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey, Joey. Hey, some girl just walked up to me and said, 'I want you Dennis,'and stuck her tounge down my throat. I love this party.",
        "response":"Quick volleyball question.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's a traditional Mexican custard dessert...Look talk to Monica, she's on thefood committee.",
        "response":"<b>[Time lapse. Chandler runs out of the bathroom.]</b>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Volleyball.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line17\"></a> JOEY: Yeah, we set up a court in your room. Uh, you didn't reallylike that grey lamp, did you?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"It's a traditional Mexican custard dessert...Look talk to Monica, she's on thefood committee.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, actually just one birthday flan.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, actually just one birthday flan.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Quick volleyball question.",
        "response":"Volleyball.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Listen you guys, I don't mean to be a pain about this but, um, I've noticed thatsome of you are just placing them on. You wanna push the caps until you hear them click.[she demonstrates, Gunther starts to walk to the door] Gunther, where're you going?",
        "response":"I um, was sorta thinking about maybe...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line18\"></a> ROSS: Ok, do you have any ideas for any openers?",
        "response":"Uhh, let's just stay clear of 'I'm the guy that's doing you daughter' and youshould be ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Listen honey, can you keep dad occupied, I'm gonna go talk to mom for a while.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line18\"></a> ROSS: Ok, do you have any ideas for any openers?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I um, was sorta thinking about maybe...",
        "response":"No. No you can't go. No this is fun. Come on we're just getting started. Here,here's your marker.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey, a woman just stuck her tounge down my throat, I'm not even listening toyou.",
        "response":"GIRL'S VOICE: Dennis.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, she'll yell at me again.",
        "response":"Alright, I can get you out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Listen if you wanna go, just go.",
        "response":"No, she'll yell at me again.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"GIRL'S VOICE: Dennis.",
        "response":"Ok, that's me. [runs back]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, I can get you out.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GREENE: Oh, scotch neat. Ya know, that's Rachel's father's drink.",
        "response":"Oh, mine too. Isn't that neat, scotch neat. Would you excuse me? [walks out in thehallway, Mr. Greene is walking out of Chandler and Joey's apartment] Hey, hey, where youuh, sneakin off to mister?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi. Uh, I have been in the bathroom. Stay clear of the salmon mousse.",
        "response":"MRS. GREENE: Oh, scotch neat. Ya know, that's Rachel's father's drink.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Shh. In a minute, I'm gonna create a diversion. When I do, walk quickly to thedoor and don't look back.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. GREENE: Scotch.",
        "response":"Scotch. Alright, I'll be back in 10 seconds with your scotch on the rocks in aglass.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Scotch. Alright, I'll be back in 10 seconds with your scotch on the rocks in aglass.",
        "response":"MR. GREENE: Neat.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, here, I, I'll get it for ya. Whad'ya want?",
        "response":"MR. GREENE: Scotch.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. GREENE: No no no, no no no, neat, as in no rocks.",
        "response":"I know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Cool.",
        "response":"MR. GREENE: No no no, no no no, neat, as in no rocks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. GREENE: Neat.",
        "response":"Cool.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, mine too. Isn't that neat, scotch neat. Would you excuse me? [walks out in thehallway, Mr. Greene is walking out of Chandler and Joey's apartment] Hey, hey, where youuh, sneakin off to mister?",
        "response":"MR. GREENE: I'm getting my cigarettes out of my jacket.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, um, see 'cause that, that is, that is the staging area. If you go in there,it'll ruin the whole illusion of the party. Yeah, I think you take your scotch back inthere and I will get your cigarettes for you sir.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line20\"></a> MR. GREENE: Get my glasses too.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. GREENE: Whad'ya mean no?",
        "response":"No, um, see 'cause that, that is, that is the staging area. If you go in there,it'll ruin the whole illusion of the party. Yeah, I think you take your scotch back inthere and I will get your cigarettes for you sir.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, the first person's most embarassing memory is, 'Monica, your party sucks.'Very funny.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line21\"></a> PHOEBE: Oh no, ooh, ooh, did somebody forget to use a coaster?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line21\"></a> PHOEBE: Oh no, ooh, ooh, did somebody forget to use a coaster?",
        "response":"What? [she runs over to where Phoebe is, Phoebe signals for Gunther to go] I don'tsee anything.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line20\"></a> MR. GREENE: Get my glasses too.",
        "response":"All righty roo. [closes the door] What a great moment to say that for the firsttime. [goes to get the cigarettes and glasses]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Mine.",
        "response":"MRS. GREENE: You wear bi-focals?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. GREENE: I'm getting my cigarettes out of my jacket.",
        "response":"No. no.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. no.",
        "response":"MR. GREENE: Whad'ya mean no?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohh, big smoker. [Packs the cigarettes and flings one on Mrs. Greene in the process.Finally gets one in his mouth and it look really out of place] Big big smoker. In fact I'mgonna go ou into the hallway and fire up this bad boy. [as he walks into the hall, hecomes face to face with Mr. Greene]",
        "response":"<a name=\"line22\"></a> MR. GREENE: Are you wearing my glasses?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. GREENE: Thank you. Is that one of my cigarettes?",
        "response":"[pulls the cigarette off his upper lip and hands it to Mr. Greene] Yeah, yes it is,I was just moistening the tip.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line22\"></a> MR. GREENE: Are you wearing my glasses?",
        "response":"Yes. [pulls them off and hands them to Mr. Greene] I was just warming up theearpieces for you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yes. [pulls them off and hands them to Mr. Greene] I was just warming up theearpieces for you.",
        "response":"MR. GREENE: Thank you. Is that one of my cigarettes?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"GIRL 1: Alright, let me just get my coat.",
        "response":"There isn't time. You must leave everything. They'll take care of you next door.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GREENE: You wear bi-focals?",
        "response":"Um-hmm. [puts them on] I have a condition, apparently, that I require two differentsets of focals.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, only the three of you, any more than that and she'll get suspicious.",
        "response":"GIRL 1: Alright, let me just get my coat.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"There isn't time. You must leave everything. They'll take care of you next door.",
        "response":"GIRL 1: Is it true they have beer?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"GIRL 1: Is it true they have beer?",
        "response":"Everything you've heard is true.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[running out of his apartment after a girl] Ok, ok, you can be shirts and I'llbe skins. I'll be skins. [sits down beside Rachel] Hey, how you holdin' up there, tiger?Oh, sorry, when my parents were getting divorced I got a lot of tigers. Got a lot ofchamps, chiefs, sports, I even got a governor.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line24\"></a> RACHEL: This is it, isn't it? I mean, this is what my life is gonnabe like. My mom there, my dad there. Thanksgiving, Christmas. She gets the house, he's insome condo my sister's gonna decorate with wicker. Oh, Chandler how did you get throughthis?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, I'm sorry but these people needed me. They work hard all week, it'sSaturday night, they deserve to have a little fun. Go.",
        "response":"Ya know, my party is fun. I mean, maybe it's a little quieter, less obvious sortafun but, you know, if people would just give it a chance... [volleyball hits her in thehead from behind]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GREENE: Sweetheart, you obviously have a problem. You've chosen a boyfriend exactlylike your father.",
        "response":"Ok mom, you know what, fine, I'll make an appointment ok, but you know what, rightnow, I gotta go, I gotta go do a thing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You want me to see a therapist?",
        "response":"MRS. GREENE: Sweetheart, you obviously have a problem. You've chosen a boyfriend exactlylike your father.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebe.",
        "response":"Alright, I'm sorry but these people needed me. They work hard all week, it'sSaturday night, they deserve to have a little fun. Go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Phoebe.",
        "response":"Alright, I'm sorry but these people needed me. They work hard all week, it'sSaturday night, they deserve to have a little fun. Go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Could you guys please try to keep it down, we're trying to start a Boggletournament.",
        "response":"[Chandler and Joey stop dancing and laugh at her]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Chandler and Joey stop dancing and laugh at her]",
        "response":"You, and you, you're supposed to be at my party. And Gunther! What are you doinghere?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[enters with the three people she got out] Ok, welcome to the fu-oh.",
        "response":"Phoebe.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Becasue it reminded you of the way our forefathers used to bitch at each other?",
        "response":"It's just this thing. Every year we would go out on my dad's boat and watch thefireworks. Mom always hated it because the ocean air made her hair all big. My sister Jillwould be throwing up over the side and my dad would be upset becasue nobody was helpingand then when we did help he would scream at us for doing it wrong. But then when thefireworks started, everybody just shut up, you know, and it'd get really cold, and wewould all just sort of smush under this one blanket. It never occured to anybody to bringanother one. And now it's just...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's just this thing. Every year we would go out on my dad's boat and watch thefireworks. Mom always hated it because the ocean air made her hair all big. My sister Jillwould be throwing up over the side and my dad would be upset becasue nobody was helpingand then when we did help he would scream at us for doing it wrong. But then when thefireworks started, everybody just shut up, you know, and it'd get really cold, and wewould all just sort of smush under this one blanket. It never occured to anybody to bringanother one. And now it's just...",
        "response":"I, I know. [Hugs her. Ross walks out and Chandler puts her in his arms.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line24\"></a> RACHEL: This is it, isn't it? I mean, this is what my life is gonnabe like. My mom there, my dad there. Thanksgiving, Christmas. She gets the house, he's insome condo my sister's gonna decorate with wicker. Oh, Chandler how did you get throughthis?",
        "response":"Well, I relied on a carefully regimented program of denial and, and wetting thebed.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I relied on a carefully regimented program of denial and, and wetting thebed.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line25\"></a> RACHEL: Ya know, I just, so weird. I mean I was in there justlistening to them bitch about each other and all I kept thinking about was the fourth ofJuly.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line25\"></a> RACHEL: Ya know, I just, so weird. I mean I was in there justlistening to them bitch about each other and all I kept thinking about was the fourth ofJuly.",
        "response":"Becasue it reminded you of the way our forefathers used to bitch at each other?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, thanks for coming, I hope you guys had fun.",
        "response":"MRS. GREENE: Alright, Monica dear, I'm gonna hit the road. Now I've left my 10 verbs onthe table. And you be sure and send me that finished poem.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GREENE: Alright, Monica dear, I'm gonna hit the road. Now I've left my 10 verbs onthe table. And you be sure and send me that finished poem.",
        "response":"Ok will do. So glad you came.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GREENE: I think I saw Rachel out in the hall.",
        "response":"Ok, let me go check. Your mom want's to say goodbye.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok will do. So glad you came.",
        "response":"MRS. GREENE: I think I saw Rachel out in the hall.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh no, you're not supposed to be here. This is the staging area, you should, it'sall wrong, you should leave, ya know, get out. [opens the door, the guys are right there]Or perhaps you'd like a creme d'menthe.",
        "response":"MR. GREENE: I have to be heading to my chateau, thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. GREENE: I have to be heading to my chateau, thank you.",
        "response":"Oh all right, then I guess we're going back into the hallway.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I ordered mine first.",
        "response":"Yeah, but I'm, I'm so much faster...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh ok.",
        "response":"MRS. GREENE: Happy birthday sweetie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, but I'm, I'm so much faster...",
        "response":"Give it to me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, but I'm, I'm so much faster...",
        "response":"Give it to me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MRS. GREENE: Happy birthday sweetie.",
        "response":"Ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Give it to me.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Give it to me.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, is that when you wrote salt water taffy man?",
        "response":"No. No, he is my submaring guy. He resurfaces like every couple years and we havethe most amazing three days together. Only this time he's coming for two weeks. Two wholeweeks, which means yay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I met him when I was playing guitar in Washington Square Park. Ryan threw insalt water taffy 'cause he didn't have any change.",
        "response":"Hey, is that when you wrote salt water taffy man?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[enters] Hey you guys, you will never guess who's coming to New York.",
        "response":"[Chandler tries to come back with a smart-ass remark but can't swallow themuffin.] Quick, Phoebe, tell us before he can swallow.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Chandler tries to come back with a smart-ass remark but can't swallow themuffin.] Quick, Phoebe, tell us before he can swallow.",
        "response":"Oh ok, Ryan, that guy I went out with, who's in the Navy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line02\"></a> MONICA: [She grabs the coffee cup on the table and licks the rim.]There you go, enjoy your coffee.",
        "response":"That was there when I got here. [Takes a bite of his muffin.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, you can have it. [He licks it and offers it to her.]",
        "response":"<a name=\"line02\"></a> MONICA: [She grabs the coffee cup on the table and licks the rim.]There you go, enjoy your coffee.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Give it to me.",
        "response":"Ok, you can have it. [He licks it and offers it to her.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Give it to me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Give it to me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Monica... [He re-enters the bedroom and Monica jumps on the bed, trying to coverit.] Hey Mon, I have a question. Is Leroy the baddest man in the whole damn town or thefattest man in the whole damn town?",
        "response":"Baddest. Otherwise the song would be Fat Fat Leroy Brown.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[He walks out of the bedroom and Monica starts to remake the bed.]",
        "response":"Monica... [He re-enters the bedroom and Monica jumps on the bed, trying to coverit.] Hey Mon, I have a question. Is Leroy the baddest man in the whole damn town or thefattest man in the whole damn town?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh, then I guess the panty raid last night was totally uncalled for. Ok, I amgoing to take a shower and today I will be singing Jim Crochee's Leroy Brown.",
        "response":"[He walks out of the bedroom and Monica starts to remake the bed.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh no, what happened?",
        "response":"Well, I just spoke to Carol. Ben's got the chicken pox.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Baddest. Otherwise the song would be Fat Fat Leroy Brown.",
        "response":"What're you doing?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Baddest. Otherwise the song would be Fat Fat Leroy Brown.",
        "response":"What're you doing?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh no.",
        "response":"Yeah, so if you haven't already had it, chances are you're gonna get it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I just spoke to Carol. Ben's got the chicken pox.",
        "response":"Oh no.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[enters] Hiii.",
        "response":"Oh no, what happened?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line05\"></a> MONICA: If I tell you, you'll think I'm crazy.",
        "response":"You're pretty much running that risk either way.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Then, you're redoing it because...",
        "response":"<a name=\"line05\"></a> MONICA: If I tell you, you'll think I'm crazy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry, I'm sorry. You know what, the way you did it was just fine.",
        "response":"Then, you're redoing it because...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you remaking the bed?",
        "response":"I'm sorry, I'm sorry. You know what, the way you did it was just fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you remaking the bed?",
        "response":"I'm sorry, I'm sorry. You know what, the way you did it was just fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Just waiting for you sweetie.",
        "response":"Are you remaking the bed?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Just waiting for you sweetie.",
        "response":"Are you remaking the bed?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What're you doing?",
        "response":"Just waiting for you sweetie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What're you doing?",
        "response":"Just waiting for you sweetie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, you see these little flower blossoms? They should be facing up, not down,because, well, the head of the bed is where the sun would be. You don't love me any moredo you.",
        "response":"Actually, if it's possible, I love you more.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It's not that hard to learn. And as for people realizing you have no idea whatyou're doing, hey, you're an actor. Act like a processor, people will think you're aprocessor.",
        "response":"[enters] Hey Chandler, here's this morning's projections.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But don't you need experience for a job like that?",
        "response":"It's not that hard to learn. And as for people realizing you have no idea whatyou're doing, hey, you're an actor. Act like a processor, people will think you're aprocessor.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, look Joey, I'm just saying if you need something to hold you over, I canget you a job right here as an entry level processor.",
        "response":"But don't you need experience for a job like that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, alright.",
        "response":"Alright, you see these little flower blossoms? They should be facing up, not down,because, well, the head of the bed is where the sun would be. You don't love me any moredo you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, alright.",
        "response":"Alright, you see these little flower blossoms? They should be facing up, not down,because, well, the head of the bed is where the sun would be. You don't love me any moredo you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, you see, the tag shouldn't be at the top left corner, it should be at thebottom right corner.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line06\"></a> RICHARD: Oh, well that's not so crazy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line06\"></a> RICHARD: Oh, well that's not so crazy.",
        "response":"I'm just easing you in.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm just easing you in.",
        "response":"Oh, alright.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah? Are you sure, really. [She picks up a mirror and sees the white splotchesall over her face.]",
        "response":"<a name=\"line09\"></a> RACHEL: You see, you look beautiful. For god sakes, dim the lights.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[enters] Hey Chandler, here's this morning's projections.",
        "response":"Hey thanks. Scott Alexander, Joey Tribbianni. Joey is a uh, fellow processor.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[enters] Hey Chandler, here's this morning's projections.",
        "response":"Hey thanks. Scott Alexander, Joey Tribbianni. Joey is a uh, fellow processor.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line08\"></a> JOEY: Oh yeah yeah. I process. People want the processing, I'm theone they call.",
        "response":"Where do you work?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line09\"></a> RACHEL: You see, you look beautiful. For god sakes, dim the lights.",
        "response":"I, I, I'm hideous.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No kidding.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line08\"></a> JOEY: Oh yeah yeah. I process. People want the processing, I'm theone they call.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey thanks. Scott Alexander, Joey Tribbianni. Joey is a uh, fellow processor.",
        "response":"No kidding.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey baby, I'm back... [Phoebe is sitting by the window in a veil.]",
        "response":"Hey Ryan, what's up?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Come in.",
        "response":"Hey baby, I'm back... [Phoebe is sitting by the window in a veil.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why aren't you at home in bed?",
        "response":"'Cause my, my grandmother's never had chicken pox. Please, please tell me youhave, 'cause oh my God, I forgot how cute you are.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why aren't you at home in bed?",
        "response":"'Cause my, my grandmother's never had chicken pox. Please, please tell me youhave, 'cause oh my God, I forgot how cute you are.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line11\"></a> PHOEBE: Well, no no, you have to stay back. I, I have the pox.",
        "response":"Chicken or small?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chicken. Which is so ironic considering I'm a vegetarian.",
        "response":"Why aren't you at home in bed?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chicken. Which is so ironic considering I'm a vegetarian.",
        "response":"Why aren't you at home in bed?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's goin' on?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line11\"></a> PHOEBE: Well, no no, you have to stay back. I, I have the pox.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey baby, I'm back... [Phoebe is sitting by the window in a veil.]",
        "response":"Hey Ryan, what's up?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chicken or small?",
        "response":"Chicken. Which is so ironic considering I'm a vegetarian.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey Ryan, what's up?",
        "response":"What's goin' on?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line12\"></a> RYAN: If I had one wish, it would be to build a time machine, goback to when I was 7, when Jimmy Hauser had the chicken pox. I would grab that kid and rubhim all over my face.",
        "response":"Yeah, or you know, you could just wish that I didn't have them now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ohh, ohh.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line12\"></a> RYAN: If I had one wish, it would be to build a time machine, goback to when I was 7, when Jimmy Hauser had the chicken pox. I would grab that kid and rubhim all over my face.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"'Cause my, my grandmother's never had chicken pox. Please, please tell me youhave, 'cause oh my God, I forgot how cute you are.",
        "response":"I'm sorry, I never had 'em.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"'Cause my, my grandmother's never had chicken pox. Please, please tell me youhave, 'cause oh my God, I forgot how cute you are.",
        "response":"I'm sorry, I never had 'em.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, or you know, you could just wish that I didn't have them now.",
        "response":"Can I please see your face?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nope. You don't want to see a face covered with pox.",
        "response":"Your face could be covered with lochs, I wouldn't care.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Can I please see your face?",
        "response":"Nope. You don't want to see a face covered with pox.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Can I please see your face?",
        "response":"Nope. You don't want to see a face covered with pox.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry, I never had 'em.",
        "response":"Ohh, ohh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line13\"></a> PHOEBE: I hate this. 'Cause I tell you, I had the most amazing twoweeks planned for us, and almost everything I had in mind, we had to be a lot closer thanthis.",
        "response":"Phoebe, I have spent the last eight months in a steel tube with men, thinking aboutthis moment. I am not gonna let a bunch of itchy spots stand between us. [He walks to herand kisses her.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And you hate fish. Oh. That's so sweet, alright. Ok, alright, you can see. This isme... [she unveils herself right as a huge lightning bolt crashes outside. Ryan screams interror.] Oh, I am scary.",
        "response":"Sorry, the lightning. Lightning was an unfortunate incidence. You look lovely,lovely.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Your face could be covered with lochs, I wouldn't care.",
        "response":"And you hate fish. Oh. That's so sweet, alright. Ok, alright, you can see. This isme... [she unveils herself right as a huge lightning bolt crashes outside. Ryan screams interror.] Oh, I am scary.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Your face could be covered with lochs, I wouldn't care.",
        "response":"And you hate fish. Oh. That's so sweet, alright. Ok, alright, you can see. This isme... [she unveils herself right as a huge lightning bolt crashes outside. Ryan screams interror.] Oh, I am scary.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sorry, the lightning. Lightning was an unfortunate incidence. You look lovely,lovely.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line13\"></a> PHOEBE: I hate this. 'Cause I tell you, I had the most amazing twoweeks planned for us, and almost everything I had in mind, we had to be a lot closer thanthis.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, how's the first day goin'?",
        "response":"Pretty good. It's like you said. It's mostly just putting numbers from one columninto another column.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, how's the first day goin'?",
        "response":"Pretty good. It's like you said. It's mostly just putting numbers from one columninto another column.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nope. You don't want to see a face covered with pox.",
        "response":"Your face could be covered with lochs, I wouldn't care.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey.",
        "response":"Hey, how's the first day goin'?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Jeannie, the head of east coast operations Jeannie?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line14\"></a> JOEY: Yeah, turns out our kids go to the same school. Small worldhuh?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey and everbody is so nice. I just had a good talk with that lady with the redhair, Jeannie.",
        "response":"Jeannie, the head of east coast operations Jeannie?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line15\"></a> JOEY: I figure my character has kids.",
        "response":"Ya know there isn't a part of that sentence I don't need explained.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Pretty good. It's like you said. It's mostly just putting numbers from one columninto another column.",
        "response":"Well there you go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Pretty good. It's like you said. It's mostly just putting numbers from one columninto another column.",
        "response":"Well there you go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line14\"></a> JOEY: Yeah, turns out our kids go to the same school. Small worldhuh?",
        "response":"Weird world. Your kids?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well there you go.",
        "response":"Hey and everbody is so nice. I just had a good talk with that lady with the redhair, Jeannie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well there you go.",
        "response":"Hey and everbody is so nice. I just had a good talk with that lady with the redhair, Jeannie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Weird world. Your kids?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line15\"></a> JOEY: I figure my character has kids.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ya know there isn't a part of that sentence I don't need explained.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line16\"></a> JOEY: Well, see when you're acting you need to think about stufflike that. My character, Joseph the processor guy, has two little girls, Ashley andBrittany. Ashley copies everything Brittany does.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line16\"></a> JOEY: Well, see when you're acting you need to think about stufflike that. My character, Joseph the processor guy, has two little girls, Ashley andBrittany. Ashley copies everything Brittany does.",
        "response":"Well, invisible kids can be that way sometimes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line17\"></a> JOEY: Yeah. Joseph and his wife, Karen, are thinking of having athird kid... Ya know what? Just did.",
        "response":"Really? Wow. That's some pretty powerful imaginary sperm you must have there.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Fine.",
        "response":"Let's just play, ok. Good, ok. [She picks up the dice.] Here we go, double sixes,here we go... [She starts to rub the dice all over herself.] Here we go, come to mama,just getting ready to roll the dice...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Fine.",
        "response":"Let's just play, ok. Good, ok. [She picks up the dice.] Here we go, double sixes,here we go... [She starts to rub the dice all over herself.] Here we go, come to mama,just getting ready to roll the dice...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, invisible kids can be that way sometimes.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line17\"></a> JOEY: Yeah. Joseph and his wife, Karen, are thinking of having athird kid... Ya know what? Just did.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know what makes the itching even worse?",
        "response":"That you don't stop talking about it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That you don't stop talking about it.",
        "response":"Fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"That you don't stop talking about it.",
        "response":"Fine.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Let's just play, ok. Good, ok. [She picks up the dice.] Here we go, double sixes,here we go... [She starts to rub the dice all over herself.] Here we go, come to mama,just getting ready to roll the dice...",
        "response":"What're you doing? Are you scratching?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Let's just play, ok. Good, ok. [She picks up the dice.] Here we go, double sixes,here we go... [She starts to rub the dice all over herself.] Here we go, come to mama,just getting ready to roll the dice...",
        "response":"What're you doing? Are you scratching?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. This is what I do for luck, ok.",
        "response":"You're scratching. Give me the dice.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. This is what I do for luck, ok.",
        "response":"You're scratching. Give me the dice.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What're you doing? Are you scratching?",
        "response":"No. This is what I do for luck, ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What're you doing? Are you scratching?",
        "response":"No. This is what I do for luck, ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're scratching. Give me the dice.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're scratching. Give me the dice.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Give me the dice.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We can't scratch. You know we can't, we'll scar.",
        "response":"Uhh, I can't stop thinking about it. It's just so hard. I just wanna grab allthese houses and rub 'em all over my body. [Grabs a handful of the houses.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We can't scratch. You know we can't, we'll scar.",
        "response":"Uhh, I can't stop thinking about it. It's just so hard. I just wanna grab allthese houses and rub 'em all over my body. [Grabs a handful of the houses.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uhh, I can't stop thinking about it. It's just so hard. I just wanna grab allthese houses and rub 'em all over my body. [Grabs a handful of the houses.]",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uhh, I can't stop thinking about it. It's just so hard. I just wanna grab allthese houses and rub 'em all over my body. [Grabs a handful of the houses.]",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. Here. [Throws them on the table.] There. Ooh, double sixes.",
        "response":"We can't scratch. You know we can't, we'll scar.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. Here. [Throws them on the table.] There. Ooh, double sixes.",
        "response":"We can't scratch. You know we can't, we'll scar.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Give me the dice.",
        "response":"No. Here. [Throws them on the table.] There. Ooh, double sixes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Give me the dice.",
        "response":"No. Here. [Throws them on the table.] There. Ooh, double sixes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Give me the dice.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, come on. You know you want it, you know you want it too, come on. Let's justbe bad, it'll feel so good. [She starts scratching him.]",
        "response":"Oh God help me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, come on. You know you want it, you know you want it too, come on. Let's justbe bad, it'll feel so good. [She starts scratching him.]",
        "response":"Oh God help me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Yeah, come on. You know you want it, you know you want it too, come on. Let's justbe bad, it'll feel so good. [She starts scratching him.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Yeah, come on. You know you want it, you know you want it too, come on. Let's justbe bad, it'll feel so good. [She starts scratching him.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God help me.",
        "response":"Now do me, do my back. Oh come on, harder.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Give it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No.",
        "response":"Give it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Give it.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Give it.",
        "response":"No.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You and Milton have to join us on the boat. Karen'll pack a lunch, you'll bring thekids, we'll make a day of it.",
        "response":"Oh, that sounds lovely. We're gonna have to set that up. Oh, I better get back.Hope the baby feels better.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that sounds lovely. We're gonna have to set that up. Oh, I better get back.Hope the baby feels better.",
        "response":"Oh, thanks, thanks. Bye bye Jeannie.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What a phony.",
        "response":"Well, I'm sure you'll teach her a lesson when she steps off the dock ontonothing. Hey Mr. Douglas.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I'm sure you'll teach her a lesson when she steps off the dock ontonothing. Hey Mr. Douglas.",
        "response":"Sir.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, thanks, thanks. Bye bye Jeannie.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line18\"></a> JEANNIE: Bye bye Joey.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joseph's good, isn't he?",
        "response":"Well, I'm going to kill you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joseph's good, isn't he?",
        "response":"Well, I'm going to kill you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line18\"></a> JEANNIE: Bye bye Joey.",
        "response":"What a phony.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, if you say so sir.",
        "response":"Joseph's good, isn't he?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I'm going to kill you.",
        "response":"Hey, hey, I just figure Joseph's the kinda guy that likes to mix it up. Ya know, getin there, ruffle some feathers.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I'm going to kill you.",
        "response":"Hey, hey, I just figure Joseph's the kinda guy that likes to mix it up. Ya know, getin there, ruffle some feathers.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why?",
        "response":"Look, I'm sorry but that's what Joseph does, ok. If you try to pull somethin', he'llcall you on it. 'What're you tryin' to pull,' he'll say.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, hey, I just figure Joseph's the kinda guy that likes to mix it up. Ya know, getin there, ruffle some feathers.",
        "response":"Why?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, hey, I just figure Joseph's the kinda guy that likes to mix it up. Ya know, getin there, ruffle some feathers.",
        "response":"Why?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ooh, duct tape. Was I supposed to bring something too?",
        "response":"This is for the scratchy twins out there. I taped oven mits to their hands.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This is for the scratchy twins out there. I taped oven mits to their hands.",
        "response":"You're strict.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"This is for the scratchy twins out there. I taped oven mits to their hands.",
        "response":"You're strict.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're strict.",
        "response":"It's for their own good.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know what. Tomorrow I'm gonna do your clocks.",
        "response":"You're gonna do what to my clocks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know what. Tomorrow I'm gonna do your clocks.",
        "response":"You're gonna do what to my clocks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're gonna do what to my clocks.",
        "response":"I'm gonna set them to my time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're gonna do what to my clocks.",
        "response":"I'm gonna set them to my time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thank you.",
        "response":"You know what. Tomorrow I'm gonna do your clocks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thank you.",
        "response":"You know what. Tomorrow I'm gonna do your clocks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"If it's not a right angle, it is a wrong angle.",
        "response":"Very good.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Very good.",
        "response":"Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Very good.",
        "response":"Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line22\"></a> MONICA: No no. See, in my bedroom I set my clock six minutes fast.You wanna know why?",
        "response":"Because it's in a slightly different time zone than the kitchen.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I'm confused. I thought we shared time.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line22\"></a> MONICA: No no. See, in my bedroom I set my clock six minutes fast.You wanna know why?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Because it's in a slightly different time zone than the kitchen.",
        "response":"No forget it, I'm not gonna tell you now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm gonna set them to my time.",
        "response":"Well, I'm confused. I thought we shared time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No forget it, I'm not gonna tell you now.",
        "response":"No come on. Come on tell me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No forget it, I'm not gonna tell you now.",
        "response":"No come on. Come on tell me.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No come on. Come on tell me.",
        "response":"No. See you don't understand.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No come on. Come on tell me.",
        "response":"No. See you don't understand.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. See you don't understand.",
        "response":"Come on.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. You don't have any of these cute little obsessive things.",
        "response":"No that's not true. That is not true.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. You don't have any of these cute little obsessive things.",
        "response":"No that's not true. That is not true.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Come on.",
        "response":"No. You don't have any of these cute little obsessive things.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Come on.",
        "response":"No. You don't have any of these cute little obsessive things.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. See you don't understand.",
        "response":"Come on.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No that's not true. That is not true.",
        "response":"Oh yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No that's not true. That is not true.",
        "response":"Oh yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah.",
        "response":"Yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line23\"></a> MONICA: You would not. I can't believe this. I hate this, you're toonormal. I can't believe my boyfriend doesn't have a thing. My boyfriend doesn't have athing.",
        "response":"See, if anyone overheard that, I didn't come off well.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Boy I would just uh, I would freak out.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line23\"></a> MONICA: You would not. I can't believe this. I hate this, you're toonormal. I can't believe my boyfriend doesn't have a thing. My boyfriend doesn't have athing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, well tell me one of yours.",
        "response":"Ok. Ahh. One of my things is, I always separate my sweat socks from my dresssocks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, well tell me one of yours.",
        "response":"Ok. Ahh. One of my things is, I always separate my sweat socks from my dresssocks.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok. Ahh. One of my things is, I always separate my sweat socks from my dresssocks.",
        "response":"What if they get mixed up?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok. Ahh. One of my things is, I always separate my sweat socks from my dresssocks.",
        "response":"What if they get mixed up?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What if they get mixed up?",
        "response":"Boy I would just uh, I would freak out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Alright, well tell me one of yours.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah.",
        "response":"Alright, well tell me one of yours.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Becasue at first he thought it was Joseph. But after he asked Joseph about it, turnsout it was you. Anyway, I just thought you should know.",
        "response":"Alright, that's it. Look Joey, I'm sorry, I realize this is the role of alifetime for ya, and if I could just fire Joseph, I would, but unfortunately that's notpossible so I'm gonna have to let both of you go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Becasue at first he thought it was Joseph. But after he asked Joseph about it, turnsout it was you. Anyway, I just thought you should know.",
        "response":"Alright, that's it. Look Joey, I'm sorry, I realize this is the role of alifetime for ya, and if I could just fire Joseph, I would, but unfortunately that's notpossible so I'm gonna have to let both of you go.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wha- wh- why, why, why does he suspect that?",
        "response":"Becasue at first he thought it was Joseph. But after he asked Joseph about it, turnsout it was you. Anyway, I just thought you should know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wha- wh- why, why, why does he suspect that?",
        "response":"Becasue at first he thought it was Joseph. But after he asked Joseph about it, turnsout it was you. Anyway, I just thought you should know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why? Wh- wh- why is Mr. Douglas looking for me?",
        "response":"'Cause he has a strong suspicion that you dropped the ball on the Lender project.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why? Wh- wh- why is Mr. Douglas looking for me?",
        "response":"'Cause he has a strong suspicion that you dropped the ball on the Lender project.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"'Cause he has a strong suspicion that you dropped the ball on the Lender project.",
        "response":"Wha- wh- why, why, why does he suspect that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"'Cause he has a strong suspicion that you dropped the ball on the Lender project.",
        "response":"Wha- wh- why, why, why does he suspect that?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey. Mr. Douglas is looking for you.",
        "response":"Why? Wh- wh- why is Mr. Douglas looking for me?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, that's it. Look Joey, I'm sorry, I realize this is the role of alifetime for ya, and if I could just fire Joseph, I would, but unfortunately that's notpossible so I'm gonna have to let both of you go.",
        "response":"What're you talking about, everybody loves Joseph.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, that's it. Look Joey, I'm sorry, I realize this is the role of alifetime for ya, and if I could just fire Joseph, I would, but unfortunately that's notpossible so I'm gonna have to let both of you go.",
        "response":"What're you talking about, everybody loves Joseph.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah. Well you can't fire Joseph. You know why, 'cause he's not in yourdepartment.",
        "response":"Alright, ok, alright. So I can't fire Joseph but uh, I can sleep with his wife.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah. Well you can't fire Joseph. You know why, 'cause he's not in yourdepartment.",
        "response":"Alright, ok, alright. So I can't fire Joseph but uh, I can sleep with his wife.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't, I hate Joseph, ok. I think he's a brown-nosing suck up.",
        "response":"Oh yeah. Well you can't fire Joseph. You know why, 'cause he's not in yourdepartment.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I don't, I hate Joseph, ok. I think he's a brown-nosing suck up.",
        "response":"Oh yeah. Well you can't fire Joseph. You know why, 'cause he's not in yourdepartment.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What're you talking about, everybody loves Joseph.",
        "response":"I don't, I hate Joseph, ok. I think he's a brown-nosing suck up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What're you talking about, everybody loves Joseph.",
        "response":"I don't, I hate Joseph, ok. I think he's a brown-nosing suck up.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, ok, alright. So I can't fire Joseph but uh, I can sleep with his wife.",
        "response":"Karen.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ahh. What the hell are you doing to me man.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line25\"></a> CHANDLER: Oh well it's not me, it's my character, Chandy. Yeah therogue processor who seduces his co-worker's wives for sport and then laughs about it thenext day at the water cooler. In fact, I have her panties right there in my drawer.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line25\"></a> CHANDLER: Oh well it's not me, it's my character, Chandy. Yeah therogue processor who seduces his co-worker's wives for sport and then laughs about it thenext day at the water cooler. In fact, I have her panties right there in my drawer.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line24\"></a> CHANDLER: Yeah, Karen. I'm thinking about having an affair with her.Oh, you know what? I just did.",
        "response":"Ahh. What the hell are you doing to me man.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Karen.",
        "response":"<a name=\"line24\"></a> CHANDLER: Yeah, Karen. I'm thinking about having an affair with her.Oh, you know what? I just did.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No freakshow, she's fictional.",
        "response":"Take it easy. If it means that much to you, I'll uh, I'll go find something else.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No freakshow, she's fictional.",
        "response":"Take it easy. If it means that much to you, I'll uh, I'll go find something else.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Take it easy. If it means that much to you, I'll uh, I'll go find something else.",
        "response":"Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Take it easy. If it means that much to you, I'll uh, I'll go find something else.",
        "response":"Thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"No freakshow, she's fictional.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"And there's a peach cobbler warming in the oven so the plate's gonna be hot butthat shouldn't be a problem for you.",
        "response":"Alright you kids, bye now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Thank you.",
        "response":"It's just that, I, I'm gonna miss Joseph. I liked him. His wife, she was hot.[Chadler pushes him out the door by the face.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I got it. [Wipes it up with her mits.]",
        "response":"[Puts his hands over Phoebe's ears.] I must tell you, you look beautiful tonight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, dinner's on.",
        "response":"And there's a peach cobbler warming in the oven so the plate's gonna be hot butthat shouldn't be a problem for you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Please. [Ryan pulls the cork with his teeth and spits it into Phoebe's mits.]",
        "response":"Oh, I spilled some.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Please. [Ryan pulls the cork with his teeth and spits it into Phoebe's mits.]",
        "response":"Oh, I spilled some.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wine?",
        "response":"Please. [Ryan pulls the cork with his teeth and spits it into Phoebe's mits.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I spilled some.",
        "response":"I got it. [Wipes it up with her mits.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, I spilled some.",
        "response":"I got it. [Wipes it up with her mits.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[They start to kiss. They try to get each other's shirts off but can't get the buttonsundone.]",
        "response":"You know what, that's it, that's it. [She rips off the mits, Ryan follows herlead.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I got it. [Wipes it up with her mits.]",
        "response":"[Puts his hands over Phoebe's ears.] I must tell you, you look beautiful tonight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Puts his hands over Phoebe's ears.] I must tell you, you look beautiful tonight.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"[Puts his hands over Phoebe's ears.] I must tell you, you look beautiful tonight.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh.",
        "response":"[They start to kiss. They try to get each other's shirts off but can't get the buttonsundone.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Sorry. You look beautiful.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"Sorry. You look beautiful.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Monica, wake up. Monica.",
        "response":"What's up?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sorry. You look beautiful.",
        "response":"Oh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No honey. You have to sleep on this side of the bed because I have to sleep onthis side of the bed.",
        "response":"Or so I would have you believe.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. I have to sleep, have to, on this side of the bed.",
        "response":"No honey. You have to sleep on this side of the bed because I have to sleep onthis side of the bed.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah. I have to sleep, have to, on this side of the bed.",
        "response":"No honey. You have to sleep on this side of the bed because I have to sleep onthis side of the bed.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah?",
        "response":"Yeah. I have to sleep, have to, on this side of the bed.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah?",
        "response":"Yeah. I have to sleep, have to, on this side of the bed.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's up?",
        "response":"I thought of a thing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's up?",
        "response":"I thought of a thing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I thought of a thing.",
        "response":"Yeah?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I thought of a thing.",
        "response":"Yeah?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, go on.",
        "response":"Ok, I have to sleep on the west side because I grew up in California andotherwise the ocean would be on the wrong side.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Alright, go on.",
        "response":"Ok, I have to sleep on the west side because I grew up in California andotherwise the ocean would be on the wrong side.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. Big deal, so you have a side of the bed, everybody has a side of the bed.",
        "response":"Hey come on, you haven't heard my reason yet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No. Big deal, so you have a side of the bed, everybody has a side of the bed.",
        "response":"Hey come on, you haven't heard my reason yet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No honey. You have to sleep on this side of the bed because I have to sleep onthis side of the bed.",
        "response":"Or so I would have you believe.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Or so I would have you believe.",
        "response":"No. Big deal, so you have a side of the bed, everybody has a side of the bed.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Or so I would have you believe.",
        "response":"No. Big deal, so you have a side of the bed, everybody has a side of the bed.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey come on, you haven't heard my reason yet.",
        "response":"Alright, go on.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey come on, you haven't heard my reason yet.",
        "response":"Alright, go on.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, I have to sleep on the west side because I grew up in California andotherwise the ocean would be on the wrong side.",
        "response":"Oh my God, you're a freak.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ok, I have to sleep on the west side because I grew up in California andotherwise the ocean would be on the wrong side.",
        "response":"Oh my God, you're a freak.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well do you get to look through one of those like, those periscope thingys.",
        "response":"I'm sorry, but I can't say.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow, it, it's neat learning about submarines.",
        "response":"I better get out of here, I'm gonna miss my flight.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I can't say.",
        "response":"Well do you get to look through one of those like, those periscope thingys.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I really can't say.",
        "response":"So do you have like any nuclear weapons on board?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry, but I can't say.",
        "response":"Wow, it, it's neat learning about submarines.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So do you have like any nuclear weapons on board?",
        "response":"I can't say.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God, you're a freak.",
        "response":"Yeah. How 'bout that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Can you believe how we spent our two weeks together?",
        "response":"<a name=\"line28\"></a> PHOEBE: I know. We didn't do any of the romantic things I hadplanned, like having a picnic at Central Park and ya know, coffee at Central Perk. Oh Ijust got that. [They kiss.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So do you uh, think we can get you one of those uh, uniform things?",
        "response":"You like that do ya?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah.",
        "response":"I'll make some calls. [Runs off.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh yeah.",
        "response":"I'll make some calls. [Runs off.]",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'll make some calls. [Runs off.]",
        "response":"Ok.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It was nice to meet you.",
        "response":"Take care.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Pleasure.",
        "response":"It was nice to meet you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You like that do ya?",
        "response":"Oh yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You like that do ya?",
        "response":"Oh yeah.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well then uh, we better make this night count. [He starts to carry her out.] Ohwait, I forgot to turn off the cappucino machine. [He carries her over to turn it off.]Anchors away. Oh no no, my purse, my purse, my purse, my purse, my purse, my pu rse. [Hecarries her to the counter to pick up her purse.] Oh, you know what. I forgot to turn offthe bathroom light.",
        "response":"Alright you know, why don't I just meet you upstairs. [Drops her on the couch andwalks out holding his lower back.]</font></p><p align=\"center\"><strong><font size=\"3\">END</font></strong></p><hr><p align=\"center\"><!--webbot bot=\"ImageMap\" startspanrectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/224bamw.htm\"rectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2.htm\"rectangle=\"    http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/222towtp.htm\"src=\"contrl08.gif\" width=\"194\" height=\"60\"alt=\"contrl08.gif \" --><MAP NAME=\"FrontPageMap0\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"139, 2, 197, 84\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/224bamw.htm\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"71, 1, 128, 84\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2.htm\"><AREA SHAPE=\"RECT\" COORDS=\"0, 2, 59, 80\" HREF=\"http://www.geocities.com/TelevisionCity/Set/5799/season2/222towtp.htm\"></MAP><img src=\"contrl08.gif\" width=\"194\" height=\"60\" alt=\"contrl08.gif \" usemap=\"#FrontPageMap0\"><!--webbot bot=\"ImageMap\" i-checksum=\"22877\" endspan--></p><hr><center><img src=\"/cgi-bin/counter/223\"></center><hr></body></html>",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm shipping out tomorrow.",
        "response":"Well then uh, we better make this night count. [He starts to carry her out.] Ohwait, I forgot to turn off the cappucino machine. [He carries her over to turn it off.]Anchors away. Oh no no, my purse, my purse, my purse, my purse, my purse, my pu rse. [Hecarries her to the counter to pick up her purse.] Oh, you know what. I forgot to turn offthe bathroom light.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"<a name=\"line28\"></a> PHOEBE: I know. We didn't do any of the romantic things I hadplanned, like having a picnic at Central Park and ya know, coffee at Central Perk. Oh Ijust got that. [They kiss.]",
        "response":"Taxi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Incredible! I met the director this time and you'll never believe who it was.",
        "response":"Who?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh I'm sorry, we're clo-... Hey sailor.",
        "response":"Is this what you had in mind?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Who?",
        "response":"All right. I'll give you one hint. Warren Beatty.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Who?",
        "response":"All right. I'll give you one hint. Warren Beatty.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right. I'll give you one hint. Warren Beatty.",
        "response":"Wow!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Is this what you had in mind?",
        "response":"I'll say.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Then what's the problem?",
        "response":"See after the scene, Mr. Beatty comes up to me and says 'good actor, bad kisser'.Can you believe that, me not a good kisser, that's like, like Mother Theresa, not a goodmother.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"No, as part of the audition. See, I'm up for this part of this guy, who the main guykisses.",
        "response":"Well, hey. You're an actor, I say you just suck it up and do it.  Or you just do it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, there's just one thing that might be kind've a problem. See, I, uh, had tokiss this guy.",
        "response":"'Cause he was just so darn cute.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, hey. You're an actor, I say you just suck it up and do it.  Or you just do it.",
        "response":"I did do it, I'm a professional.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"'Cause he was just so darn cute.",
        "response":"No, as part of the audition. See, I'm up for this part of this guy, who the main guykisses.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Come on, I need your help here.",
        "response":"All right. I'll do it, I kissed him before I can do it again.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow!",
        "response":"Yeah, there's just one thing that might be kind've a problem. See, I, uh, had tokiss this guy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right. I'll give you one hint. Warren Beatty.",
        "response":"Wow!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I did do it, I'm a professional.",
        "response":"Then what's the problem?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, well you promised Barry, you'd marry him.",
        "response":"Look you guys, I have to go, I'm the Maid-of-Honor. And besides you know what Ijust need to be in a room again with these people and feel good about myself.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh, let's go.  Oh, wait I have gum. Okay.  Good, very good, firm but tender. I'd recommend you to a friend.",
        "response":"Then I don't know what it is. What's the problem?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Then I don't know what it is. What's the problem?",
        "response":"Joey, you know, maybe your just not used to kissing men, maybe you just tensed upa little, maybe that's what you need to work on.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You see this, this is a friend.",
        "response":"Uh-huh, let's go.  Oh, wait I have gum. Okay.  Good, very good, firm but tender. I'd recommend you to a friend.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You see this, this is a friend.",
        "response":"Uh-huh, let's go.  Oh, wait I have gum. Okay.  Good, very good, firm but tender. I'd recommend you to a friend.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Joey, you know, maybe your just not used to kissing men, maybe you just tensed upa little, maybe that's what you need to work on.",
        "response":"Yeah, that makes sense.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Because I promised Mindy I would.",
        "response":"Yeah, well you promised Barry, you'd marry him.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right. I'll do it, I kissed him before I can do it again.",
        "response":"You see this, this is a friend.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right. I'll do it, I kissed him before I can do it again.",
        "response":"You see this, this is a friend.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Come on, like you never talk that.",
        "response":"Nooo! Never! I mean, we're living in the moment. God, it is so nice for once tonot have to get all hung up on 'Where is this going?'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Nooo! Never! I mean, we're living in the moment. God, it is so nice for once tonot have to get all hung up on 'Where is this going?'",
        "response":"Afraid to ask him?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I think my boyfriend ever so dreamy, I wonder what our wedding's gonna be like.",
        "response":"What are you talking about? What wedding?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Woo-hoo, geeek!",
        "response":"I like this girl, okay, I seriously like this girl, you now how sometimes I tendget a little defended and quipy...",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, we haven't exactly met, we just stayed up all night talking on theinternet.",
        "response":"Woo-hoo, geeek!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well she totally called me on it, okay. She said, 'cut it out, get real', and Idid.",
        "response":"Wow! What's that like?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What are you talking about? What wedding?",
        "response":"Come on, like you never talk that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What are you talking about? What wedding?",
        "response":"Come on, like you never talk that.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Wow! What's that like?",
        "response":"It's like this, me, no jokes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Awww! You know that's probably why babies learn to talk, so they can tell grownups to cut it out.",
        "response":"Hey, you know I got a question for ya. Just a little thing, no pressure.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Awww! You know that's probably why babies learn to talk, so they can tell grownups to cut it out.",
        "response":"Hey, you know I got a question for ya. Just a little thing, no pressure.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Where's Benny?  There he is!  Where's Benny, there he is.",
        "response":"Awww! You know that's probably why babies learn to talk, so they can tell grownups to cut it out.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, you know I got a question for ya. Just a little thing, no pressure.",
        "response":"Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, you know I got a question for ya. Just a little thing, no pressure.",
        "response":"Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did you ever, uh, like, think about the future?",
        "response":"Sure I do.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.",
        "response":"Did you ever, uh, like, think about the future?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay.",
        "response":"Did you ever, uh, like, think about the future?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Afraid to ask him?",
        "response":"Could not be more terrified.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Did you ever, uh, like, think about the future?",
        "response":"Sure I do.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Honey, you are in it.",
        "response":"Oh God, you are about to get sooo lucky.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Honey, you are in it.",
        "response":"Oh God, you are about to get sooo lucky.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God, you are about to get sooo lucky.",
        "response":"Oh, yeah!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh God, you are about to get sooo lucky.",
        "response":"Oh, yeah!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, am I in it?",
        "response":"Honey, you are in it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, am I in it?",
        "response":"Honey, you are in it.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sure I do.",
        "response":"Yeah, am I in it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sure I do.",
        "response":"Yeah, am I in it?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, uh, sometimes I think about selling my practice, we could move to France,make French toast.",
        "response":"Okay, so, uh, we're in France, we're making the toast. Do you see a littlebassinet in the corner?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, uh, sometimes I think about selling my practice, we could move to France,make French toast.",
        "response":"Okay, so, uh, we're in France, we're making the toast. Do you see a littlebassinet in the corner?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Keep talkin'.",
        "response":"Well, uh, sometimes I think about selling my practice, we could move to France,make French toast.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Keep talkin'.",
        "response":"Well, uh, sometimes I think about selling my practice, we could move to France,make French toast.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, so, uh, we're in France, we're making the toast. Do you see a littlebassinet in the corner?",
        "response":"Like a hound?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, so, uh, we're in France, we're making the toast. Do you see a littlebassinet in the corner?",
        "response":"Like a hound?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Like a hound?",
        "response":"Not a basset, a bassinet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah!",
        "response":"Keep talkin'.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, yeah!",
        "response":"Keep talkin'.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I just think the baby would keep falling off the dog. Do you, uh, do you ,do you not see kids in our future.",
        "response":"Oh, hey. I love children, I have children. I just don't want to be 70 when ourkids go off to college, and our lives can finally start.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well, I just think the baby would keep falling off the dog. Do you, uh, do you ,do you not see kids in our future.",
        "response":"Oh, hey. I love children, I have children. I just don't want to be 70 when ourkids go off to college, and our lives can finally start.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, hey. I love children, I have children. I just don't want to be 70 when ourkids go off to college, and our lives can finally start.",
        "response":"Uh-huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, hey. I love children, I have children. I just don't want to be 70 when ourkids go off to college, and our lives can finally start.",
        "response":"Uh-huh.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You really need the bassinet?",
        "response":"Well, I just think the baby would keep falling off the dog. Do you, uh, do you ,do you not see kids in our future.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You really need the bassinet?",
        "response":"Well, I just think the baby would keep falling off the dog. Do you, uh, do you ,do you not see kids in our future.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Not a basset, a bassinet.",
        "response":"You really need the bassinet?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Not a basset, a bassinet.",
        "response":"You really need the bassinet?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Like a hound?",
        "response":"Not a basset, a bassinet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Look I want you, now.",
        "response":"That's Great. You know we don't need to talk about this now. Really, I mean thisis, is so way, way, way, in the future, I'm talkin' hovercrafts and apes taking over theplanet.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So how's your date with your cyberchick going. Ooh, hey, what is all that .",
        "response":"Oh, it's a website, it's the, uh, the Guggenheim <i></i>museum. See, she likes art, and I like funny words.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, it's a website, it's the, uh, the Guggenheim <i></i>museum. See, she likes art, and I like funny words.",
        "response":"What does she mean by HH?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, it's a website, it's the, uh, the Guggenheim <i></i>museum. See, she likes art, and I like funny words.",
        "response":"What does she mean by HH?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What does she mean by HH?",
        "response":"It means we're holding hands.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What does she mean by HH?",
        "response":"It means we're holding hands.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It means we're holding hands.",
        "response":"Are you the cutest?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh.",
        "response":"Look I want you, now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh-huh.",
        "response":"Look I want you, now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know, what I think is so great that you are totally into this person and yetfor all you know she could be like 90 years old, or have two heads, or. It could be a guy.",
        "response":"Okay, it's not a guy, all right, I know her.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You know, what I think is so great that you are totally into this person and yetfor all you know she could be like 90 years old, or have two heads, or. It could be a guy.",
        "response":"Okay, it's not a guy, all right, I know her.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm afraid I might just be.",
        "response":"You know, what I think is so great that you are totally into this person and yetfor all you know she could be like 90 years old, or have two heads, or. It could be a guy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm afraid I might just be.",
        "response":"You know, what I think is so great that you are totally into this person and yetfor all you know she could be like 90 years old, or have two heads, or. It could be a guy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It could be like a big giant guy.",
        "response":"Man, I got this close to him  and Monica kneed mein the back. What's going on?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, it's not a guy, all right, I know her.",
        "response":"It could be like a big giant guy.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you the cutest?",
        "response":"I'm afraid I might just be.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you the cutest?",
        "response":"I'm afraid I might just be.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"It means we're holding hands.",
        "response":"Are you the cutest?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"We were just wondering if Chandler's girlfriend is a girl.",
        "response":"Oh, well. Just ask her how long she's gonna live. Women live longer than men.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, ask her 'What is her current method of birth control?'",
        "response":"All right.  &quot;My husband is sleeping with hissecretary.&quot; She's married!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, ask her 'What is her current method of birth control?'",
        "response":"All right.  &quot;My husband is sleeping with hissecretary.&quot; She's married!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Man, I got this close to him  and Monica kneed mein the back. What's going on?",
        "response":"We were just wondering if Chandler's girlfriend is a girl.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Man, I got this close to him  and Monica kneed mein the back. What's going on?",
        "response":"We were just wondering if Chandler's girlfriend is a girl.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right.  &quot;My husband is sleeping with hissecretary.&quot; She's married!",
        "response":"Well at least we know she's a woman.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"All right.  &quot;My husband is sleeping with hissecretary.&quot; She's married!",
        "response":"Well at least we know she's a woman.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"How do you not fall down more?",
        "response":"Okay, ask her 'What is her current method of birth control?'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well at least we know she's a woman.",
        "response":"I can't believe she's married.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"So, I read this article in the paper the other day that says you're not supposedto throw rice at weddings, because when pigeons eat rice it kills them.",
        "response":"Oh, that's why you never see pigeons at sushi bars. See, we're having fun.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you all right?",
        "response":"Yeah, when I was in the bathroom I saw the window that I crawled out of at mywedding, and God, I just started thinking that I shouldn't be here, you know I shouldn't,people are going to be looking at me and judging me and, and thinking about the last time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Are you all right?",
        "response":"Yeah, when I was in the bathroom I saw the window that I crawled out of at mywedding, and God, I just started thinking that I shouldn't be here, you know I shouldn't,people are going to be looking at me and judging me and, and thinking about the last time.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that's why you never see pigeons at sushi bars. See, we're having fun.",
        "response":"Oh, absolutely. Yeah, you know I'm not even thinking about that thing that we'renot supposed to think about.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, that's why you never see pigeons at sushi bars. See, we're having fun.",
        "response":"Oh, absolutely. Yeah, you know I'm not even thinking about that thing that we'renot supposed to think about.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, absolutely. Yeah, you know I'm not even thinking about that thing that we'renot supposed to think about.",
        "response":"Neither am I.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Are you all right?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hi.",
        "response":"Are you all right?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, there.",
        "response":"Hi.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry. What was I supposed to do stand up and shout 'Hey, Rachel, your butt isshowing!'",
        "response":"Oh my God this is sooo humiliating. I think the only thing that tops that was,was, was when I was in the eight grade and I had to sing the Copa Cabana in front of theentire school. I think I got about two lines into it before I ran and freaked out. Oh myGod, my entire life is flashing before my eyes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, when I was in the bathroom I saw the window that I crawled out of at mywedding, and God, I just started thinking that I shouldn't be here, you know I shouldn't,people are going to be looking at me and judging me and, and thinking about the last time.",
        "response":"Sweetie, it's be gonna okay, all right. It's a wedding, generally people focus onthe bride.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, when I was in the bathroom I saw the window that I crawled out of at mywedding, and God, I just started thinking that I shouldn't be here, you know I shouldn't,people are going to be looking at me and judging me and, and thinking about the last time.",
        "response":"Sweetie, it's be gonna okay, all right. It's a wedding, generally people focus onthe bride.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"WEDDING PLANNER: All rightie, everybody look at me. Good. All right, its time. Bridesmaidsand ushers let's see two lines, thank you.",
        "response":"Okay, I'll see you after the thing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"God I know, you're right.",
        "response":"WEDDING PLANNER: All rightie, everybody look at me. Good. All right, its time. Bridesmaidsand ushers let's see two lines, thank you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why the hell didn't you tell me!",
        "response":"I'm sorry. What was I supposed to do stand up and shout 'Hey, Rachel, your butt isshowing!'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Sweetie, it's be gonna okay, all right. It's a wedding, generally people focus onthe bride.",
        "response":"God I know, you're right.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, I'll see you after the thing.",
        "response":"Okay, good luck",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, good luck",
        "response":"Thank you, Okay, Okay.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm sorry. What was I supposed to do stand up and shout 'Hey, Rachel, your butt isshowing!'",
        "response":"Oh my God this is sooo humiliating. I think the only thing that tops that was,was, was when I was in the eight grade and I had to sing the Copa Cabana in front of theentire school. I think I got about two lines into it before I ran and freaked out. Oh myGod, my entire life is flashing before my eyes.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God this is sooo humiliating. I think the only thing that tops that was,was, was when I was in the eight grade and I had to sing the Copa Cabana in front of theentire school. I think I got about two lines into it before I ran and freaked out. Oh myGod, my entire life is flashing before my eyes.",
        "response":"Rach, hey look, I remember that, it wasn't so bad.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God this is sooo humiliating. I think the only thing that tops that was,was, was when I was in the eight grade and I had to sing the Copa Cabana in front of theentire school. I think I got about two lines into it before I ran and freaked out. Oh myGod, my entire life is flashing before my eyes.",
        "response":"Rach, hey look, I remember that, it wasn't so bad.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rach, hey look, I remember that, it wasn't so bad.",
        "response":"Oh Ross, would you stop, you got me, I'm dating you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, now that is the third time someone has said something like that to me today.",
        "response":"Rach! Rach!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh Ross, would you stop, you got me, I'm dating you.",
        "response":"MR. WINEBURG: Rachel!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"MR. WINEBURG: Rachel!",
        "response":"Oh hi, Mr. Wineburg, hi Mrs. Wineburg.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rach! Rach!",
        "response":"Oh, hi!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Rach! Rach!",
        "response":"Oh, hi!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Min. Oh Rach, you're still here, at our wedding, they were packing upthe chopped liver about now.",
        "response":"Yeah, I love that story. Um, I got a question for you guys. Why do people keep issaying that is good to see me up and about?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh honey, I'm so proud of you, Min.",
        "response":"Min. Oh Rach, you're still here, at our wedding, they were packing upthe chopped liver about now.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I'm Mrs. Dr. Barry Hunter hyphen Farber.",
        "response":"Oh honey, I'm so proud of you, Min.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know.",
        "response":"I'm Mrs. Dr. Barry Hunter hyphen Farber.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know.",
        "response":"I'm Mrs. Dr. Barry Hunter hyphen Farber.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God, I'm married!",
        "response":"I know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God, I'm married!",
        "response":"I know.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, hi!",
        "response":"Oh my God, I'm married!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, hi!",
        "response":"Oh my God, I'm married!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, I love that story. Um, I got a question for you guys. Why do people keep issaying that is good to see me up and about?",
        "response":"Well uh, after you ran out on your wedding, Barry's parents told people that youwere sort of....insane.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Aren't you gonna answer her, that's like the tenth bing-bong message she sent. Shewants to know what's wrong?",
        "response":"What's wrong? What's wrong? You're married that's what's wrong.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well uh, after you ran out on your wedding, Barry's parents told people that youwere sort of....insane.",
        "response":"Insane!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Well uh, after you ran out on your wedding, Barry's parents told people that youwere sort of....insane.",
        "response":"Insane!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's wrong? What's wrong? You're married that's what's wrong.",
        "response":"Oh, my.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What's wrong? What's wrong? You're married that's what's wrong.",
        "response":"Oh, my.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Insane!",
        "response":"...from the syphilis.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Insane!",
        "response":"...from the syphilis.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"...from the syphilis.",
        "response":"What?!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, look, Phoebe I wanted to meet her in person too, okay, but she's married,she has a husband.",
        "response":"What if the husband person is the wrong guy, and you are the right guy. I mean youdon't get chances like this all the time, if you don't meet her now, you're gonna bekicking yourself when your 80, which is hard to do, and that's how you break a hip.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Hey, look, Phoebe I wanted to meet her in person too, okay, but she's married,she has a husband.",
        "response":"What if the husband person is the wrong guy, and you are the right guy. I mean youdon't get chances like this all the time, if you don't meet her now, you're gonna bekicking yourself when your 80, which is hard to do, and that's how you break a hip.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What if the husband person is the wrong guy, and you are the right guy. I mean youdon't get chances like this all the time, if you don't meet her now, you're gonna bekicking yourself when your 80, which is hard to do, and that's how you break a hip.",
        "response":"Okay, I'll do it!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"She wants to meet you in person.",
        "response":"Hey, look, Phoebe I wanted to meet her in person too, okay, but she's married,she has a husband.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"She wants to meet you in person.",
        "response":"Hey, look, Phoebe I wanted to meet her in person too, okay, but she's married,she has a husband.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"She wants to meet you in person.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What?",
        "response":"She wants to meet you in person.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, my.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh, my.",
        "response":"What?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"What if the husband person is the wrong guy, and you are the right guy. I mean youdon't get chances like this all the time, if you don't meet her now, you're gonna bekicking yourself when your 80, which is hard to do, and that's how you break a hip.",
        "response":"Okay, I'll do it!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, I'll do it!",
        "response":"Oh, yeah! Okay! Great! Go, man, go put on your shoes, and, and march out there andmeet her!  Oh, wait, no, no you have to take ashower, 'cause, eww.  No, youknow what you have to answer her, answer her first.  No,no, you know what make some coffee 'cause its too much.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, last chance.  Again, I'm sorry.",
        "response":"You know what, maybe I don't need to have children. You know maybe I just think Ido because that is what society, and by that I mean my mom, has always convinced me thatI... I do, I have to have children, I'm sorry, Ijust do.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, one more, please. Come on, I'm gonna get it in this time, I will.",
        "response":"Okay, last chance.  Again, I'm sorry.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why are you adding, why are you adding, why are you adding, why are you adding?",
        "response":"Most of you don't know me, I'm Rachel's boyfriend.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Why are you adding, why are you adding, why are you adding, why are you adding?",
        "response":"Most of you don't know me, I'm Rachel's boyfriend.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Most of you don't know me, I'm Rachel's boyfriend.",
        "response":"Oh dear God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Most of you don't know me, I'm Rachel's boyfriend.",
        "response":"Oh dear God.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Uh, I like to, uh, to add something to that...",
        "response":"Why are you adding, why are you adding, why are you adding, why are you adding?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ross, uh and uh, I'd just like to say that it did take a lot of courage for Rachelto come here tonight. And, uh, for the record she did not run out on Barry because she hadsyphilis.   What are you doing I'm serious. Uh, the reason shewalked out on, on Barry is simply that she didn't love him, which incidentally worked outpretty well for me  Cheers.",
        "response":"She you in the parking lot.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Ross, uh and uh, I'd just like to say that it did take a lot of courage for Rachelto come here tonight. And, uh, for the record she did not run out on Barry because she hadsyphilis.   What are you doing I'm serious. Uh, the reason shewalked out on, on Barry is simply that she didn't love him, which incidentally worked outpretty well for me  Cheers.",
        "response":"She you in the parking lot.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh dear God.",
        "response":"Ross, uh and uh, I'd just like to say that it did take a lot of courage for Rachelto come here tonight. And, uh, for the record she did not run out on Barry because she hadsyphilis.   What are you doing I'm serious. Uh, the reason shewalked out on, on Barry is simply that she didn't love him, which incidentally worked outpretty well for me  Cheers.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh dear God.",
        "response":"Ross, uh and uh, I'd just like to say that it did take a lot of courage for Rachelto come here tonight. And, uh, for the record she did not run out on Barry because she hadsyphilis.   What are you doing I'm serious. Uh, the reason shewalked out on, on Barry is simply that she didn't love him, which incidentally worked outpretty well for me  Cheers.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"&quot;...marenge, thank you honey, and do the cha-cha. And while shelike to be a star, Tony always tended bar. At the, wait, wait, everybody..&quot;",
        "response":"Everybody!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"&quot;...marenge, thank you honey, and do the cha-cha. And while shelike to be a star, Tony always tended bar. At the, wait, wait, everybody..&quot;",
        "response":"Everybody!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Everybody!",
        "response":"At the Copa, Copa Cabana  The hottest spot north of Havana. Atthe Copa, Coo-pa Ca-ban-a, music and fashion were always the passion, at the Copa....",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Marenge,",
        "response":"&quot;...marenge, thank you honey, and do the cha-cha. And while shelike to be a star, Tony always tended bar. At the, wait, wait, everybody..&quot;",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"She you in the parking lot.",
        "response":"No, Rach!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God!",
        "response":"If I have to I'll, I'll do all again , I'll do the 4 o'clock feeding thing, I'llgo to the P.T.A. meetings, I'll coach the soccer team.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God!",
        "response":"If I have to I'll, I'll do all again , I'll do the 4 o'clock feeding thing, I'llgo to the P.T.A. meetings, I'll coach the soccer team.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"If I have to I'll, I'll do all again , I'll do the 4 o'clock feeding thing, I'llgo to the P.T.A. meetings, I'll coach the soccer team.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"If I have to I'll, I'll do all again , I'll do the 4 o'clock feeding thing, I'llgo to the P.T.A. meetings, I'll coach the soccer team.",
        "response":"Really?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You'll do what?",
        "response":"If kids is what I takes to be with you then kids it is.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You'll do what?",
        "response":"If kids is what I takes to be with you then kids it is.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"If kids is what I takes to be with you then kids it is.",
        "response":"Oh my God!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"If kids is what I takes to be with you then kids it is.",
        "response":"Oh my God!",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Okay, I'll do it.",
        "response":"You'll do what?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, if I have to. Monica, I don't wanna lose you, so if I have to do it allover again, then I will.",
        "response":"You're the most wonderful man. And if you hadn't of said 'if I have to' likeseventeen times, then I'd be saying 'okay, let's do it.'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Yeah, if I have to. Monica, I don't wanna lose you, so if I have to do it allover again, then I will.",
        "response":"You're the most wonderful man. And if you hadn't of said 'if I have to' likeseventeen times, then I'd be saying 'okay, let's do it.'",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God, I can't believe what I'm getting ready to say. I wanna have a baby, butI don't wanna have one with someone who doesn't really wanna have one.",
        "response":"God. I love you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But you're not.",
        "response":"Oh my God, I can't believe what I'm getting ready to say. I wanna have a baby, butI don't wanna have one with someone who doesn't really wanna have one.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"But you're not.",
        "response":"Oh my God, I can't believe what I'm getting ready to say. I wanna have a baby, butI don't wanna have one with someone who doesn't really wanna have one.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're the most wonderful man. And if you hadn't of said 'if I have to' likeseventeen times, then I'd be saying 'okay, let's do it.'",
        "response":"But you're not.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"You're the most wonderful man. And if you hadn't of said 'if I have to' likeseventeen times, then I'd be saying 'okay, let's do it.'",
        "response":"But you're not.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Yeah, if I have to. Monica, I don't wanna lose you, so if I have to do it allover again, then I will.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Really?",
        "response":"Yeah, if I have to. Monica, I don't wanna lose you, so if I have to do it allover again, then I will.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Oh my God, I can't believe what I'm getting ready to say. I wanna have a baby, butI don't wanna have one with someone who doesn't really wanna have one.",
        "response":"God. I love you.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"God. I love you.",
        "response":"I know you do. Me too.  So what now?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"God. I love you.",
        "response":"I know you do. Me too.  So what now?",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"I know you do. Me too.  So what now?",
        "response":"I guess we just keep dancing.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Where is she, Where is she?  Oh, hey, I have a question, where isshe?",
        "response":"Chandler, relax, Chandler, she'll be here.",
        "is_tmp":false},
      {
        "question":"Chandler, relax, Chandler, she'll be here.",
        "response":"Ooh, oh, oh, that's her.",
        "is_tmp":false}
]
